The Red Night suddenly appears.
Real, yet unreal... just like a parallel dark world in a different space and time.
The Black Knights attacked the boy and the girl, who had fallen down there, and called them “Fragments”,
What kind of breeze has swept them into this sinister place?
By the end of this nightmare, will there be an answer?
We need to find Yuka-san where she would likely go to.
Okay.
I think it's already too late for that.
Takahisa-senpai!
You're a mess!
She was definitely a worthy opponent.
Still, I let her run away.
What do you mean by "too late"?
This is Yuka-san's...
Where was it?
Where did you find it?
The infirmary.
Senpai!
It's a mess though.
The infirmary, that is.
It can't be.
Kakeru-kun is...
Kakeru-kun is changing.
I'm sorry.
Kakeru-kun is...
My Kakeru-kun is...
No...
No!
I don't want that to happen!
The infirmary is completely destroyed.
Yuka...
Yuka!
Calm down, Kakeru.
It's all right, senpai,
Yuka-san is not here.
I don't smell any blood.
Even though there's no proof that she's all right,
it seems she managed to escape.
It hasn't been long. She can't have gone that far.
Let's split up and search for her.
It's dangerous, but we don't have a choice.
Yukiko, Kukuri...
Let's split up and search for her around the school.
Understood.
Kakeru and Takahisa, you two don't look so good.
Until you have regained your strength, look for her inside the school.
No, I want to...
Hey, hey...
Aren't you doing it for your own convenience?
Once you find Yuka, head back to school and meet up with Kakeru and Takahisa.
Then Takahisa will send out a flame signal, after which everyone has to return at once.
You can at least do that, right?
Sure, Miss Captain.
Are you okay with that, Kakeru?
Yes.
Okay, let's go.
Yes, for the sake of friends and tomorrow.
For the sake of friends and tomorrow.
Yuka-san!
Yuka!
Let's head to the gym.
Hey!
Are you all right?
It's all because of me.
If only I hadn't left Yuka alone back then...
Yuka!
I'm sorry.
Yuka...
Please be safe, Yuka.
What's so funny?
My bad, don't get angry.
Kakeru...
I'm just amazed at how openly
you can show your feelings for a girl like that.
What?
A thought came to my mind,
if she were to disappear, would I be as terrified as you are right now?
Yukiko is my closest friend.
When I look at her, it hurts.
It's called karma, right?
Let's not do this anymore.
If you knew my past, then maybe your view about me will change as well.
I've been watching you all this time.
I know that.
Then tell me.
It's a secret.
If you won't let it go, then it'll be hard for me to be with you.
Sounds miserable, right?
Being pitied by a kid like that.
These insects!
Don't eavesdrop on a private conversation!
Takahisa!
Let's go find your princess.
The Black Moon...
It's getting closer and closer.
Yuka-san!
Oh, lost, lost Yuka-san!
Please answer me if you can hear me!
Yuka...
This is...
Thank goodness, Kakeru-kun.
You like it.
Tomorrow, I will make lunch for you again, okay?
Yuka-san!
Hey, Kakeru-kun...
Do you like me?
I really like you.
Yuka-san?
Kakeru-kun?
This is...
That disgusting witch!
Trying to escape, when I am not there.
Superbia.
Yes.
Take care of the vessel of the Eye of Aion and the Fragments.
I am counting on you, Invidia and Scholastica.
Understood, Avaritia-sama.
You heard that, right, Invidia?
You lost pathetically and ended up with a disgusting burnt face.
Now there's only one thing left for you to do!
Yuka-san, are you all right?
If we don't hurry back, everyone will get worried.
Oh right,
let me tell you some good news.
Kukuri-san defeated the Black Knight.
Kukuri-san's power is amazing!
You all are amazing.
What?
You all have such wonderful powers,
and you fight with all your strength.
But not me.
There is no need for you to be upset over that.
You're not fit for fighting.
Since I don't have any power, I feel that I'm losing Kakeru-kun.
What are you talking about?
You know Kakeru-senpai is crazy about you, don't you?
He's fighting hard just to protect you!
I wonder to what extent your love has grown.
These things, these things...
Yuka-san...
I think it's time for me to tell you about my past.
Until my grandfather in Japan took me under his care,
I had been living in a country called Drasvania.
The world I knew... was a hell.
An endless, bloody conflict among races...
Inside that storm of destruction and pillage, people clung to weapons and fought.
Men, women and children as well.
Since I couldn't die,
even after stepping on a landmine, I regenerated and survived.
So I was used as a human weapon.
My family and companions were slaughtered one after another.
That's why I kept killing, ...killing, ...and killing.
"For the sake of my friends and tomorrow."
Those words became my moral support.
My fighting skills and other personality were created in that hell.
If I didn't have those, I would have failed to protect my friends and my future.
If I don't seal my innerself with these glasses,
I'd become something quite dangerous.
Yuka-san...
I don't want you to become someone like me.
That's why, no matter what your power is, it's good that it hasn't awakened yet.
Maybe Kakeru-senpai feels the same way about it.
Yukiko-chan!
Yuka-san...
Yukiko-chan...
It's all right.
It's all right now.
Because...
I am...
It's useless.
I won't let you escape.
That's...
W-What's that light?
You, who were fighting along your brother Benedictus,
Scholastica...
Your vessel of Acadia doesn't exist anymore.
Vanish!
Scholastica...
The Black Knight was...
What happened just now?
You again?
You're quite annoying!
As well as the sin of being a Fragment, you hurt my pride and body.
Now you will pay for that with your life!
How convenient.
Before I go back, I'll kill you!
Then again, I'm pretty empty handed here.
What should we do, Kakeru?
We have no other choice, do we?
If so, then I'll go first.
Kakeru!
Misuzu-senpai!
Good timing.
Here I come!
I'll be your opponent!
Invidia,
there's no need for you to hold back now.
Hurry up and come back, Yukiko, Tachibana-senpai.
Where did she...
Where did she go?
Behind me?
That sword is one of the Kusakabe family's five swords, Kashagiri Hiromitsu.
What?
Your stance is a Kusakabe stance.
You are a Kusakabe onmyouji, aren't you?
How do you know such things?
To think that I'm about to fight a Kusakabe female swordsman,
fate sure is full of ironies.
That is the Kusakabe's duel blade stance.
How do you know...?
It can't be.
My eye...!
Is... is this my limit?
The sin of being a Fragment can be atoned by destruction of the soul.
What incredible power!
I can't move.
Who the hell are you?
Are you...?
The time has come.
You guys can't be allowed to exist!
Tachibana-senpai...
What kept you, Yukiko?
It can't be.
It can't possibly be...
It seems you're not in a condition to fight.
My name is Superbia.
Let's put our fight on hold for now.
I'll leave them to you, Invidia.
Kakeru...
Misuzu-senpai...
What is this thing?
Is it a barrier to seal us?
A barrier?
K-Kill me.
She's planning to self-destruct!
No way!
We must get out of here!
The vessel of the Eye of Aion,
and you Fragments,
will die with me!
Stop that!
Don't touch Kakeru-kun!
That's...
Is that Yuka?
What?
I-It disappeared?
My self-destruct power...
Why?
Yuka...
What happened just now?
What did Yuka do?
I guess her light nullified our powers.
Power?
Yuka has...
...awakened?
That was cool, Yuka!
It's amazing.
But it's dangerous as well.
Dangerous?
You saw it, didn't you?
Not just the enemy's, but our powers were nullified as well.
It's all right, Kakeru-kun.
I'm here to protect you.
That's why, please,
be mine alone.
Mine alone...
Yuka!
He died in battle?
You're lying!
Verard has...
This is unforgivable!
Absolutely unforgivable!
I will destroy this disgusting and tainted world!
This is what Verard and I, Liselotte, wish for!
Yuka...
I didn't want your power to awaken.
I didn't want you to get involved in this fight.
Tachibana-senpai?
It can't be...
That's...
Next time
Witching Hour.
Takahisa, let's go have some yakiniku.
Loin...
Chicken...
Korean...
Just eat whatever you want!