The Red Night suddenly appears.
Real, yet unreal... just like a parallel dark world in a different space and time.
The Black Knights attacked the boy and the girl, who had fallen down there, and called them “Fragments”,
What kind of breeze has swept them into this sinister place?
By the end of this nightmare, will there be an answer?
Was this the result of our pride?
They don’t know what they truly are.
There is nothing more frightening than innocence.
However...
Did you come up with a plan?
Please leave it to me, Avaritia-sama.
Good.
Kakeru-kun...
Ah, I’m sorry, I fell asleep.
Want some water?
It’s okay.
Please rest.
Aren’t you tired?
I need to call my mother.
I already called her, so don’t worry about that.
Thank you.
While we are in this world, there won't be any problems.
Don't worry and sleep well.
I will protect you.
I will always protect you.
Dummy, I should be the one protecting you.
But, thank you anyway.
All right then.
Ah, Yukiko is in her room,
but she's not feeling well.
Yuka is asleep too.
Let's not go to school today.
It would be dangerous to get separated if we got pulled into the Red Night.
Sorry, but can you get me some tea?
We could use her power, couldn't we?
Yuka's power, that is.
We may have a chance to win if we use her power.
However, it also nullifies our power, doesn't it?
Win?
Takahisa, what are we trying to win against?
How should we end all this?
Getting pulled into the Red Night,
and being chased by the Black Knights, we have no other choice but to fight,
in order to protect ourselves.
There's no other way.
After all, they were the ones who attacked us first.
What did they mean by “Fragments”?
The six of us share nothing in common, except that we're all students.
What exactly is this "sin" that that Black Knight referred to?
They attacked us, so we fought.
And we had to win the fight!
That’s all.
Where are you going?
I’m being impatient.
This isn't like me.
The one who awakened the demon is you.
Did you write that?
Who are you?
Are you my ally?
Please don’t hurt Yuka.
I don't care what happens to me.
But, Yuka...
Please.
Hey!
Takahisa-senpai...
Good morning.
Ah, good morning.
How's Yuka?
She’s sleeping.
What are you doing?
Just checking the barrier.
Barrier?
There is one that surrounds the mansion.
It will react if a demon tries to enter.
Demon?
What do you mean to say?
This world is safe, isn’t it?
We must be on our guard.
Can you feel them with your onmyouji power?
Senpai?
Kakeru, come with me for a moment.
Okay.
Kakeru...?
Yes... I... to senpai...
No one cares about such trivial things.
But...
We were in the middle of a fight, so it couldn’t be helped, right?
It’s his mistake that he was carelessly running around.
If you keep worrying about such trivial things,
then winning a fight would be impossible.
First think about winning and about living.
If he had died from that, it would've been his fate.
That's sad.
Then you would end up being alone, right?
What are you talking about?
You've been through it and it helped you survive, right?
Because I couldn't die.
I witnessed many deaths.
The ones I loved and the ones who were close to me, all died.
It’s enough already, it's enough!
My heart broke,
and that gave birth to my other self.
Yukiko...
I convinced myself not to have any more friends.
"It’s okay to be alone."
I thought that was enough.
And yet again it's...
...for the sake of my friends and tomorrow.
I hate the Red Night,
but I'm thankful for it,
since I was able to make friends again.
I was able to meet people who could acknowledge me.
And Takahisa-senpai, I was able to meet you too.
I love everyone.
I really love you all.
That’s why...
That’s why I don’t want to hurt any of you.
You too are no longer alone.
They protected you.
I’ve never thought of making friends with...
It’s not like that.
It’s Saeko-sensei.
Oh, that woman...
It's nothing like that.
By mixing the western and the eastern magic,
a forbidden technique called the “Geihou” was developed.
Seventy years ago,
because of this technique, an onmyouji was exiled from the Kusakabe clan.
Her name was Kusakabe Misao.
Despite being a woman, she mastered all kinds of magic.
When I learned about her, I began to admire her.
Strong and sublime...
That thought of mine hasn’t changed even to this day.
Why are you telling me this?
The Black Knight called Superbia...
...is none other than Kusakabe Misao.
Kakeru-kun?
I don't know why she's in the Red Night, nor do I know how she became a Black Knight.
However, I'm sure that she is Misao.
No way, that's ridiculous!
The one called Misao lived seventy years ago, didn’t she?
So she should be dead now, right?
Inside the Red Night, time stands still.
You must have experienced it.
No matter how long we stay on that side,
the time remains the same as when we got pulled into the Red Night.
She must have been living in that world, in which time stops, for seventy years.
And she became a Black Knight.
There was a warning.
A warning?
This character is engraved on the talismans of "Geihou" magic holders.
Just before the Red Night started,
when I was busy reading fortunes,
I was hit by a dark wind, and this was carved on my body.
The one I once admired has become my enemy.
And if the past is anything to go by, she must still possess massive power.
Right now, I'm in no position to defeat her.
Senpai, what are you...?
Senpai?
Drink my blood.
Kakeru, I'm offering you the power of the Kusakabe clan.
Kakeru-kun...
Now.
It’s for your and Yuka's sake.
Drink it.
Despite getting dragged into the Time of the Witch, I still have my heart.
My loving thoughts for you...
A love with no lies...
I swear to you;
this world that you hated,
the world that stole your future,
I will destroy it.
I will absolutely destroy it with my own hands.
I love you, Verard.
The weather is so good...
Takahisa!
Oh, damn it.
Come with me for a moment.
Ow ow ow...
Hey, stop it already.
Stop complaining.
As I thought, the smell of a fresh can is the best.
You brought me to this place so that I can't attend my class, right?
Oh, were you gonna attend class?
I’m going.
Where were you last night?
At my friend’s house.
Friend?
This is the first time I heard this.
Do I need to tell you everything?
What are you talking about?
You cause problems, but the one who always has to deal with them is me.
Oh, I see, so it’s her.
What?
The cute girl with the glasses.
I see.
So that’s what this is about.
Okay then.
You can go now.
W-Wait a sec.
It isn't like that.
You’re still young, aren’t you?
Listen to me!
Has it really been seven years since I picked you up?
It sure seems like time flew.
Don’t call it “picking up”.
I’m not a thing, okay?
What is it?
Nothing.
Well then, I'll head to the class and take a nap.
Ah right, come here after class, okay?
What?
I get paid today, so let's go get some yakiniku.
Yakiniku?
Okay, got it.
Then take it easy.
If you eat meat without taking rest, you will get sick, you know.
That guy...
To be born in the evening and die the next day was their only wish.
Unknowingly, their lives were nothing more than bubbles breaking on the surface of thew water.
Hey, what’s wrong with Yuka and Kakeru-kun?
I don’t know where the young come from, or where the deceased go,
What are you doing?
This is the flying love letter.
and yet, this world is nothing but a temporary place.
Shiori-chan, please accept it.
Whom should I cry for?
Lovely-love air mail, from Tadashi-kun.
What should I be happy for?
Seeing the people and their lives, I once had a vision of a glorious morning.
Oops!
It got demolished.
Teruya, what are you doing?
Please listen to me, teacher.
My lovely-love air mail was...
Idiot, the class is still going on.
Oh, yeah...
Stupid idiot.
Oh my, really.
Teacher...
What’s the problem, Momono?
I’m not feeling well. I would like to go to the infirmary.
Oh, can you go alone?
Yes.
Teacher, I'll go with her.
Actually, I'll stay with Shiori-chan forever.
No thanks.
Oh my!
Die!
So they've made their move.
Then there's no reason for me to keep my distance from them anymore.
Okay, he's moving well.
My body feels so light.
I can clearly see her movements.
An attack from the side?
Senpai!
I'm all right.
I'm sorry.
I... accidentally...
No, that was good.
Don’t forget it.
Okay.
Yuka...
I saw it, you were impressive.
Well, thanks to senpai, I think I've become a bit stronger.
Please.
Thank you.
Yuka...
Hey, Yuka!
Now I will be just like Kakeru-kun, right?
You saw that?
Yes.
Yuka...
Umm... About earlier, I’m really sorry.
You were trying to comfort me, right?
Even so, what I did was...
I’m sorry.
Here you go.
Drink it.
Thank you very much.
About that...
I didn't speak well of Saeko-sensei earlier.
Sometimes you can't trust the people who are always beside you, right?
I was like that as well.
I realized it when I lost them.
People who had always been with me were no more.
And I felt as if a hole was dug into my life.
I started worrying,
because they protected me.
And having them protect me, you know...
Just drink it.
Okay, itadakimasu.
Thank you.
If you hadn't said that to me, I might have never realized it.
Takahisa-senpai...
That person you knew left you, right?
You must have felt very bitter.
But don’t worry, now you have one more person.
Am I right?
She's tiny, isn’t she?
Despite being this tiny, she's trying her best.
Saeko, if you hadn’t picked me up that time, I would never have reached here.
No, I would have been dead.
Thank you.
When the Red Night ends, let's go somewhere.
Me, you and Yukiko.
Let's have a blast.
Well then, let's go look for her.
Okay.
That girl, Yukiko... She was quiet all this time and now she wanders off?!
If she comes back, give me a call, okay?
Got it.
Well then, let's go.
Be careful.
What is wrong, Kakeru-kun?
Nothing, let’s go in.
Did something happen between you and Kakeru-kun?
He said you looked just like his sister.
So he may be feeling a bit awkward around you.
If there is a problem, tell me.
I will talk to Kakeru-kun.
I am placing it here then.
Okay.
What's wrong?
You're cleaning the place all of a sudden.
We're staying here for free.
So I should at least do the cleaning.
Yuka's back to her normal self again.
What’s wrong?
That thing.
Ah, it’s just a lizard.
Lizards frighten me.
It's all right.
They're not poisonous and they protect the house.
They won’t attack you.
However, if it bothers you, then I will catch it and leave it outside.
Kakeru-kun, you're so warm.
Yuka...
If only I could stay like this with you, that would be great.
I wonder if they found Yukiko-chan by now.
I don’t care.
Yuka...
I don't want to talk about that.
What is it?
It’s coming from the second floor.
I'll go check it out.
Don't leave me, I'll go too.
If something happens to you, then my power will...
You can’t, Yuka.
I don’t want you to use that power.
Why?
Do you hate me?
What are you saying?
It isn't like that.
You'll get tired if you use it, right?
I don’t want you to suffer anymore.
I will check the second floor.
Stay here, okay?
Okay, I understand.
If the Red Night ends,
things will return to normal.
then Yuka will certainly...
Is this it?
I guess it was just the wind.
I was waiting,
Vessel of the Eye of Aion.
Shiori-san?
What are you doing?
Who exactly are you?
I was sent by the Holy Office of the Index.
My true name is Ursula of the Epistle.
Why have you come?
Because you awakened the demon.
We weren't pulled into the Red Night today, right?
Yeah, you're right.
By the way, is it really okay for me to accompany you like this?
It’s all right.
Saeko’s money belongs to everyone.
Ah, you're mean!
But, since I waited so long for this, I will enjoy it.
Go on, eat it.
Eat to your heart’s content.
It's been a long time since I had something like yakiniku.
Hey Saeko, come on, let's go.
S-Saeko...
Next time:
Broken Bonds.
It’s said that the two would live together happily forever.