The Red Night suddenly appears.
Real, yet unreal... just like a parallel dark world in a different space and time.
The Black Knights attacked the boy and the girl, who had fallen down there, and called them “Fragments”,
What kind of breeze has swept them into this sinister place?
By the end of this nightmare, will there be an answer?
We weren't pulled into the Red Night today, right?
Yeah, that's true.
By the way, is it really okay for me to accompany you like this?
It's all right.
Saeko's money belongs to everyone.
Ah, you're mean!
But, since I waited so long for this, I will enjoy it.
Go on, eat it. Eat to your heart's content.
It's been a long time since I had something like yakiniku.
Hey, Saeko!
Come on, let's go!
Sae... ko...
Sa... Saeko...
Saeko...
SAEKO!!!
Saeko!
Saeko...
Hang in there...
Saeko!
Please...
Answer me... Saeko!
Saeko...
I see it.
Shiori-san, who are you?
Are you with the Black Knights?
I think that's enough.
I was testing you.
You have successfully...
In fact, you've surprisingly grown...
...into someone on whom we can put all our hopes.
Hopes?
I'll kill you!
That's right.
I want to sever your precious bonds!
Where the hell is Yukiko?
She's so troublesome.
Back then, Invidia tried to kill herself.
K-Kill me...
My power of destruction h-has disappeared?!
Why...?
The enemy wanted us dead under any circumstance.
Now, our teamwork is being tested.
We'll die for sure if the enemy succeeds in disrupting the team.
Fire?
Yukiko?
Yukiko!
Misuzu-senpai!
I've been looking for you. Where did you go?
Your clothes... Did something happen?
Die!
Your powers have awakened.
Please use this power and destroy the demon.
Destroy the demon?
You were the one who awakened it,
and you're the only one who can destroy it.
What are you talking about, Shiori-san?
What do you want me to defeat?
I was too careless.
This place has already been...
What was that?
They're here.
You are... Superbia!
Master of the Eye of Aion...
This isn't the Red Night,
so why are you here?
We travel between worlds by expending our life energy,
that's all.
Sensei was murdered?
Y-Yes.
Impossible! I don't believe it!
Unfortunately, it's true.
Why?
This isn't the Red Night, so why did Superbia...?
Senpai...
It's time to face the truth and solve the problem as soon as possible.
Yes, I think you are right.
Anger and sorrow have taken over Takahisa-senpai.
We have to quickly defeat Superbia and stop Takahisa.
Is the Kusakabe girl not here?
What?
If she isn't, then ask her to come out!
This is...
...Superbia!
She's at my house?
Such strong aura... There's no doubt.
Then who is Takahisa-senpai fighting against?
Yukiko, take care of Takahisa.
Kukuri and I will look for Superbia.
Can you do it?
Yes.
For the sake of our friends and for tomorrow.
Let's head back now.
I'll go on ahead.
Something's strange.
Why do I feel like something terrible has happened?
Kakeru!
Mizusu-senpai!
So, you've come.
Kashagiri Hiromitsu and Kannagiri Nagamitsu...
To think that you are now the wielder of those swords, Kusakabe style has fallen for sure.
Kakeru, she's a powerful opponent. Please assist me.
Okay.
Master of the Eye of Aion...
I have already arranged other opponents for you.
They are...?
The Black Knights that we defeated before?!
Kakeru!
Superbia...
No, Kusakabe Misao!
So you are Misao.
Why?
You were the Kusakabe clan's strongest sorceress.
Why did you become a Black Knight?
To oppose destruction.
Destruction?
And...
...to protect my Avaritia-sama!
Kusakabe Misao...
The legendary warrior.
You are worth my praise for being able to observe the difference in strength.
And also for changing your battle strategy accordingly.
Awaken by the consciousness of death, I will not go easy on you.
My life has forever been...
...for the sake of my friends and for tomorrow!
Why do you exist?
What a strong aura!
I'm unable to move.
Kakeru won't be able to help me.
Why isn't Kukuri here yet?!
And Yukiko hasn't returned yet either.
Takahisa-senpai!
Saeko...
Because of this ability, my parents abandoned me.
You took me in and took care of me till today.
I was a useless person.
I would have been a crazy person if Saeko wouldn't have been with me!
And to that Saeko, you...!!!
Takahisa-senpai!
Is that you, Yukiko?
Please stop.
That's not a Black Knight.
It's just an illusion.
It seems you're right.
But, I can no longer control myself.
I can't control...
...this power of destruction which my parents and I always feared of.
This fiery demon which has broken loose...
Yukiko...
It's all over.
Very soon, I will lose my own consciousness.
You must stop me.
For the sake of our friends and for tomorrow.
Stop it, Takahisa-senpai.
If you'd be the one to kill me,
I'd be satisfied!
The Red Night...
Controlling two magical spells at the same time?!
Yuka-san...
Shiori-chan...
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for Kakeru-kun.
He asked me to wait here for him.
At this moment, he is fighting the Black Knights.
Kakeru-kun is?!
You are not allowed to go.
Move aside!
Move aside, Shiori-chan!
If you dare to interfere with his growth,
then I'll have to insist that you rest here instead.
I want to protect Kakeru-kun.
I have to go and save Kakeru-kun!
He can protect himself now.
He will definitely defeat those dolls.
Please do not worry.
Really?
Yes.
Will he be all right?
Well, if that's the case, there's no need for me to go.
However, I cannot guarantee the others' safety.
It's fine as long as Kakeru-kun is okay.
Hey, Shiori-chan,
would you like to have tea?
I'll go and make some tea now.
It's useless!
I have already seen through all your attacks.
That's...
So that's how it is.
This is bad.
If I continue to waste my energy,
I won't be able to kill her.
Kakeru-kun and I grew up in the same orphanage.
Ever since then, Kakeru-kun has always been very gentle.
He was always by my side, protecting me.
And then the parents I have now, adopted me.
Soon after that, Kakeru-kun started living alone.
He even accompanied me to the same high school.
Kakeru-kun and I have always been together.
It has always been like this in the past, and so it will be in the future.
I love fairy tale endings.
“Since then, they lived together happily ever after.”
Misuzu-senpai...
Is that all you got?
Earlier, I was kind of looking forward to this.
But now, it seems that the Kusakabe era is coming to an end.
Just a moment will do.
If I can just find an opening...
I ask for your protection and for your help to defeat the enemy.
I call upon the God of Fire and the flaming chariots to send my enemies to hell!
I'm putting everything on this one strike!
Katentsuishou!
Ka-Kashagiri has...
Damn you!
The game ends here.
Senpai!
Misuzu-senpai!
Die!
My sword...
You brat, you drank the Kusakabe family's blood, didn't you?
That's all for tonight.
But, “for the sake of friends and for tomorrow”,
I have severed the bonds between you.
What?
Senpai...?
Misuzu-senpai!
The Holy Office of Index had sensed the presence of an evil power on top of the Aya Hill.
And so, they sent me.
What is “The Holy Office of Index”?
It was created to destroy or seal magic that threatens to destroy the world.
The world's largest magical organization.
Magical organization?
So, you're a magician?
Not only me.
There are others too.
By “others”, you don't mean...
...the Black Knights?!
They are not ordinary magicians,
they are apostles sent by the Holy Office of Index.
They fight to destroy evil.
Wait a minute...
You mean the Black Knights are apostles of justice?
How can that be?
Regarding Superbia, Misuzu-san must know more.
She's too strong for me...
I am completely incomparable to her...
It's useless...
I... have already...
Misuzu-senpai...
What happened, Yukiko?
I killed him.
I killed Takahisa-senpai.
I...
...killed him with my own hands.
Takahisa is dead?
But, “for the sake of friends and for tomorrow",
I have severed the bonds between you.
Next time
The Witch Awakens
Do you think that there's an answer at the end of the nightmare?