The Red Night suddenly appears.
Real, but not real... just like a dark parallel world in a different space and time.
The Black Knights attacked the boy and the girl, who had fallen down there, and called them “Fragments”.
What kind of breeze has swept them into this sinister place?
By the end of this nightmare, will there be an answer?
Persistent, aren't you?!
No way, he's from our school, isn't he?
Did he get into a fight? Unbelievable!
Just as I expected, time stood still in this world.
Isn't it nice for you guys to be so carefree...
Everyone, welcome to the “Modern Societies Study Club” hosted by me, Yukiko Hirohara.
Modern Societies Study is the investigation and research of various phenomena in our modern society.
In short, it's a modern version of archeological research.
I've heard that many times!
Yeah, finally the “Modern Societies Study Club” has new members.
Two girls and one boy.
It can't be...
Nee-san died seven years ago.
What I saw in the Red Night must have been an illusion.
Still, back then...
Kakeru-kun, are you all right?
It's not good to fret over something.
Besides, we are all here.
Yes, that's true.
I'm glad to meet so many allies.
Yukiko-chan, you're amazing, aren't you?
You've survived the Red Night all by yourself, right?
Yes.
So, do you have some kind of special power?
I'm merely a normal girl, you know.
However, when I'm angry, I'm pretty scary.
You're always cheerful, Yukiko-chan.
It's the only strong point that I have.
Seriously,
where and with whom did you fight to get injured like that?
Your attendance is dropping pretty fast, right?
You've been skipping classes lately, don't you want to graduate?
You're annoying!
Stop preaching, you're no more than an old hag who is still single.
Takahisa, I'm really glad that you'd never think of laying your hands on women.
Wait!
Wait right there, Takahisa!
Fragments...
Those Black Knights referred to us as "Fragments"...
Since you Fragments are about to disappear, I have no obligation to tell you.
What did he mean by “Fragments”?
Besides, how many “Fragments” are there?
Me!
I know one.
When the Red Night appeared the first time, someone called “The Ally of Justice” helped me.
Yukiko-kun, so you know her as well?
It's not a girl.
It's a boy.
How can I talk about it?
Things regarding that world and this ability...
Takahisa!
I won't let you run away.
She's so persistent.
All right, it's settled then.
The task for today is to search for that guy.
Since we have already decided, let us not waste any time.
Let's go!
Sorry for the intrusion.
Where are you hiding...?
Takahisa, where are you?!
Phew, that was close.
Ow ow ow...
What was so urgent that...? You're so terrible.
You're that “Ally of Justice"!
Glasses Girl!
It's you again.
Everyone, the search has ended.
It's him.
I'm really surprised.
There are so many people who can see the black moon...
You're Satsuki, right?
What is it?
Are you sure that you don't have any ability?
It's impressive that you've survived so far.
What?
Don't get angry. It was a compliment.
Want some fries?
No.
N-No, thanks...
I'm good.
I'll have some.
Is that so?
No one has any detailed knowledge about the Red Night?
Then, see you guys later.
Wait, Takahisa Tajima.
Aren't you going to join the Modern Societies Study Club?
Weak dogs join packs.
I have no interest in team work.
Did he just call us dogs?!
What if the Red Night comes again?
Then I'll think of something by myself.
Kakeru-kun...
Such an bad-mannered person...
No, though he may look like that, he's actually pretty kind.
That's right. Very kind...
Not horrible at all.
In fact, people may really envy you.
Kakeru-senpai, you won’t be able to succeed if you swing it around aimlessly!
Your impatience will confuse you even more.
What is it that you are fighting for?
That is...
So that I can protect Yuka.
Somehow, it sounds sad.
Those words alone are not enough to achieve what you want.
Your feelings are not transforming into power.
Does the sword that you are holding carry your resolution?
Resolution?
It's your resolution that will enlighten you.
However, your thoughts have not reached the stage of enlightenment yet.
It's the heart that requires training first, and not the body.
Transform your thoughts into power, and don't think about anything else.
Okay!
Transform thoughts into power...
I want power...
...in order to protect Yuka.
Yuka!
Kakeru-senpai?
Kakeru-kun, what's wrong?
Ah... No... I wonder what just happened.
I shouldn't be saying this,
but if it were a real battle,
you wouldn't have been able to protecting Yuka-san, you would've been dead.
I was afraid you'd say that...
I'm sorry, it was not intentional.
No,
you're right.
Kakeru-kun...
In order to test Kakeru's resolution, I intended to attack her.
His actions just now...
Hey Yuka...
Yes?
Right now, I'm embarrassingly weak.
But, I will definitely protect you.
Don't strain yourself.
I have no power either.
As long as you're by my side, I'm fine.
I'm doing it for the same reason.
“I want to protect Yuka”. I want to transform that thought into power.
Kakeru-kun...
Oh! Ciao! Buongiorno, Shiori!
Piacere. Come sta, Shiori?
Quanto costa?
Please don't speak such weird Italian.
To be in passionate, bilingual relationships with beautiful girls, I need to practice very hard.
Please burn.
Burn until you turn to ash.
Oh, capito!
Hey, Shiori-chan, isn't it “ladies first” in Europe?
I'll listen to whatever you say.
Please walk straight down this road, turn right and die there.
Si. I will gladly do that!
Go straight...
Turn right...
Carbonara!
Arrivederci.
Goodbye.
He's such an idiot!
If he gets any dumber, I don't know what to call him anymore.
Kusakabe-senpai!
Hi.
Yuka left a bit early.
Kakeru-kun, about yesterday's training...
Yes?
No, never mind.
Y-Yuka...
Ah, welcome, guys!
Right now, we're in the middle of one of the club's activities.
Club activities?
Right!
Why does Yuka-san have such big breasts, despite her small body?
Stop it, Yukiko-chan!
They are neither sagging, nor are they erect.
Without any push-up bra, this is a modern miracle!
How can she do that on sacred school ground?
Hey, Yukiko-chan, stop it now!
I said stop...
Here it comes!
The Red Night...
That is...
Takahisa-senpai is engaged in battle.
What?
Burn to ashes!
Takahisa-senpai is a mental ignition type, a Pyrokineticist.
A Black Knight...
Fragments, you won't be so lucky today.
Exactly who are you guys?!
I have nothing to say to the sinners who will eventually turn into dust.
“Nothing to say”, you say?
Yukiko-kun, please take care of them!
Okay!
Kanagiri Nagamitsu
Here I come!
This guy.... is using martial arts?
He's fast!
Kusakabe-senpai is being pushed back.
It has begun, right?
Yes, Avaritia-sama.
Those Fragments defeated Gula.
Please don't worry.
This time, Ira and Invidia are going.
And I, Superbia, am there as well.
Kakeru-kun!
I-I'm fine.
But Senpai...
Misuzu-senpai is in trouble.
If only I had power...
Just desiring power will not make you get it.
You're in trouble unless you bring forth your power.
The situation is somewhat like that.
I'll be right back!
Y-Yukiko-chan?
This speed...
Such an overwhelming fighting ability...
You're annoying!
Yukiko-kun!
Don't underestimate me!
What?!
Yukiko-chan?
It's just like she's a different person completely.
Noooo!!
Yukiko!
Ira...
Invidia.
I thought that Ira could handle all the Fragments alone, but...
You should all just die.
Hold it right there!
The Ally of Justice has come!
It's show time!
How dare you... do this to my face...!
I'll kill you!
The Red Night is about to end.
This is not the end.
Next time we'll finish the job...
We're safe!
What's wrong, Yuka?
Ka... Kakeru-kun...
Unbelievable! Those wounds were too deep...
I made a mess, didn't I?
Yukiko...
Yukiko-chan!
That's what happens when I take my glasses off.
A split personality?
Where did you learn that inhuman fighting ability and that killer instinct?
Ahh, well...
I don't want to talk about it though...
More importantly, are you hurt, Yukiko-chan?
It's healed!
Actually, I have the ability to regenerate.
I cannot die.
You can't die?
No.
It's creepy, isn't it?
It's alright.
I'm used to it, anyway.
In the past, everyone... about me...
I was born in a country called Doresvenia.
It was a land full of chaos and killings.
That's enough.
It's all right, Yukiko.
In all, four people have accepted me.
You guys, and....
Nah, it's not creepy at all.
In fact, people probably envy you.
Even if you get hurt, you'll go right back to being okay.
Back to the beautiful girl you are!
Yukiko-chan...
Thank you very much.
Yuka-san, Kakeru-senpai, Misuzu-senpai...
And...
Takahisa-senpai!
I'll be waiting for you at the club.
Next Episode:
For My Friends and For Tomorrow
At the end of the nightmare, will there be an answer?