I’m sorry.
T-Takahisa-senpai...
Takahisa-senpai...
The Black Knights are doing this in the name of justice?
Yes.
So you're saying that we're the bad guys?
That's ridiculous!
Fragments...
That’s right, you are fragments.
Fragments of the Demon Stone of the Void, which holds vast power.
Demon Stone of the Void?
I am a Fragment as well.
To be specific, fragments are embedded in our bodies.
There are seven Fragments.
You,
Me,
Yuka-san,
Yukiko-san,
Kukuri-san,
Takahisa-san,
and the witch that was captured.
Fragments?
Are they evil?
The fragments are not evil.
However, if the seven fragments come together,
then their power would become unimaginable.
In other words, it depends on the desires of the keeper...
So is this Lisette’s purpose?
In order to gather all seven fragments,
she dragged us into her world, the Red Night.
Yes.
Then, is it Lisette who is causing all of this?
Please help me.
That’s not her actual form.
When she was sealed, her magic and memories were separated, which caused her to take on that form.
Her actual name is Liselotte.
Liselotte...
She will fulfill her wish as soon as she manages to gather all seven fragments.
Her wish?
Pitfall into Hades.
The thing which you call "the Black Moon'' is in fact a door to Hades.
Liselotte’s purpose is to open that door leading to the darkness by using all seven Void stones.
What will happen if she succeeds?
The world will fall into the Abyss.
In other words, it will be destroyed.
Is that right?
Yes.
The world... will be destroyed...?
So that's why the Black Knights are doing their best to prevent it from happening,
to save the world...
I see. They sure are righteous.
However, only six fragments exist now.
Takahisa...
But Kakeru-san is still here.
Using the Eye of Aion, the door to the Abyss can still be opened.
The tea is ready.
There are also cookies, Kakeru-kun.
All right, help yourself.
Yuka...
Do you think we can win?
All of us...
Misuzu-senpai...
No, Kakeru-kun.
It’s “Kusakabe-senpai”.
What's wrong?
Ah, it’s nothing.
I'm sorry, I feel a little bit tired.
I guess I'll go rest.
Yuka, I'll take this cup of tea with me, okay?
All right.
Shiori-kun, let's continue to discuss this later.
Senpai...
Kakeru-kun, you didn't rest at all.
Aren't you tired?
Well... yeah...
How about we sleep together?
Like in the old days...
Idiot...!
What are you talking about?
What’s the problem? Why are you blushing?
You’re acting strange, Kakeru-kun.
The world will be destroyed.
I just can’t fathom it... I wonder if there’s something better to think about.
Kakeru-kun...
Yu-Yuka?!
Let’s sleep together.
Hey!
Sleep with her.
Perhaps then we can continue our story.
Eight hundred years ago, a sorceress achieved an immortal body.
People called her the Witch of Babylon.
They feared her, and stayed away from her.
That would be Liselotte...?
Eventually, she met a young king and fell in love with him.
The name of that young king was Verard.
At that time, his kingdom, Drasuvania, was caught up in a civil war.
It's better if this world is destroyed.
That’s right, we no longer need this world.
As long as I have you, it’s enough.
Kakeru-kun...
After that, Verard was killed by one of his most reliable men.
After learning about Verard’s death, Liselotte drowned herself in sorrow,
and swore to carry on her lover’s wish by accomplishing it herself.
Pitfall to Hades...
Since that time,
the Holy Organization of the Index has been fighting that witch
to prevent her from harming the world.
And then, sixty-four years ago,
some disciples of the Organization succeeded in sealing her away in another world.
On these grounds.
So that’s why the Red Night appears in this city.
However, since they sacrificed themselves to fight her,
the disciples of the Order...
...turned into terrible forms.
The Black Knights...
Those who were in the timeless world of Liselotte,
which you called "The Red Night", were in fact protecting the seal placed on the witch.
So that's what this is about.
Kakeru-kun...
The Black Knights believed that Verard might someday awaken inside you,
possess you and then make use of the Eye of Aion to support the witch.
That’s why they want to kill you to prevent it from happening.
Verard will take over my body...?
That’s where our beliefs differ.
The possessor of the Eye of Aion
holds the power to banish the witch forever,
far from just sealing her.
The reason why I haven't told you who I was and have been secretly observing you
was to decide for myself
whether or not you are trustworthy enough to decide the fate of the world.
So, what’s your answer?
You’re simple, but weak.
Their prediction could come true.
Verard could take control of your heart and your mind.
However, I decided not to believe it.
Actually, I myself was fairly pessimistic about this world.
I thought of it as a terrible wasteland.
That’s why, when I was given this mission,
I thought it would be fate if I were ever to fail.
However,
I slowly understood.
People thrive in this world, and life exists as a result.
Teacher, this idiot is sleeping in the class.
That’s why I decided to believe in you.
You, who belongs to this world, are familiar with its inhabitants and can embrace the future.
For the sake of my friends and for tomorrow.
Can you do it?
I want to.
I want to protect this world in any way possible.
But,
Shiori-san...
Until yesterday, I believed that as long as I tried hard enough...
As long as I had my friends, it would be all right.
But...
Now...
At this moment,
it's like we're falling apart.
Tachibana-senpai...
Yeah.
Oh right, I'm sorry.
I got everything wrong about that...
about that message.
I’m sorry.
Thank you.
Is that you, Kakeru?
Yes.
Where is Yuka?
She got tired after sunbathing, so she's sleeping.
I carried her to the living room.
Sit down.
Okay...
Until now, I always used to think about battles.
I wanted to become strong.
I aimed at becoming the strongest onmyoji.
That's why I didn't care about anyone and practiced alone.
Ever since I was a kid, I admired Misao Kusakabe, the legendary onmyoji.
I was foolish to think that I had a chance to win.
When I looked at myself, I thought I could defeat her.
It’s pitiable.
She made me feel this.
I can’t defeat her.
Senpai...
She's on a completely different level than me.
She accompanied many people, and learned many things from them,
while I tried to isolate myself,
trying to learn everything by myself,
just accumulating knowledge.
So what’s bad about that?
It was my pride that rendered me inexperienced,
because of which I couldn't move until I thought it through.
Theoretical knowledge, or the intuition of someone experienced...
Which one do you think is better?
Even before I made my move, Misao knew it all.
I can only do moves that are all from a book and can be read right through.
That's not true, you're just overthinking it.
Maybe you’re right...
It may be just as you said.
I’m just being arrogant.
I should be thanking you for helping me gain control over the Eye of Aion.
It wasn't theoretical knowledge; it was by using your sword and your body.
When you suddenly meet someone whom you’ve always admired, you tend to become nervous, right?
You can’t be your normal self.
You can’t be calm.
That’s why...
I’m sorry; I can’t put it in simple words.
But...
Thank you.
That’s right.
Thank you, Kakeru-kun.
Senpai...
Come closer.
Kakeru-kun...
Where is Kakeru-kun?
The toilet, I guess.
He’ll get back soon.
Just for a bit...
Just for a bit, please.
Misuzu-senpai...
I beg of you.
Okay.
He's late.
I will go look for him.
Kakeru-kun!
So you're awake?
Where did you go?
I was taking a stroll through the garden.
Why?
It’s all right then.
Kakeru-kun, come with me for a sec.
What's wrong?
Just come.
I understand now.
I liked Takahisa-senpai.
I loved him...
Hey, Yuka!
We're not allowed to go in there.
It’s all right.
Hug me.
Yuka...
Please...
Parallel worlds?
The magic used to seal away the witch was a forbidden magic,
The Rainbow of Contract.
It divides the magical power of the enemy in to seven worlds, thus weakening them.
So sixty-four years ago, using this technique, they were able to stop the pitfall?
Thus seven fragments were born and each of them fell into their respective parallel worlds.
So the seven fragments fell into their true worlds?
But now...
When the fragments were dragged into the Red Night,
they arrived at the same place.
Though I wonder why, when they returned from the Red Night,
they all came back to the same world.
This world?
I can smell her.
Let me make that smell disappear.
Yuka...
You said each fragment belonged to its own world,
then to whom does this world belong to?
As long as I have you, it’s enough.
All I need is you.
Yuka...
You feel the same, right?
As long as you have me, it’s enough, right?
You don't regret that you lost your sister, right?
Sister?
You shouldn’t be surprised.
Kukuri-san was just an illusion.
An illusion?
If this is one of the worlds to which a fragment holder actually belongs,
then by using the power of the fragment,
he or she can change the structure of the world.
That means...
Yuka-san created this illusion for Kakeru-san’s sake.
Kukuri-san, the true wielder of the fragment, died in her own world.
So you’re saying this is Yuka’s world?
It’s okay if you don’t fight anymore.
I will protect you.
Yuka...
Yukiko!
It can’t be.
I never thought you would come here alone.
I won’t forgive you.
I will never forgive you!
What are you going to do?
I will kill you!
Senpai!
Yukiko went to the Crystal Tower alone.
What?!
Let’s go.
I won’t let you go.
Yuka...!
As long as you're with me, you'll be fine,
because I will protect you.
Yuka...
I'll go on ahead.
We’ll be waiting.
Yuka!
Am I a bad person?
Was it because of me that such thing...
No weapon?!
Don't you dare harm my Kakeru-kun!
Kakeru-kun...
Yuka!
I reached this stage to save Yuka.
I treasure her.
That feeling won’t change.
However, there is something more important that I have to do first.
Everyone, here I come.
Senpai...
Takahisa-senpai...
Takahisa...
You’re not fit to be my opponent at all.
Yukiko, you could have just waited for us.
Misuzu-senpai!
Shiori-san!
Kakeru...
Superbia, the rest of the Fragments have arrived.
Let’s finish them.
Your wounds regenerate, right?
But that’s because of the power of your fragment.
Let me turn you back into a human.
Let me grant you your wish.
Die!
Yukiko!
A fragment of the Void...
She took it out?
Bastards!
Stay away!
Let me pluck your right eye out!
Avaritia-sama!
The fragment...
Yuka...
It can’t be!
I will save you.
Liselotte...
Next time:
The Choice Called "Destruction"
So there really was no answer at the end of this nightmare!