The Red Night suddenly appears.
Real, but not real... just like a dark parallel world in a different space and time.
The Black Knights attacked the boy and the girl, who had fallen down there, and called them “Fragments”.
What kind of breeze has swept them into this sinister place?
By the end of this nightmare, will there be an answer?
The black moon...
Why? How did it...?
What's the meaning of this?
I don't know. However, I'm sure that this is not a good sign.
The next time you find yourselves in the Red Night, let's meet at the school.
Okay.
Besides, the kid I was planning on introducing to you doesn't feel up to it.
So you mean she didn't want to meet us?
I thought if we all gathered, then we could feel a bit safer.
People have their own reasons.
Give it some time.
Okay, I understand.
Well, see you.
Kusakabe-senpai...
What is it, Satsuki-kun?
There's something I would like to talk to you about.
I see.
Meet me in my classroom during lunch break.
Okay.
Kakeru-kun, what is it you want to talk about?
It's nothing!
Well, come on, the class has begun.
Kakeru-kun...
"The one who awakened the demon...
...is you."
Demon...
Like this?
Then you're...
As I expected, it's me...
So that means I was the cause of Yuka and the others getting pulled into the Red Night?
Because of me...
Right, next question, Satsuki-kun?
Satsuki-kun?
Kakeru-kun...
I-I'm sorry.
Pay attention in class.
I'm sorry.
Kakeru-kun... are you feeling sleepy?
Looks like you did something last night. Was it something perverted?
Kaori-san, hitting me with text books will make you repeat a class, did you know that?
Teacher, please throw out this loudmouthed trash.
It's wrong to treat people like that...
Okay, okay, that's enough! Joke about it during break time, okay?
Power?
Yeah. I want to awaken it.
It seems like there is some kind of power sleeping inside me.
What can I do?
I want you to teach me to fight.
If the power slumbering inside me is to be used for fighting,
it might awaken when I'm in a duel.
No, it has to!
It would be nice if it did.
I understand how you feel about protecting Minase Yuka.
Yet, haste may lead you to failure.
As you know, nothing can be achieved in one night.
I understand that.
However, I still want to do it.
No, I must do it!
It's all my fault.
Please, Kusakabe-sempai!
Please teach me the way of the sword.
I refuse.
Senpai! Please wait!
Hey hey, let's eat at that place.
Let's go.
Found you, Yuka-san.
Y-Yukiko-chan...
Ah, looks delicious!
Can I have a bite?
Avocado and shrimp!
It's perfect!
Thanks for the meal.
You said one bite...
Ah, I'm sorry! It was so delicious, I ate it all!
Thank you.
Eh? Why are you thanking me?
Aren't you supposed to be angry that I ate it all?
Aargh! Did you poison it?
It's nothing like that.
I feel better after seeing you smile.
So, thank you.
Ah, is that so?
Then, I will smile even more.
It's no good.
There is no point in reading these works of fiction.
Is that person an acquaintance of yours?
Eh... Ah... Yeah...
Don't tell me...
...you like him?
It's nothing like that!
What are you talking about? It's not true!
Nothing like that?
I'm sorry...
That person... I can't say much, but...
He's the same as me.
He's in pain too.
Yukiko-chan...
A bit unexpected, but your breasts are quite big, aren't they?
This feels great!
W-Wait, Yukiko-chan!
So nice...
I saw that.
What?
She's a cute and bright girl, isn't she?
If you are interested in her, then...
It's not that.
You should say what's on your mind.
Keeping quiet and bottling it all up isn't good for your health, you know...
Since you are still young...
Ok! Shiroi-chan,
is this good enough?
It seems there is some problem with your head.
It's a collection, you know.
Explain why chapter 1 is next to chapter 5.
Ah, you're right.
The numbers are not meant for decoration,
so please fix it.
What are you guys doing?
Shiori-chan became a librarian.
Though he said that he would help, he is nothing more than a nuisance.
Is that so?
Right.
Okay! It's perfect!
As I thought, the collection has to be moved down one level after all.
Please do it quickly.
Right...
Tadashi, do your best!
Kakeru-kun...
Senpai...
So she is Kusakabe Misuzu.
My family was one of the Onmyouji houses that have been protecting this country and its people for generations.
So eventually, I felt that I had to become an Onmyouji.
And as such, I wanted to become a strong one.
It's the hand seal.
A hand seal?
I have all of the five swords of the Kusakabe house which have been passed down to me.
Their power is evil by nature,
and so, I always seal them off, and only call them out when needed.
Kogarasu Maru Amakuni,
Kashagiri Hiromitsu,
Kanagiri Nagamitsu,
Tachibana Dosetsu Raikiri,
And the last, Dojigiri Yasutsuna.
In order to select the worthy ones to get the treasured swords, in Kusakabe, the Onmyouji house of Star,
people of the same bloodline duel with each other using these swords.
And the one who wins takes the swords.
So the presence of all the five swords means that...
You must've defeated everyone, right?
Amazing!
Originally, in order to avoid the accumulation of all the powers in one place,
it was intended that each descendant should be allowed to hold only one of these.
Still, this was the result of a legitimate match; hence there was no way to deny it.
So I had no choice but to leave the village.
Village?
So this house is...
I heard that it was my mother's.
Since the main house members were out for revenge,
I fled from my relatives, and since then I've been living here.
Out for revenge, you say?
But why? You acquired them after a legitimate match, didn't you?
The Kusakabe family was famous,
so they wanted to keep up the reputation.
Having all the precious swords taken by a junior, moreover a woman,
the Elders didn't like that at all.
Besides, in the last match I...
I'm being self-indulgent.
Alright, let's get started.
Okay!
Heavier than you expected, isn't it?
Yes.
Now you try it.
Okay!
Once more.
Is that so?
You and Satsuki grew up together in the same orphanage?
Yes.
Thank goodness.
I don't see the black moon.
Yeah.
How's Kakeru-kun doing?
He's not talented in the way of the sword...
However, it's better than doing nothing.
Kakeru-kun's power will awaken, right?
If it's his destiny...
That's all I can say.
The final match...
You suddenly stopped while you were talking earlier.
Did something happen?
You stopped, because you didn't want to tell, right?
I'm sorry.
I stabbed my father.
With the last sword, Dojigiri Yasutsuna,
I stabbed my father, the head of the Kusakabe family.
Although it was an official match, his students could not forgive my actions.
Senpai...
I never got along well with my father.
He disapproved of my admiration towards a certain person.
A certain person?
Misao Kusakabe, a female Onmyouji, who was said to be the strongest.
However, she committed a prohibited action, so she was expelled from the village.
What did she do?
I heard that she mastered a foreign technique.
Foreign technique?
By combining the secrets of western sorcery,
she broke the Kusakabe tradition.
Techniques that differ from the ideals of the Kusakabe family are considered “foreign techniques”.
By the way,
this is one of the “foreign techniques”.
How is Misao-san doing now?
That incident took place about seventy years ago.
That means she's already...
No.
Perhaps...
This may be bad, but...
...on the other side?
By “the other side”, you mean the Red Night?
Kakeru-kun...
Did you do it?
Keep practicing until you can do it.
Go back.
There is no point in doing things this way.
Please teach me through an actual battle.
I can't. It's still too early for you.
Even though it's early, please teach me.
Kakeru-kun...
There's no time left. While practicing this way, if it… again…
Please go back.
Kusakabe-senpai, I am...
Have they come?
The Eye Master will likely not awaken.
Your first priority is taking care of the Fragments.
Got it.
I will go too.
Again, I will have you fall asleep soon.
Another seventy years, no, this time maybe a hundred years, oh captured witch.
No, let me out, please.
It's useless...
...since you're immortal.
Damn you!
I did it.
Alright, one more!
Don't get too full of yourself after slaying just one piece of trash.
Kakeru-kun...
Black Knights!
Aren't you looking nice over there?
Actually, this one here hasn't awakened yet, right?
Protecting both of them that way may slow you down.
Wanna die fast?
I don't intend to die.
You three are more hopeless and pathetic than us, who have abandoned our flesh.
Flesh?
So you bastards used to be human?
What if we were?
How did you end up like that?
You are not worthy of an explanation.
Run!
Senpai, but...
Don't even think about fighting them.
If you want to protect Minase, run now.
Go!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
I won't let you run away.
Stay alive, Kakeru, Yuka...
Kakeru-kun...
Don't look back, just run.
Hiding, are you?
Kakeru-kun...
Okay, he's gone.
Kakeru-kun!
Damn!
No!
I'll divert his attention.
Run when you get the chance.
Don't do it!
Kakeru-kun, you'll get yourself killed!
Now I'll smash you.
No matter how many, it will be the same!
Vanish, Fragment!
Thanks for your help.
Gura.... has fallen.
It's probably the work of that Onmyouji.
Bastard!
Kukuri-neesan...
Yuka?
Kakeru-kun...
I see. So we have returned.
Thank goodness!
I'm sorry.
So you're awake.
Kusakabe-senpai...
I'm sorry that I made you worry.
I'm glad you're safe.
Satsuki-kun, Yuka-kun...
Let me introduce you. This is our new ally.
Next Time: Disguised Smile.
Is there an answer at the end of the nightmare?