[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 02
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.24,0:00:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一刻的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.85,0:00:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一瞬的风景
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.72,0:00:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猩红的铁马  点燃了胸中仅存的激情

Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.62,0:01:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}对于一再向GGP发动恐怖攻击的非法组织“BMA”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.06,0:01:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}当局正在研讨能对他们适用的反恐法...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.06,0:02:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖分子闹得越欢  越是中了GGP的下怀啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.83,0:02:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}...向全国发布了通缉令
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.01,0:02:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}关于反恐法在国内的实施...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.06,0:02:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP也差不多要开始动真格了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.00,0:02:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  内阁和警视总厅为了维持治安
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.23,0:02:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下也不得不同意引进警用RideBack了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.53,0:02:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么没底气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.68,0:02:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明你妹妹不顾家人反对  整天在开那RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.31,0:02:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底像的谁呢  她的那种倔强性格
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.80,0:02:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.06,0:02:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.60,0:02:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙之介  珠代就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.80,0:02:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的灵魂都颤抖了!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.94,0:02:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是天才尾形琳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.95,0:02:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论干什么都是那么完美
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.77,0:02:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平衡感之类的肯定远超常人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.80,0:02:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一言蔽之!  你在基因上肯定就已经高人一等了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.12,0:03:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然间“咻”地一声
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.17,0:03:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好似一匹天马  在眼前飞舞而过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.78,0:03:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心也被“唰”的一声射穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.64,0:03:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞得有那么高吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.45,0:03:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.51,0:03:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是有如抗拒物理法则一般  奇迹的一跃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.73,0:03:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太夸张了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.20,0:03:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是手忙脚乱之下无意间跳起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.64,0:03:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里哪里  您太谦虚了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.54,0:03:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是只有琳姊才能完成的一跃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.69,0:03:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也好想“飞”一次看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.16,0:03:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦好啦  注意你的蛋黄酱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.61,0:03:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  救了琳的那位白马王子是?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.38,0:03:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是社团顾问来着...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.42,0:03:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位呀  长得可不一般了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.86,0:03:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给人的感觉...好像空手就能杀死熊一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.41,0:03:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算啥王子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.49,0:03:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  你在干什么呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.30,0:03:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天给你添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.35,0:03:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛮可爱的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.23,0:03:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  你就是那个想入部的新生?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.86,0:03:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  是在说我吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.90,0:03:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄错人啦  是坐在里边的那个女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.47,0:03:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是尾形琳小姐...对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.38,0:04:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天兵荒马乱的  真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.31,0:04:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是机械工学专业二年级的菱田
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.39,0:04:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是同系三年级的河合
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.64,0:04:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.83,0:04:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客套话少说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.67,0:04:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把入部申请书带来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.60,0:04:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是参观也好  欢迎你再来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.08,0:04:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部室一般随时都有人在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.07,0:04:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说两位学长  在那之前是不是还有什么话没说?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.79,0:04:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.72,0:04:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让琳乘上会失控的危险车种不说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.89,0:04:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要让她加入你们部?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.00,0:04:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  关于这个问题...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.99,0:04:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是就是  要不是琳姊肯定受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.65,0:04:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.75,0:04:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么下次再见
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.04,0:04:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.17,0:04:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.78,0:04:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像缠上你了呢

Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.88,0:04:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(318,263)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)}來吧珠代!? S.L.F
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.88,0:04:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(318,285)}{\fn華康中黑體\fs20\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)}～Spread Legs Form

Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.26,0:04:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}今日凌晨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.37,0:05:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}GGP佐世保基地遭自称BMA的武装集团袭击
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.61,0:05:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}根据目击情报
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.19,0:05:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}恐怖分子使用了一种名为RideBack的武器
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.81,0:05:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.76,0:05:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很在意吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.84,0:05:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天引起那场骚动的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.34,0:05:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.95,0:05:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新手乘上Fuego能做出那种跳跃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.48,0:05:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不可能是什么偶然
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.85,0:05:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么可能不感兴趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.88,0:05:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.82,0:05:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形琳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.50,0:05:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经的天才舞者  故人尾形游纪之女
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.86,0:05:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3岁就开始学习芭蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.63,0:05:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在各种大赛上留下优异成绩  芭蕾界的宠儿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.86,0:05:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然啦  对于冈仓先生这样的文艺盲
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.33,0:05:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形琳这个名字估计是毫无印象吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.90,0:05:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(350,50)\fr-12\an8\fs18\bord0\shad0\1c&H000000&}谁敢擅自偷喝我就杀了他!!  珠代
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.19,0:06:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是昨天那台...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.67,0:06:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RB-Z
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.68,0:06:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那台是我的专用机
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.74,0:06:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego还在修理
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.94,0:06:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道你一定会来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.27,0:06:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.42,0:06:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想乘吧  RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.27,0:06:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  我只是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.94,0:06:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要逃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.86,0:06:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.41,0:06:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你乘一下也行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.80,0:06:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我用RideBack一决高下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.27,0:06:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让你一点的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.17,0:06:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能赢我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.96,0:06:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以让你随时随地、自由地驱使RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.75,0:06:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要是输了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.49,0:06:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就来当我的妹抖
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.39,0:06:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RB-Z  坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.49,0:06:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受吗  天才芭蕾少女小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.91,0:06:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我替你把Fuego准备好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.39,0:06:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间定在下个星期六
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.52,0:06:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上午10点这里见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.64,0:07:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不来的话就算你输
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.49,0:07:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊...等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.58,0:07:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹  妹抖?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.72,0:07:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么乱七八糟的  她从哪个时代来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.09,0:07:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说会让我一点...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.25,0:07:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题重点不在这里啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.18,0:07:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说她是RideBack部部长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.72,0:07:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈珠代
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.01,0:07:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文学部法国文学专业三年级  目前无男友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.54,0:07:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从哪调查来的啊  那些情报
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.87,0:07:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  那位部长为什么要向琳这个外行下战书啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.21,0:07:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.28,0:07:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定她也看到了  那一跃!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.27,0:07:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让部长都感到嫉妒  真不愧是琳姊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.96,0:07:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会去应援的  请加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.53,0:07:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没决定接受呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.88,0:07:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵  真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.62,0:07:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.61,0:07:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的!  琳姊一定会赢的!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.69,0:08:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  嗯  不用你说也知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.49,0:08:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有好好上学啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.66,0:08:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正在社团活动
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.41,0:08:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又在信口开河了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.25,0:08:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了  我挂了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.06,0:08:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  等一下  坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.76,0:08:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对RideBack很了解吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.16,0:08:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  RideBack?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.64,0:08:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小意思啦  尽管问吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.39,0:08:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这是吹的什么风啊  老姊会来问Ride
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.55,0:08:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  是我朋友有点兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.74,0:08:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  去年全国大赛冠军
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.62,0:08:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈珠代是在老姊你那个大学吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.55,0:08:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是方便的话  能不能帮我要个签名啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.96,0:08:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都教你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.77,0:08:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是...Spread Legs Form
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.02,0:09:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要转为疾驰模式的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.05,0:09:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边轻按第二控制杆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.38,0:09:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,默认设定情况下  同时用右后脚跟踩下踏板
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.54,0:09:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投币洗衣房空出来了吗?  琳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.70,0:09:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.76,0:09:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.06,0:09:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  琳啊...星期六...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.40,0:09:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不去呢  那什么比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.81,0:09:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要自己安排课程表
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.57,0:09:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周末总还有事要忙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.86,0:09:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经跃跃欲试了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.82,0:09:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...会那么心跳不已呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.17,0:10:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的会来吗  那女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.67,0:10:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊一定会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.41,0:10:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹对吧  好有干劲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.82,0:10:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是“尾形琳守护会”的代表嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.00,0:10:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过亲自驾驶也是很有趣的哦 RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.66,0:10:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你愿意的话  比赛结束之后试乘一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.37,0:10:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田  你那边怎么样了?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.60,0:10:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只等主角大驾光临了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.47,0:10:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的会来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.50,0:10:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设置
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.95,0:10:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5号  核查完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.18,0:10:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我继续去设置6、7号了  麻烦你核查了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.96,0:10:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.30,0:11:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.15,0:11:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  这边这边
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.68,0:11:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田  把我的骑手服借给她
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.70,0:11:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐意效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.35,0:11:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次彻底核查过了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.62,0:11:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要是万一发生意外的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.32,0:11:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得按下那个EW手环上的紧急停止键
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.49,0:11:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.48,0:11:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规则很简单
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.26,0:11:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对决采用的是大学校内的车行道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.56,0:11:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里到山顶的蓄水塔的往返赛道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.46,0:11:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你一圈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.90,0:11:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你完成三圈之前要是我没跑完四圈就算我输
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.70,0:11:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让你熟悉赛道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.10,0:11:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先热身两圈  跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.03,0:11:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的话完了  没什么异议吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.17,0:11:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.53,0:11:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就出发
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.70,0:12:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正式比赛从第三圈才开始  别着急
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.66,0:12:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊加油!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.16,0:12:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.98,0:12:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FIGHT!  琳姊!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.88,0:12:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊不由分说就下战书确实很不讲理
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.50,0:12:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过接下这挑战的小琳也很豪迈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.75,0:12:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速度好快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.54,0:12:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊  不是先热一下身吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.77,0:12:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在热身呢  配合着后面那位的步调
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快啊  已经来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.56,0:13:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害  真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.41,0:13:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然跟得上那个片冈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.16,0:13:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有一套啊  那个新人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.19,0:13:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天这真的是她第二次骑RideBack吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.49,0:13:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20}GOGO!  Let's go! Let's go!  Ogata!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.21,0:13:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有怯场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.76,0:13:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果显而易见  可你还是会来的原因——
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.04,0:13:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上有一种人  只要受到挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.86,0:13:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算明知会输  也一定会接下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.03,0:13:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是这种人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.19,0:13:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形琳 你也是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.89,0:13:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我都是同类
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.76,0:13:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受我的挑战就是最好的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.45,0:13:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你大概猜错了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.76,0:13:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说...想看个清楚吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.68,0:13:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全日本冠军究竟有多少实力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.52,0:14:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.72,0:14:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有那时的感觉...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.90,0:14:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.96,0:14:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想说我不及你对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.14,0:14:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  我再让你一圈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.35,0:14:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换  比赛现在就开始
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.17,0:14:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.06,0:14:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.93,0:14:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等一下  珠代学姊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.93,0:14:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳还没熟悉赛道呢  再说...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.72,0:14:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河合  这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.33,0:14:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  是我忘说了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.89,0:14:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里正在搬运工程器材
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.29,0:14:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开放通行大概还需要5分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.40,0:14:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之请先从八号楼那边绕一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.37,0:14:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.75,0:14:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田  刚才那个不算
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.66,0:14:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是从部室门口正式开始
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.78,0:14:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.75,0:14:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问  驾驶RideBack有多复杂呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.09,0:14:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常驾驶的话  很简单哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.85,0:14:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本身就有附带自动保持平衡的自动模式
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.59,0:14:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小琳她们用的是手动模式
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.71,0:15:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是擅长运动的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.51,0:15:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始光是站着也很吃力了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.20,0:15:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fsp1}那么说  那个果然是奇迹之grand je{\fsp-4}t{\fsp1}e啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.84,0:15:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跨栏鸡腿?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.21,0:15:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芭蕾术语中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.47,0:15:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大跳的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.01,0:15:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿过这种地方真的不会有问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.68,0:15:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事  只管横冲直撞就是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.94,0:15:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“不走寻常路”才是RideBack的妙趣所在
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.61,0:15:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部长  你们在哪儿穿越呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.91,0:15:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自治会又要来投诉了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.19,0:15:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想投诉就来吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.84,0:15:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.47,0:15:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.37,0:15:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没看到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.80,0:15:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着哦  就快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.64,0:15:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.73,0:15:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.82,0:15:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备~
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.93,0:15:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,START!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.16,0:15:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊  FIGHT!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.70,0:16:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RideBack好像有点帅呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.77,0:16:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔  你也开窍了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.41,0:16:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开窍了~
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.07,0:16:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那是琳吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.50,0:16:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子姊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.72,0:16:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  现在赛局如何了?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.28,0:16:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其乐融融并肩跑的时间也就到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.64,0:16:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姊突然加速了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.56,0:16:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个形态我在网上见过
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.18,0:16:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.04,0:16:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强的加速
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.53,0:16:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连小琳也转为S.L.F.了?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.85,0:16:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.15,0:16:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让RideBack的双脚前后展开
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.78,0:16:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以此降低重心的疾驰模式
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.09,0:16:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然空气阻力会相应变小
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.10,0:16:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过弯时的软件操作会更复杂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.80,0:17:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田  你在看赛道情况吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.48,0:17:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.22,0:17:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个新人  好像把差距渐渐缩小了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.75,0:17:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈  你是故意让她追上的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.22,0:17:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦  别妨碍比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.86,0:17:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按常理通常驾驶都忙不过来的新人  居然跟得上我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.67,0:17:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.04,0:17:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么试试这招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.09,0:17:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不出我所料
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.64,0:17:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了追上我  毫不犹豫地用上了直冲池塘的加速
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.56,0:17:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩在绵羊的表皮下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.22,0:18:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隐藏着能撕碎一切的利牙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.41,0:18:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田  Fuego掉进池塘里了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.83,0:18:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去帮忙把它拖上来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.07,0:18:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这边来 Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.25,0:18:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经通过蓄水塔了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.03,0:18:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事根本无所谓  琳怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.72,0:18:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那接下来的事就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.24,0:18:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  还是我去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.02,0:18:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又动起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.23,0:18:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  又停下了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.02,0:18:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.57,0:18:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.53,0:19:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳好像就在你前面不远处  能看到她吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.71,0:19:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没放弃吗  我欣赏你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.13,0:19:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛继续
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.33,0:19:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又动了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.39,0:19:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.41,0:19:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.09,0:19:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差距越来越小
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.94,0:19:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego原来能跑这么快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.59,0:19:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  紧紧咬住我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.46,0:19:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并排了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.16,0:19:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FIGHT!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.42,0:19:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊  琳!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.97,0:19:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呆子  这个速度撞上去又会...!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.93,0:20:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然有此等骑手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.76,0:20:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,检查下来并无大碍
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.05,0:20:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是轻度脑震荡而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.20,0:20:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依片冈的性格  没分出胜负才是大问题
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.98,0:20:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田  报名还没截止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.99,0:20:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  你醒着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.82,0:21:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参赛报名我已经替你报了呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.70,0:21:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我  是她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.68,0:21:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在正式比赛再比一次  尾形琳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.00,0:21:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天开始我会严格训练你  做好心理准备吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.62,0:21:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.26,0:21:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说凉里妹妹也要加入RideBack部
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.22,0:21:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是看到琳的骑姿之后  自己也想骑骑看了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.05,0:21:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.29,0:21:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的这样就好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.03,0:21:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是挺好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.93,0:21:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还蛮适合你的

Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.51,0:23:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新手小琳一来就让她参加全国大赛?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.11,0:23:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  真的吗  真的是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.19,0:23:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过话说玩RideBack的人本来就少
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.42,0:23:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要报名谁都能参加
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.57,0:23:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是超冷门竞技  冷门运动万岁!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.32,0:23:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那有什么好高兴的啊!


Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.92,0:23:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,245)\fs23\b1\bord0\shad1\1c&HFFFFFF&\4c&H6A6A6A&\4a&H3F&}{\fad(0,120)}于是 信号旗挥下


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.77,0:00:29.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.77,0:00:29.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.77,0:00:29.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.77,0:00:29.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.01,0:02:24.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.02,0:02:27.02,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.03,0:02:30.03,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.69,0:22:00.05,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.41,0:22:07.78,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.03,0:22:15.40,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.65,0:22:23.29,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.34,0:22:28.63,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.04,0:22:32.38,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.92,0:22:36.43,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.75,0:22:40.65,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.44,0:22:45.89,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.96,0:22:49.69,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.78,0:22:53.64,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.67,0:22:57.41,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.47,0:23:01.24,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.33,0:23:05.67,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.56,0:23:09.35,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.35,0:23:13.49,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:55.69,0:22:00.05,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:02.41,0:22:07.78,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:11.03,0:22:15.40,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:17.65,0:22:23.29,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:25.34,0:22:28.63,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:29.04,0:22:32.38,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:32.92,0:22:36.43,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.75,0:22:40.65,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:41.44,0:22:45.89,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:45.96,0:22:49.69,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.78,0:22:53.64,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:53.67,0:22:57.41,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.47,0:23:01.24,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:01.33,0:23:05.67,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:06.56,0:23:09.35,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.35,0:23:13.49,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.69,0:22:00.05,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.41,0:22:07.78,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.03,0:22:15.40,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.65,0:22:23.29,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.34,0:22:28.63,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.04,0:22:32.38,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.92,0:22:36.43,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.75,0:22:40.65,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.44,0:22:45.89,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.96,0:22:49.69,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.78,0:22:53.64,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.67,0:22:57.41,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.47,0:23:01.24,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.33,0:23:05.67,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.56,0:23:09.35,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.35,0:23:13.49,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:55.69,0:22:00.05,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:02.41,0:22:07.78,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:11.03,0:22:15.40,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:17.65,0:22:23.29,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:25.34,0:22:28.63,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:29.04,0:22:32.38,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:32.92,0:22:36.43,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.75,0:22:40.65,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:41.44,0:22:45.89,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:45.96,0:22:49.69,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.78,0:22:53.64,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:53.67,0:22:57.41,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.47,0:23:01.24,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:01.33,0:23:05.67,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:06.56,0:23:09.35,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.35,0:23:13.49,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.71,0:00:29.46,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:32.86,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.88,0:00:36.39,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.48,0:00:39.81,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.18,0:00:43.35,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.40,0:00:47.04,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.32,0:00:50.51,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.59,0:00:54.11,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.76,0:01:11.07,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.12,0:01:14.86,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.90,0:01:18.54,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.56,0:01:20.01,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.05,0:01:23.42,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.44,0:01:27.09,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.09,0:01:29.29,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.79,0:01:36.56,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this




Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.76,0:00:31.51,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.14,0:00:34.91,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.93,0:00:38.44,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.53,0:00:41.86,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.23,0:00:45.40,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.45,0:00:49.09,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.37,0:00:52.56,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.64,0:00:56.16,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:13.12,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.17,0:01:16.91,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.95,0:01:20.59,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.61,0:01:22.06,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.10,0:01:25.47,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.49,0:01:29.14,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.14,0:01:31.34,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.84,0:01:38.61,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this

