[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 01
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.05,0:00:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一段旋律
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.81,0:00:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩就是尾形游纪的女儿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.76,0:00:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名人之后啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.17,0:00:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未来的首席舞者吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.37,0:00:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说这是她首次领衔主演
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.26,0:01:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.52,0:01:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界在不断变化
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.48,0:01:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像舞台上的场景切换一般
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.85,0:01:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2025年
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.06,0:01:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自称“世界统治构想”的反联合国集团
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.06,0:01:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(280,325)\fs16\bord2\shad0\fsp2\fscy95}GGP
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.57,0:01:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一夜之间成为了全球霸主
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.15,0:01:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级大国与反联合国集团
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.08,0:01:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军事力量上的天壤之差
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.37,0:01:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP通过投入“新战力” 一举扭转
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.32,0:01:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进而取得了历史性胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.34,0:01:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而 英雄们从未抛头露面
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.88,0:01:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一句空洞的“历史性胜利”隐蔽下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.73,0:01:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悄悄退下了历史舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.13,0:01:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随之到来的是 世界秩序的新构想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.90,0:02:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭来无限反感的军事统治
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.27,0:02:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连锁反应式的 规模不断扩大的报复行为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.90,0:02:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不到一丝希望的灰色天空
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.49,0:02:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,革命、新生的秩序
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.27,0:02:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管外边的世界如此动荡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.24,0:02:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的生活依然一成不变
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.74,0:02:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯唯诺诺地依顺着母亲的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.06,0:02:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走上芭蕾之路 在舞台上挥洒生命
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.06,0:02:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.35,0:02:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这光照 这感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.18,0:02:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯有站在舞台之上时 我才能感受到自己的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.75,0:03:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无情的闭幕 来得如此突然
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.45,0:03:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的世界 就此发生改变

Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.35,0:05:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二三 跳!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.96,0:05:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好壮观
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.17,0:05:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落“樱”缤纷啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.13,0:05:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是不是有点兴奋过头了?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.15,0:05:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.60,0:05:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天开始就是全新的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.78,0:05:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且宿舍还是同室 简直就是奇迹呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.51,0:05:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不兴奋才怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.75,0:05:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒没错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.11,0:05:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到车站只要徒步8分钟哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.93,0:05:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便利店又近哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.34,0:05:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卫浴分开 全新装修
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.63,0:05:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且房间大小足足有10帖榻榻米耶~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.63,0:05:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\move(-12,12,12,12,0,200)\fs16\bord0\4c&H073546&\i1}{\fad(400,200)}译注: 约15平方米
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.38,0:05:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是那么说 床和桌子可是各有两张呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.26,0:05:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对哦 这么一说好像是挺小的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.78,0:05:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且连空调都没 夏天叫人怎么过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.54,0:06:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心好了 我们的前任不都是这么过来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.85,0:06:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总会有办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.25,0:06:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿如此啦...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.87,0:06:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好美

Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.08,0:06:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(208,235)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)}猩紅鐵馬

Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.30,0:06:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本国的混乱局面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.42,0:06:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在各位同学的父辈们的不懈努力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.08,0:06:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及GGP的复兴支援下 才得以收拾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.31,0:06:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望各位同学在本校刻苦学习
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.80,0:06:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等各位走上社会时 我国能更为繁荣昌盛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.43,0:06:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.31,0:06:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盛开的樱花美极了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.71,0:06:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边已经谢了大半了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.62,0:07:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您那边近况如何?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.93,0:07:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.03,0:07:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面乐不思蜀呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.43,0:07:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没回来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.46,0:07:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是青春期的男孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.42,0:07:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里只有老人和狗 也难怪他会觉得沉闷
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.47,0:07:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.60,0:07:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这套房子 两人住实在太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.06,0:07:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午餐还能在外面解决 晚饭就只有我和佩伦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.50,0:07:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实很寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.29,0:07:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司高中毕业后的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.70,0:07:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也差不多到了该认真考虑的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.19,0:07:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳你自己呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.50,0:07:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得后悔吗? 就那么放弃了芭蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.06,0:07:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会 那是我自己下的决定
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.71,0:07:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶奶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.80,0:07:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真对不起 老是旧事重提
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.66,0:07:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听到你的声音 我就很高兴了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.79,0:08:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后不管再忙 也要给家里打电话哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.06,0:08:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然啦 奶奶再见 我先挂了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.87,0:08:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.98,0:08:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳 我洗好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.62,0:08:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.07,0:08:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.80,0:08:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 只是入学仪式回来有点累 发了会呆
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.91,0:08:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来冲个澡 精神一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.03,0:08:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.63,0:08:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 祥子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.04,0:08:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为室友 今后还请多多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.73,0:08:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此彼此 今后请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.85,0:08:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么现在才来这套呀 琳也真怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.52,0:08:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22\shad1\fad(0,200)}...航母驶入佐世保港
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.26,0:08:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22\shad1\fad(0,200)}“GGP世界统治权受联合国承认日”
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.21,0:08:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22\shad1\fad(0,200)}庆祝这一革命纪念日的游行由于一部分...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.39,0:08:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问...您是尾形琳小姐吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.88,0:08:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 果然没认错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.28,0:09:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是美术专业一年级的内田凉里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.10,0:09:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呀 老远看到就猜会不会是您了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.50,0:09:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能这样面对面和您说话 简直像是在做梦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.78,0:09:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈是您的忠实舞迷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.11,0:09:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们母女俩一起去看了好多次您的演出
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.90,0:09:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.99,0:09:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您还记得吗 前年在国立第三剧场
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.74,0:09:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.32,0:09:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还历历在目呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.03,0:09:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的那个大跳 那跳跃力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.03,0:09:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(313,325)\fs16\bord1\shad0\fsp0\fscy95}grand je{\fsp-4}te
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.20,0:09:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是回想一下就已经陶醉不已了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.70,0:09:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且凑这么近一看  您跟您母亲果然像极了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.38,0:09:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全继承了天才舞蹈家·尾形游纪的外貌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.26,0:09:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您母亲才是百年一遇...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.93,0:09:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 是十万年一遇的真明星呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.11,0:09:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜在六年前的那场地震中...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.99,0:09:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听到新闻后整整哭了好几天
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.78,0:09:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 我说你啊 口无遮拦也...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.52,0:10:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上村同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.69,0:10:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上村同学也在这边吃午饭呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.68,0:10:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二外语选的什么? 最热门的法语...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.98,0:10:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形小姐?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.47,0:10:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.65,0:10:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年一起进入二次选拔的神山
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.33,0:10:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你肯定会进这里的表演系专业呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.75,0:10:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你放弃芭蕾了 是真的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.44,0:10:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.55,0:10:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳 时间来得及吗? 差不多该去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.39,0:10:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新生辅导讲座的申请
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.61,0:10:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.29,0:10:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我要先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.30,0:10:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电话联系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.71,0:10:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小惠 这边这边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.70,0:10:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.78,0:10:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么回头见啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.01,0:10:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.03,0:10:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问...刚才说的...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.90,0:10:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃芭蕾的事是真的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.31,0:11:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.21,0:11:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,韧带断裂?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.50,0:11:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首次主演的皇后角色也因此被撤换
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.50,0:11:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(283,325)\fs16\bord1\shad0\fsp1\fscy95}Regina
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.25,0:11:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有发表正式声明 但琳已经放弃芭蕾了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.67,0:11:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会呢 伤愈复出的人不是也有...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.46,0:11:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.91,0:11:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但琳对自己的芭蕾已经无法感到满足了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.05,0:11:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标毕竟不同呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.83,0:11:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳的目标可是天才尾形游纪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.38,0:11:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不可能了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.33,0:11:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要知道 我对琳的芭蕾的痴迷程度也不输你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.50,0:12:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.37,0:13:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害呀 刚才那声雷
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.13,0:13:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 自说自话就进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.44,0:13:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你是想入部的新生?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.18,0:13:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.78,0:13:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到RideBack部
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.59,0:13:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到有这等好事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.42,0:14:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这么可爱的清秀型女孩会来我们部
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.30,0:14:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清...清秀型?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.26,0:14:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 要不要试乘一下?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.17,0:14:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天刚好调整完毕送回来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.54,0:14:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 你误会了 我只是进来避雨的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.85,0:14:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说我也没驾照
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.96,0:14:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事 开这家伙是不需要什么驾照的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.90,0:14:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复杂的操作全交给电脑就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.26,0:14:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简单的驾驶谁都能行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.30,0:14:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在还没受认可 不能上公路
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.64,0:14:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它到底是什么东西呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.09,0:14:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它叫RideBack 没在电视上看过吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.69,0:14:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.45,0:14:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 看来知名度还不高啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.85,0:14:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可变形式二轮摩托——RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.54,0:14:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做出现今二轮摩托望尘莫及的各种三次元动作
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.61,0:14:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换言之 它是台人型摩托
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.77,0:14:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近还举办了全国大赛 知名度也在渐渐攀升呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.23,0:15:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这台是Teryan·Kaduro牌
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.76,0:15:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mountain Trail·RB
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.78,0:15:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Type-L “Fuego”
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.70,0:15:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在西班牙语中是“火焰”的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.42,0:15:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FUEGO...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.52,0:15:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车如其名 多少有些难以驾驭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.12,0:15:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本操作还是很简单的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.61,0:15:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.03,0:15:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 这不是还在下雨吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.81,0:15:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当打发时间 乘上去试试嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.30,0:15:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就试一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.45,0:15:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好 非常乐意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.52,0:15:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么首先绕到车身后面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.47,0:15:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,HO{\b1}☆
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.48,0:15:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.53,0:15:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身轻如燕呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.12,0:15:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能再往前坐一点么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.30,0:15:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双手放在车把上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.70,0:15:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点一下中间的方形面板
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.72,0:16:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃...是这个吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.87,0:16:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有点摇晃感哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.66,0:16:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.40,0:16:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺高的呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.27,0:16:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.03,0:16:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和字面意思一样 有人觉得像是被驮在背上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.75,0:16:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这边来 Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.20,0:16:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它会说话吗? 这台 呃...Ride?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.61,0:16:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.54,0:16:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不会说话 但能够理解一些简单的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.62,0:16:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 雨停了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.50,0:16:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就告辞了...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.60,0:16:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.27,0:16:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RideBack在室外开更有感觉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.60,0:16:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从电池模式切换为引擎启动
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.68,0:16:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 在听我说吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.48,0:16:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.39,0:16:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右手顺时针转动正中的钥匙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.21,0:17:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按下红色开关下边的启动键
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.67,0:17:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转动右把手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.64,0:17:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右脚踩下踏板
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.11,0:17:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正视前方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.76,0:17:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK? 要解除锁定了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.51,0:17:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢松开左离合
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.18,0:17:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左手和右脚全归位后
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.16,0:17:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右手慢慢转动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.31,0:17:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就保持这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.28,0:17:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上边风景不错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.34,0:17:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着再握紧左离合
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.09,0:17:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同学 这离合根本不动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.97,0:17:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那捏右手边的离合试试?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.97,0:17:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不行 被固定住了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.28,0:17:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意前方啊 前方!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.00,0:17:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体往右倾
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.92,0:17:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往左
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.13,0:18:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮的大力侧滑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.13,0:18:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(368,325)\fs16\bord1\shad0\fsp0\fscy95}power slide
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.96,0:18:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 不好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.57,0:18:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.55,0:18:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镇定些
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.73,0:18:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它听懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.35,0:18:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.70,0:18:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大胆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.15,0:18:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 小裤裤全看到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.11,0:18:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在对重心移动产生反应
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.02,0:18:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可思议 一点都不害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.65,0:18:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事呢 感到好安心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.32,0:18:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子会跳舞呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.83,0:19:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱花离我这么近
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.87,0:19:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子 接下来能来个单足旋转吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.87,0:19:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(402,325)\fs16\bord1\shad0\fsp1\fscy95}Pirouette
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.50,0:19:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.54,0:19:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是整天在捣鼓他那台Ride 有什么事再...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.03,0:19:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开呀啊啊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.72,0:19:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 等会我再打过去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.44,0:19:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.32,0:19:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego失控了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.08,0:19:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我上车
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.93,0:19:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚看到她下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.27,0:19:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是控制芯片或者线路方面...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.34,0:19:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少废话 赶时间
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.06,0:19:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓紧我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.66,0:19:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,油门是不是有点拧过头...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.66,0:19:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太乱来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.38,0:19:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那与其说是空气动力学...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.35,0:20:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.54,0:20:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么 快关掉引擎下来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.18,0:20:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.01,0:20:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子要怎么才能停下?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.16,0:20:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就不听我的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.27,0:20:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.65,0:20:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.91,0:20:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那前面是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.33,0:20:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续握住手把 注意前方!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.71,0:20:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.01,0:21:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没路了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.08,0:21:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恢复了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.93,0:21:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刹车!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.43,0:21:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刹车?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.29,0:21:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞起来了?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.52,0:21:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.18,0:21:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.04,0:21:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的世界 开始改变了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.37,0:23:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清秀型美女来了!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.90,0:23:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们部也要热闹起来了呢 部长
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.14,0:23:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还真是对不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.82,0:23:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我就是个粗野的生锈的铁娘子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.40,0:23:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再订购一台新RideBack怎么样?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.68,0:23:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 你手上拿的是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.42,0:23:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我去部室背后聊聊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.01,0:23:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊

Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.62,0:23:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(275,263)\fs25\bord0\shad0\1c&HEDEDED&}{\fad(0,120)}珠代的挑战!? S.L.F
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.62,0:23:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(325,285)\fs22\bord0\shad0\1c&HEDEDED&}{\fad(0,120)}～Spread·Legs·Form


Comment: 0,0:00:00.01,0:00:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.01,0:00:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.77,0:03:57.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:03:50.77,0:03:57.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.77,0:03:57.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:03:50.77,0:03:57.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:00.01,0:00:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.01,0:05:19.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.02,0:05:22.02,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.03,0:05:25.03,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.74,0:22:02.10,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.46,0:22:09.83,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.08,0:22:17.45,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.70,0:22:25.34,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.39,0:22:30.68,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.09,0:22:34.43,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.97,0:22:38.48,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.80,0:22:42.70,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.49,0:22:47.94,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.01,0:22:51.74,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.83,0:22:55.69,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.72,0:22:59.46,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.52,0:23:03.29,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.38,0:23:07.72,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.61,0:23:11.40,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.40,0:23:15.54,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:57.74,0:22:02.10,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:04.46,0:22:09.83,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:13.08,0:22:17.45,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:19.70,0:22:25.34,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:27.39,0:22:30.68,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.09,0:22:34.43,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:34.97,0:22:38.48,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:38.80,0:22:42.70,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.49,0:22:47.94,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:48.01,0:22:51.74,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.83,0:22:55.69,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.72,0:22:59.46,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:59.52,0:23:03.29,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:03.38,0:23:07.72,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:08.61,0:23:11.40,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.40,0:23:15.54,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.74,0:22:02.10,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.46,0:22:09.83,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.08,0:22:17.45,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.70,0:22:25.34,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.39,0:22:30.68,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.09,0:22:34.43,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.97,0:22:38.48,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.80,0:22:42.70,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.49,0:22:47.94,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.01,0:22:51.74,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.83,0:22:55.69,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.72,0:22:59.46,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.52,0:23:03.29,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.38,0:23:07.72,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.61,0:23:11.40,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.40,0:23:15.54,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:57.74,0:22:02.10,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:04.46,0:22:09.83,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:13.08,0:22:17.45,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:19.70,0:22:25.34,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:27.39,0:22:30.68,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.09,0:22:34.43,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:34.97,0:22:38.48,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:38.80,0:22:42.70,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.49,0:22:47.94,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:48.01,0:22:51.74,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.83,0:22:55.69,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.72,0:22:59.46,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:59.52,0:23:03.29,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:03.38,0:23:07.72,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:08.61,0:23:11.40,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.40,0:23:15.54,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶


Comment: 0,0:01:58.77,0:01:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.76,0:03:59.51,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.14,0:04:02.91,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.93,0:04:06.44,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.53,0:04:09.86,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.23,0:04:13.40,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.45,0:04:17.09,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.37,0:04:20.56,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.64,0:04:24.16,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.81,0:04:41.12,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.17,0:04:44.91,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.95,0:04:48.59,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.61,0:04:50.06,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.10,0:04:53.47,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.49,0:04:57.14,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.14,0:04:59.34,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.84,0:05:06.61,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this
