[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 03
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.87,0:00:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好高呀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.22,0:00:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过好像感觉不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.08,0:00:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我通宵才组装好的  别弄坏哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.98,0:00:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.88,0:00:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  不要松开手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.75,0:00:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心惊肉跳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.73,0:00:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问...Regulation是?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.11,0:00:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是指机体性能符不符合参赛标准吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.41,0:00:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是差距太大的话  根本就不用比了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.93,0:00:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.80,0:00:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego的外形是市面上的一般型号
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.92,0:00:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过内部构造是冈仓顾问一手组装而成的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先骨架结构就已经超出参赛标准了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.04,0:00:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能开它参赛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.65,0:00:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.18,0:00:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.48,0:00:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Balon和Fuego一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.83,0:00:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是Teryan·Kaduro牌的新型号
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.02,0:00:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操作系统也相同  小琳肯定...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.30,0:00:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好危险
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.32,0:01:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说你什么好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.44,0:01:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再三提醒你要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.45,0:01:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.08,0:01:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.25,0:01:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别游手好闲了  快点过来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.59,0:01:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.92,0:01:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不开Fuego就觉得不安吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.50,0:01:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.35,0:01:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力练习的奖励
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.66,0:01:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过半个月来的特训  进步不小哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.31,0:01:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在大赛上也足有一搏之力了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.72,0:01:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.69,0:01:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天开赛  来分个高下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.02,0:01:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}将出任GGP治安维持部队司令的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.91,0:01:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}罗曼诺夫·卡伦巴克大校抵达横田基地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.00,0:01:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}预定下周举行的就任仪式
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.09,0:01:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}以首相为首的内阁大臣们将全体出席
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.45,0:03:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是RB-Z
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.20,0:03:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好赞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.26,0:03:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是纯国产的最后旗舰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.87,0:03:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过真亏她能弄到手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.66,0:03:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈今年也是夺冠大热门吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.08,0:03:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挡道啦!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.72,0:03:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢吞吞地跑个死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.77,0:03:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓先生  大赛委员会简报会要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.77,0:03:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(295,326)\fs16\bord1\shad0\fsp2\fscy95}marshal
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.28,0:03:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了

Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.82,0:04:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,233)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)}於是 信號旗揮下

Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.64,0:04:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs20\fad(0,200)}这里是为您带来无限精彩的FM实况转播节目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.64,0:04:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\pos(12,12)\fs16\bord0\4c&H4A4A4A&\i1\fad(0,200)}译注: 电台节目内容翻译精确度\N比较低&有部分忽略, 还请见谅

Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.31,0:04:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}<HURRY CARRY PETTING OUT>!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.44,0:04:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}今天的嘉宾是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.45,0:04:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子姊  这边这边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.91,0:04:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  我带慰问品来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.98,0:04:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垂涎欲滴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.29,0:04:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是谢谢你啦  特意送到这种深山里来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.38,0:04:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啦  正好有空
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.44,0:04:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像过节似的  气氛不错呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.87,0:04:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是每年一度的大会
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.76,0:04:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再怎么也要热闹一番嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.89,0:04:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说有些队真的是来凑热闹的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.39,0:04:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们队至少名义上是卫冕冠军
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.86,0:04:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能那么胡闹就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.73,0:04:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.76,0:04:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和珠代学姊一起在试车
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.79,0:04:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.93,0:05:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.14,0:05:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那跑法是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.86,0:05:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得有点不顺心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.29,0:05:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉...就好像被车把牵着走一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.79,0:05:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也表达不好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.83,0:05:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.62,0:05:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去把Balon的差速限制装置界限调高试试
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.62,0:05:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,326)\fs16\bord1\shad0\fsp2\fscy95}LSD
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.65,0:05:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  为了方便左转弯时姿势放低
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.14,0:05:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,减震器的阻尼值也重新设定一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.21,0:05:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太强人所难了吧  离预选只剩两小时了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.88,0:05:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勉强赶上都很困难啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.06,0:05:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在这样子根本没法比
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.88,0:05:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被车把牵着走吗...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.71,0:05:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何?  二连霸有希望吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.26,0:05:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是为此而来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.92,0:05:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令尊也在为你加油吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.08,0:05:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲跟比赛没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.88,0:05:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊的父亲是名人吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.63,0:05:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,历任大藏大臣和外相
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.61,0:05:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,执政党中的最大派系的首脑人物
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.85,0:05:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈南风
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.61,0:05:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没在电视上见过吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.32,0:06:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个看起来就像大坏蛋的?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.54,0:06:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.43,0:06:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上  大哥还是警察中的精英官僚
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.57,0:06:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈先生在参加GGP的研修时  和新司令见过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.06,0:06:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  还是特别课程来着
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.56,0:06:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说他是指挥RideBack部队而发迹的?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.12,0:06:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使得陷入苦战的GGP一举扭转局面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.33,0:06:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经成为传说的一战
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.85,0:06:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“亚利桑那战役”
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.66,0:06:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但正式记录中一概没有他的踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.49,0:06:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP的怪事之一
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.32,0:06:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来好假
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.10,0:06:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mr.片冈  这边请
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.21,0:06:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就去见见这位话题人物了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.77,0:06:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}决定正赛起跑杆位的预赛部分开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.47,0:06:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}难点在于山岳赛道中如何不失误哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.38,0:06:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是设置问题
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.54,0:06:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她之所以那么快  原因全在Fuego吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.69,0:06:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.15,0:06:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  加油
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.20,0:07:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.26,0:07:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  成绩还是没上来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.32,0:07:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉费尽全力才勉强跑起来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.01,0:07:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有资格说她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.77,0:07:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.17,0:07:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次参赛  能全程跑完就很了不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.13,0:07:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  让这个崭崭新的新人参赛本身就太乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.11,0:07:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本以为琳姊不管开什么型号都没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.65,0:07:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来RideBack也讲缘分啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.28,0:07:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才怪啦  设置相同就等于是同一台机体
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.75,0:07:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过Fuego是有些怪毛病
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.67,0:07:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这层意思上  说不定是有点缘分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.01,0:07:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  连你都开始说胡话了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.94,0:07:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前就有些在意了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.09,0:07:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连珠代学姊也没法完全驾驭Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.23,0:07:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能扔在一边对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.79,0:07:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而小琳却那么得心应手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.82,0:07:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得奇怪吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.02,0:07:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.44,0:07:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不顺心  有什么东西在阻碍我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.36,0:07:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.73,0:07:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是开Fuego明明...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.28,0:08:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  都给老子放认真点!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.91,0:08:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混账  给我记着!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.18,0:08:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓唬我们队新人的一点报复而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.28,0:08:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}预赛开始就遥遥领先
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.68,0:08:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}卫冕冠军  RideBack Princess  片冈珠代
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.40,0:08:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最快的一个  预赛第一名啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.62,0:08:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.25,0:08:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.97,0:08:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego的自动控制系统设置...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.97,0:08:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(336,326)\fs16\bord1\shad0\fsp2\fscy95}ACS
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.24,0:08:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矩阵全乱七八糟的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.42,0:08:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样还不如不用呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.74,0:08:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓顾问为什么会采用这种设定呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.85,0:08:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田  怎么又擅自乱动RB-Z
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.76,0:08:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前叉设定调回原始值
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.10,0:08:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有三档下的加速改成齿轮传动
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.43,0:08:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等调整完正赛都要开始啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.01,0:08:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易预赛拿到第一名
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.91,0:09:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.86,0:09:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有Balon的设置问题...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.50,0:09:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这个问题  虽然有点乱来...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.38,0:09:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豪赌么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.73,0:09:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  照你的意思去做
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.65,0:09:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.00,0:09:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦啦  琳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.37,0:09:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预赛好像是17名
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.39,0:09:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.91,0:09:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田  只剩10分钟啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.92,0:09:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一步了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.20,0:09:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.00,0:09:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊好像很失落呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.22,0:09:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟登台前的表情一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.49,0:09:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就是那样集中精神的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.51,0:09:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论怎样的情况下  琳都不会轻易言弃的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.93,0:09:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最了解她了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.20,0:09:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}全日本RideBack冠军赛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.31,0:09:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}正赛终于要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.36,0:09:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}您正在收听的是SNN-Motor频道<赛车族GO!>节目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.91,0:10:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}解说嘉宾是<RideBack Magazine>的铃木总编
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.33,0:10:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}大家好  我是<RideBack Magazine>的铃木
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.51,0:10:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}那么事不宜迟...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.56,0:10:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简单来说就是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.46,0:10:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把Balon搭载的ACS辅助系统给卸载了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.95,0:10:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ACS?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.58,0:10:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego当然也有搭载
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.31,0:10:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我看了下备份资料  故意设置成了无效状态
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.60,0:10:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就卸了Balon的ACS
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.38,0:10:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设成了和Fuego相同的状态
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.90,0:10:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起跑阶段别飙太猛  慢慢来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.79,0:10:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就请加油啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.19,0:10:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.93,0:10:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}全日本RideBack冠军赛终于要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.24,0:10:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}去年片冈珠代史无前例地首创了...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.11,0:10:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好兴奋呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.37,0:10:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.50,0:10:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛中那么设置果然还是不太妙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.01,0:11:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不成功则成仁了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.60,0:11:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我预感小琳肯定能行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.64,0:11:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}...全日本RideBack冠军赛  终于进入倒数了!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.10,0:11:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  没撞着
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.60,0:11:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早看穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.35,0:11:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  片冈压制住第一个弯道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.93,0:11:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.65,0:11:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  出发晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.09,0:11:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}本杰明·富兰克林在巴黎不断地争取法国对美国独立革命的援助
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.22,0:11:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Nice Start!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.01,0:12:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形  你来翻译一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.96,0:12:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.07,0:12:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.97,0:12:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.72,0:12:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久疏问候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.42,0:12:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到日本

Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.89,0:12:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RB-Z  继续保持领先
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.46,0:12:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Balon呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.32,0:12:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒数第二
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.58,0:12:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.83,0:12:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊  Fight!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.90,0:12:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 超过一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.78,0:12:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}越野赛区  山岳赛道一切正常
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.23,0:12:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}领先的是710号  即将进入山岳赛道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.35,0:12:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊又超过一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.45,0:13:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来状态不错  说不定真能行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.81,0:13:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然过弯时姿势比较高
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.36,0:13:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过相比之前要顺心多了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.74,0:13:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也反对引进警用RideBack吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.85,0:13:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的个人意见无碍大局
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.38,0:13:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是想尽力吸收其优点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.27,0:13:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拟定万全之策之后再一步到位
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.19,0:13:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好滑头的抵抗方式啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.74,0:13:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前任在你们身上耽误了太多时间
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.30,0:13:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来替他收拾残局的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.26,0:13:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别指望我会手下留情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.42,0:13:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本国解散RideBack部队
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.19,0:13:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为没有局部战争的需要了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.18,0:13:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这个国家不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.40,0:13:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐世保和小仓的恐怖活动中已经用上了RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.41,0:13:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个狭小的国度肯定会大显身手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.86,0:13:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭现有的装备足以应对了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.60,0:13:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让自己的国家装甲车满街跑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.57,0:13:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.21,0:13:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是不认为长了两只手的摩托车
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.47,0:14:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能成为有效抑制手段罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.77,0:14:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本人的脑筋真是死板得要命
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.37,0:14:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经的部下中也有这么一个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.16,0:14:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过那男人靠着开RideBack成了英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.86,0:14:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}进入越野赛区之后片冈珠代依然一马当先
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.82,0:14:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}科波拉(Cobra)兄弟紧随其后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.64,0:14:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恨的片冈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.85,0:14:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你赢的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.47,0:14:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真烦人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.99,0:14:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}同时后方集团中有一位突出选手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.27,0:14:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}711号  首次参赛的女骑手...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.21,0:14:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会有那么危险的骑法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.10,0:14:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那骑法是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.74,0:14:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害  又超过一个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.08,0:14:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是琳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.94,0:14:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  冈仓顾问打来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.46,0:14:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是在大赛委员会...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.88,0:14:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  您好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.86,0:14:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙  把Balon的ACS卸了是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.75,0:15:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被发现了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.30,0:15:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过没违反参赛规则啦...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.45,0:15:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样会给对手添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.02,0:15:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发进站信号  让她弃权
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.61,0:15:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  可她的排名也在上升啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.72,0:15:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说不会有问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.24,0:15:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.83,0:15:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上发进站信号...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.28,0:15:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.52,0:15:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘了教她信号牌的意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.49,0:15:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢材!  自己想办法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.55,0:15:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.29,0:15:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓顾问说...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.94,0:15:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Balon太危险  让她赶快弃权
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.21,0:15:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.56,0:15:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把Balon的ACS关掉的事被他看穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.79,0:15:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么呀  那个什么AC...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.98,0:15:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自动对悬挂系统的平衡控制进行辅助的装置
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.66,0:15:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\bord0\shad0\b1\1c&H000000&}小琳  快进站!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.43,0:15:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有它的话RideBack会极度不稳定
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.85,0:15:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微遇上点颠簸就会摔倒
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.26,0:15:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那琳现在岂不是超危险的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.23,0:15:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般情况确实如此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.66,0:15:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小琳现在跑得显然比预赛时还快
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.23,0:15:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只是我的推测
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.42,0:16:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳的反射神经速度可能超过了自动修正
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.05,0:16:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者在刹那间产生了某种另外的修正来弥补
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.70,0:16:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然难以置信  但小琳就这么在跑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.87,0:16:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}嘿  后方开始有动静了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.06,0:16:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}是片冈选手的后辈呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.83,0:16:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掌握技巧了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.50,0:16:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}从后方以惊人的气势一路赶超
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.09,0:16:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}单圈成绩也不坏  已经赶上大集团了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.57,0:16:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}好强的赶超
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.68,0:16:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}711号  一口气超过了集团中的三台
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.66,0:16:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}好厉害啊  离胜利只有一步之遥了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.39,0:16:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.43,0:16:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.48,0:16:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}...接近背后了  711号
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.95,0:16:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}等  等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.59,0:16:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}这位新人在第三扇形区的单圈速度
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.16,0:16:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}比领先集团还要快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.67,0:16:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种热情高涨的气氛是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.85,0:16:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.65,0:16:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于开足马力了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.41,0:16:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥  要替我赢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.93,0:16:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hiroshi  你的死不会白费...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.25,0:16:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想干架么  放马过来!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.47,0:16:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.71,0:17:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那对蝮蛇兄弟  太卑鄙了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.12,0:17:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要提出抗议吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.57,0:17:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用吧 冈仓顾问也在大赛委员会看着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.90,0:17:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起担心这个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.64,0:17:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是看着她  免得比赛完了之后把那对兄弟给杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.11,0:17:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}...经过起跑线了  领先的是科波拉(兄)
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.44,0:17:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}一二名相差无几
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.00,0:17:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追上了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.81,0:17:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等得都不耐烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.32,0:17:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  这里的虚拟语气
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.64,0:17:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听一下下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.40,0:17:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}...并非领先的片冈选手  而是同队的新人!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.02,0:17:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}711号
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.73,0:17:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}绝对没错  她就是新一代RideBack Princess
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.82,0:17:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}她的名字是!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.60,0:17:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好心理准备了吧  尾形
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.55,0:17:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ye..Yes
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.24,0:17:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊第四名了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.04,0:17:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真叫人捏把汗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.63,0:18:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.94,0:18:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过还是不同  跟Fuego还是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.40,0:18:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不用打出这东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.04,0:18:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正已经最后一圈了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.08,0:18:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是冈仓顾问吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.09,0:18:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来没事么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.37,0:18:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把Balon的排气调控系统关了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.44,0:18:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引擎要烧了  菱田你来赔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.81,0:18:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.48,0:18:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}怎么回事  711号尾形选手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.37,0:18:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}引擎爆裂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.62,0:18:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引擎完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.99,0:18:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}太遗憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.27,0:18:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}上演了一出精彩赶超的尾形选手就此退赛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.01,0:18:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}真是令人遗憾万分
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.34,0:18:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Balon跟不上她的骑术吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.61,0:18:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}最后一个弯道定胜负  科波拉(兄)紧追不舍!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.95,0:18:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}差距微乎其微!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.89,0:18:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  明年再决胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.47,0:19:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.24,0:19:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据我们的调查
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.40,0:19:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎没有在GGP的RideBack部队中活跃过的日本人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.34,0:19:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错  连小道消息都没
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.34,0:19:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想到一个可能的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.45,0:19:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应GGP要求  公安秘密盯着的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.02,0:19:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个神秘的归国者
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.27,0:19:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且兴趣似乎还是RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.70,0:19:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯~
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.88,0:20:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把那对惹人讨厌的蝮蛇兄弟狠狠教训一顿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.75,0:20:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊太强了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.59,0:20:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好感动
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.13,0:20:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁啊  给这家伙喝酒的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.39,0:20:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是未成年人  只给她喝了橙汁哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.74,0:20:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说呀  要是Balon没出故障就第四名了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.65,0:20:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Balon...笨蛋...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.16,0:20:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs23}熏一下就醉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.97,0:20:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  那孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.71,0:20:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳说开Fuego去散一下步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.41,0:20:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.37,0:20:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Balon的事...很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.63,0:21:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是技师的失误  不是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.39,0:21:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能问个问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.35,0:21:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头一回乘上Fuego那次
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.82,0:21:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么没减慢加速  而是选择了起跳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.14,0:21:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手忙脚乱的  自己也不是很明白
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.86,0:21:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是  不知为什么...觉得Fuego能够信任
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.47,0:21:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再去开一会

Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.76,0:23:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓顾问  关于Balon的修理问题...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.70,0:23:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引擎翻修这台阶有点太高了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.15,0:23:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能请你拨一点追加预算...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.19,0:23:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来一直在睡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.24,0:23:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表情根本看不出来!


Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.18,0:23:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,245)\fs23\b1\bord0\shad1\1c&HFFFFFF&\4c&H6A6A6A&\4a&H3F&}{\fad(0,120)}祥子{\fnzhunyuan}、{\fn華康中黑體}千鈞一發之際


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.77,0:01:58.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:01:51.77,0:01:58.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.77,0:01:58.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:01:51.77,0:01:58.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.01,0:03:20.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.02,0:03:23.02,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.03,0:03:26.03,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.11,0:22:01.47,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.83,0:22:09.20,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.45,0:22:16.82,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.07,0:22:24.71,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.76,0:22:30.05,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.46,0:22:33.80,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.34,0:22:37.85,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.07,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.86,0:22:47.31,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.38,0:22:51.11,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.20,0:22:55.06,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.09,0:22:58.83,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.89,0:23:02.66,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.75,0:23:07.09,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.98,0:23:10.77,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.77,0:23:14.91,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:57.11,0:22:01.47,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.83,0:22:09.20,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.45,0:22:16.82,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:19.07,0:22:24.71,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.76,0:22:30.05,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.46,0:22:33.80,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:34.34,0:22:37.85,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.07,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.86,0:22:47.31,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.38,0:22:51.11,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.20,0:22:55.06,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.09,0:22:58.83,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.89,0:23:02.66,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.75,0:23:07.09,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:07.98,0:23:10.77,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.77,0:23:14.91,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.11,0:22:01.47,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.83,0:22:09.20,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.45,0:22:16.82,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.07,0:22:24.71,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.76,0:22:30.05,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.46,0:22:33.80,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.34,0:22:37.85,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.07,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.86,0:22:47.31,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.38,0:22:51.11,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.20,0:22:55.06,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.09,0:22:58.83,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.89,0:23:02.66,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.75,0:23:07.09,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.98,0:23:10.77,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.77,0:23:14.91,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:57.11,0:22:01.47,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.83,0:22:09.20,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.45,0:22:16.82,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:19.07,0:22:24.71,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.76,0:22:30.05,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.46,0:22:33.80,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:34.34,0:22:37.85,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.07,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.86,0:22:47.31,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.38,0:22:51.11,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.20,0:22:55.06,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.09,0:22:58.83,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.89,0:23:02.66,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.75,0:23:07.09,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:07.98,0:23:10.77,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.77,0:23:14.91,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.76,0:02:00.51,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.14,0:02:03.91,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.93,0:02:07.44,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.53,0:02:10.86,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.23,0:02:14.40,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.45,0:02:18.09,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.37,0:02:21.56,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.64,0:02:25.16,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.81,0:02:42.12,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.17,0:02:45.91,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.95,0:02:49.59,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.61,0:02:51.06,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.10,0:02:54.47,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.49,0:02:58.14,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.14,0:03:00.34,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.84,0:03:07.61,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this
