[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 08
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.87,0:06:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(403,236)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)} {\fnzhunyuan\fs35}GET RIDE!{\fn華康中黑體\fs28}{\org(-5000,0)\fr0.03} 被選中之人

Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.16,0:00:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.49,0:00:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又见面了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.56,0:00:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不“飞”了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.95,0:00:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.48,0:01:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego Type-L吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.30,0:01:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被它选中了么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.36,0:01:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.49,0:01:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来相当不满啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.20,0:01:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是乖乖去GGP比较好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.16,0:01:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.30,0:01:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫基弗 一介恐怖分子而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.48,0:01:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么人 尾形琳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.84,0:01:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突破GGP的包围
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.91,0:01:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把警方的特种车玩弄于掌心的神秘RB少女
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.63,0:01:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是那样的 我只是一心为了救人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.32,0:01:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,错了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.57,0:01:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐上Fuego的你不受任何人与事的拘束
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.69,0:02:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在祝福之光中 你把目的调换了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.87,0:02:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.28,0:02:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我也和你一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.98,0:02:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自由了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.82,0:02:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接你的人很快就到 在那之前就随意好了

Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.19,0:04:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约10年前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.25,0:04:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在大陆的一隅打响的 小小的战争
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.27,0:04:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终改变了全球的秩序
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.44,0:04:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本GGP只不过是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.26,0:04:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对超级大国的全球性军事支配进行抵抗的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.97,0:04:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小规模抵抗势力之一
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.74,0:04:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级大国与GGP的实力差距 一目了然
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.77,0:05:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而扭转了这一形势的 就是日后的“传说之战”
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.21,0:05:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚利桑那战役
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.05,0:05:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为超级大国支配权象征的ICBM基地
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.37,0:05:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至能抵御核报复攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.86,0:05:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这座难攻不落的铁壁要塞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.96,0:05:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天才科学家 齐力·玛伽农一手创建的RideBack部队
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.92,0:05:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对这里发动了奇袭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.28,0:05:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指挥官是当时还正年轻的罗曼诺夫·卡伦巴克
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.83,0:05:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RB部队成功攻陷基地
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.66,0:05:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以这场胜利为界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.25,0:05:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP逐步扩张 最终攀上了霸主宝座
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.26,0:05:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是被幽禁在基地中的齐力博士没能被救出
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.38,0:06:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外RideBack部队有半数战死
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.16,0:06:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其后 部队内又发生违反军纪事件
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.02,0:06:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多名上级士兵遭处分
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.63,0:06:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 这场历史性胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.95,0:06:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成了不可公开的“传说之战”
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.69,0:06:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神秘RB少女的社团顾问 冈仓天司郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.46,0:06:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与曾经的战友 GGP司令罗曼诺夫·卡伦巴克
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.86,0:06:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都被RideBack连在一起了吗...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.45,0:06:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来是军用RB制造厂商 HESNER公司
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.22,0:07:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东西已经到货了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.01,0:07:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要开始为派对做准备了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.34,0:07:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让GGP突入之后再引爆么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.91,0:07:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一被突然轰炸怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.41,0:07:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧 他们肯定会为了哥布林摇着尾巴跑来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.83,0:07:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙想要的 是我和基弗的尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.12,0:07:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确如此
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.83,0:07:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解开手铐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.49,0:07:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里往西北方向5km
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.55,0:07:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一座大别墅里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.43,0:07:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 你先去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.57,0:07:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要留在这里欢迎他们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.95,0:07:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,防身用的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.35,0:07:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说你可能根本用不着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.33,0:07:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标车辆 依旧停在原地 没有动静
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.41,0:07:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封锁半径5km内的主干道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.11,0:07:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Bravo小队 绕到目标背后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.31,0:07:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是一座弃用的气象观测所 要开始轰炸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.60,0:08:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不用 慢慢地把鼠辈们全熏出来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.81,0:08:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.59,0:08:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突入部队 失去联络
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.26,0:08:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Bravo来电 疑似目标的人物正向西北偏北移动
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.22,0:08:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去目标
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.54,0:08:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他们可能会逃去的建筑全挑出来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.22,0:08:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残存兵力重新整编之后做好移动准备
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.97,0:08:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加图姆 你带RideBack部队绕到他们前面去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.36,0:08:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.22,0:08:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\shad0\bord0\1c&H000000&\fs23}冈仓研究班暂时休讲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.76,0:08:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.85,0:09:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到曾经的英雄哥布林会在这种地方工作
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.16,0:09:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形琳 冈仓天司郎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.90,0:09:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想就他们两个的事和你商量一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.40,0:09:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她为了救出弟弟 确实向警察反抗了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.22,0:09:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要是我没让她上车的话 她根本就不会被逮捕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.05,0:09:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感到自己也有点责任
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.55,0:09:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.94,0:09:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓先生跟这事又有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.26,0:09:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP司令罗曼诺夫·卡伦巴克
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.00,0:09:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们两个是战友
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.26,0:09:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战友?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.99,0:09:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过据我所知 他们关系并不好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.53,0:09:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如说是被盯上了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.62,0:09:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要我怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.76,0:09:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许有办法救出尾形琳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.98,0:09:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,材料有了 但证据不足
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.60,0:10:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了补足这部分 我需要一点门路 明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.95,0:10:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 不过作为交换 你也要协助我们这边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.80,0:10:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\shad0\bord0\1c&H000000&\fs23}私人领地 禁止入内
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.48,0:10:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,B-Knight
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.05,0:10:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BMA的主力机型 要坐上试试看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.43,0:10:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 我不想骑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.83,0:10:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过Fuego是一台特别的机体吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.11,0:10:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego到底哪里特别了?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.84,0:11:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该最清楚不过了 为什么要隐瞒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.79,0:11:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隐瞒?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.96,0:11:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不懂 就是为了弄清这点我才...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.14,0:11:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机体与骑手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.98,0:11:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此都超越界限时才能看到的炫目光景
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.15,0:11:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兴奋的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.84,0:11:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对被选中的骑手来说 那里就是整个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.83,0:11:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳 好好记着
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.18,0:11:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对舞者来说 舞台就是一切
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.04,0:11:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是整个世界 是人生的意义所在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.10,0:11:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.87,0:11:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被选中了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.66,0:11:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.86,0:11:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.83,0:11:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被造出它的那个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.94,0:11:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也和你一样 是被哥布林——冈仓选中之人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.63,0:12:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.68,0:12:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他到之前我来教你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.88,0:12:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是真正的Ride

Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.43,0:12:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么军队会出动
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.22,0:12:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP瞒着我们在干些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.59,0:12:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,县警那边传来消息说国道正遭封锁
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.86,0:12:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了 转到这边来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.76,0:12:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.45,0:12:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人找您
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.70,0:12:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从妹妹那里听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.65,0:12:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边有多混乱你也看到了 有事请快说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.46,0:12:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}就在方才 25号国道因GGP的车辆管制而封锁
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.16,0:12:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是关于这场混乱的元凶们的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.24,0:12:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}为此 以下区域间将不可通行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.56,0:12:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}西25区至26区 东32区至...




Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.31,0:13:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RRON?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.88,0:13:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制Ride的骨干操作系统
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.78,0:13:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于一度记录过的动作 机体会自动做出回应
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.61,0:13:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego和这些家伙搭载了由哥布林
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.99,0:13:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是冈仓研发的更为进化的系统
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.54,0:13:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它就像纯种赛马一样 是会自己挑选骑手的机体
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.74,0:13:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机体给出回应的刹那 骑手必须做出下一个判断
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.66,0:13:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做不到这点的人没有资格驾驶它
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.79,0:13:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是被它驮在背上而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.40,0:13:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是被驮着...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.41,0:13:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把B-Knight配合上你的EW手环了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.04,0:13:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意志能给机体注入生命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.22,0:13:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与爱马“人马合一” 体验一下真正的Ride吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.95,0:13:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿起缰绳吧 尾形琳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.90,0:13:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把沉睡在你体内的力量 展现给我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.85,0:14:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.91,0:17:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基弗 出击了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.72,0:17:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到 我马上就去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.04,0:17:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他来接你之前老老实实待在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.05,0:17:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.89,0:17:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦出击之后就没得补给了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.64,0:17:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌方RideBack15台 其后方还有多个小队
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.77,0:17:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包围网正在渐渐收紧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.26,0:17:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规模和预想相当
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.98,0:18:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大老远把人叫来 一声不吭就想出门了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.36,0:18:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.91,0:18:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来的真晚啊 小公主都等得不耐烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.33,0:18:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.56,0:18:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说要和我们并肩作战? 哥布林
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.26,0:18:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥布林已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.88,0:18:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.09,0:18:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但罗曼诺夫还厚颜无耻地活着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.44,0:18:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就在这里面的庭院里 连机体一起带走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.46,0:18:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有缘再见
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.55,0:19:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一口气攻进去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.84,0:19:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是陷阱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.41,0:19:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标建筑周边发生爆炸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.92,0:19:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二小队全灭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.01,0:19:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一台黑色RB出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.48,0:19:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加图姆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.72,0:19:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.04,0:19:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你还跑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.02,0:20:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.47,0:20:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去联络 没人回答
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.72,0:20:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.20,0:20:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让阿帕奇去追击 烧光他们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.61,0:20:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么做无妨吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.98,0:20:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妨什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.01,0:20:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情报局的烂摊子还是我们在收拾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.86,0:20:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们闭上嘴看着就是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.54,0:21:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加图姆中尉联络
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.05,0:21:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接过来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.01,0:21:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.23,0:21:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗曼诺夫·卡伦巴克
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.56,0:21:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.79,0:21:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜就任
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.15,0:21:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 谢谢你的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.23,0:21:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临时组建的RB部队
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.09,0:21:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾 还不够我吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.30,0:21:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要的是我的尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.71,0:21:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要的是你的尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.07,0:21:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得你有胜算吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.71,0:21:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱哭鬼罗曼诺夫少爷
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.55,0:21:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗干净脖子等着吧

Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.07,0:23:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BMA不读作“BU-MA”吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.20,0:23:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 违法反GGP组织“BUMA”
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.86,0:23:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过标志不是熊 <KUMA> 而是臭鼬哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.62,0:23:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算是俏皮话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.26,0:23:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最具标志性的是黄色烟幕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.18,0:23:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BU~

Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.55,0:23:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,245)\fs23\b1\bord0\shad1\1c&HFFFFFF&\4c&H6A6A6A&\4a&H3F&}{\fad(0,120)}向陽的庭院中


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.66,0:02:47.48,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:02:40.66,0:02:47.48,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.66,0:02:47.48,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:02:40.66,0:02:47.48,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.90,0:04:08.90,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.91,0:04:11.91,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.92,0:04:14.92,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.42,0:22:00.78,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.14,0:22:08.51,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.76,0:22:16.13,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.38,0:22:24.02,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.07,0:22:29.36,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:33.11,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.65,0:22:37.16,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.48,0:22:41.38,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.17,0:22:46.62,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.69,0:22:50.42,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.51,0:22:54.37,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.40,0:22:58.14,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:01.97,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.06,0:23:06.40,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.29,0:23:10.08,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.08,0:23:14.22,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:56.42,0:22:00.78,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.14,0:22:08.51,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:11.76,0:22:16.13,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:18.38,0:22:24.02,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.07,0:22:29.36,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:29.77,0:22:33.11,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:33.65,0:22:37.16,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:37.48,0:22:41.38,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.17,0:22:46.62,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:46.69,0:22:50.42,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.51,0:22:54.37,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:54.40,0:22:58.14,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.20,0:23:01.97,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.06,0:23:06.40,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:07.29,0:23:10.08,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.08,0:23:14.22,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.42,0:22:00.78,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.14,0:22:08.51,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.76,0:22:16.13,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.38,0:22:24.02,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.07,0:22:29.36,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.77,0:22:33.11,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.65,0:22:37.16,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.48,0:22:41.38,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.17,0:22:46.62,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.69,0:22:50.42,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.51,0:22:54.37,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.40,0:22:58.14,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:01.97,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.06,0:23:06.40,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.29,0:23:10.08,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.08,0:23:14.22,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:56.42,0:22:00.78,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.14,0:22:08.51,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:11.76,0:22:16.13,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:18.38,0:22:24.02,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.07,0:22:29.36,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:29.77,0:22:33.11,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:33.65,0:22:37.16,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:37.48,0:22:41.38,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.17,0:22:46.62,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:46.69,0:22:50.42,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.51,0:22:54.37,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:54.40,0:22:58.14,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.20,0:23:01.97,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.06,0:23:06.40,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:07.29,0:23:10.08,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.08,0:23:14.22,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.65,0:02:49.40,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.03,0:02:52.80,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.82,0:02:56.33,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.42,0:02:59.75,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.12,0:03:03.29,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.34,0:03:06.98,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.26,0:03:10.45,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.53,0:03:14.05,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.70,0:03:31.01,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.06,0:03:34.80,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.84,0:03:38.48,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.50,0:03:39.95,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.99,0:03:43.36,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.38,0:03:47.03,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.03,0:03:49.23,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.73,0:03:56.50,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this

