[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 07
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.66,0:00:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.40,0:00:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请停手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.59,0:00:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你们...请停手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.41,0:00:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上高中的那会儿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.53,0:00:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到别人有什么东西 自己确实也会想要呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.21,0:00:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很能理解 我以前也是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.66,0:00:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.73,0:00:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开车时把相熟的学长推下车杀掉还是不行的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.30,0:00:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.75,0:00:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有杀任何人!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.49,0:00:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 答错啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.12,0:01:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要再来一次吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.06,0:01:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人不是你们自己杀的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.14,0:01:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BUBU— 又答错了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.95,0:01:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不快点答对的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.67,0:01:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们只能去问那位可爱的大姊姊啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.65,0:01:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意承认杀人 在笔录上签字了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.75,0:01:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了

Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.66,0:03:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.37,0:03:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.96,0:03:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.69,0:03:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该感谢这么替你着想的弟弟

Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.28,0:04:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(147,233)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(800,330)}罪與罰

Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.13,0:04:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚 在笠原市内的135号县道上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.99,0:04:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用违法车辆 对一般市民施以暴行的暴走族集团
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.36,0:04:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共有10人被逮捕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.61,0:04:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中还包括了未成年的少男少女...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.11,0:04:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您拨打的电话不在服务区 或已关机 目前无法接通
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.58,0:04:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.01,0:04:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 接不通
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.46,0:04:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定没事的 再说还没确定就是琳姊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.84,0:04:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道总有一天会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.31,0:04:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河合学长
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.93,0:05:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 受不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.02,0:05:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田学长 我可以骑一下Balon吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.38,0:05:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 要骑Balon?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.66,0:05:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.66,0:05:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不做点什么就会忍不住去想
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.92,0:05:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.39,0:05:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那样的话没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.94,0:05:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟着起什么劲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.50,0:05:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里唉声叹气 事态也不会有任何好转
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.66,0:05:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳不可能做坏事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.09,0:05:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被抓的真的是小琳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.41,0:05:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也一定是个误会 不会有事的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.66,0:05:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信她
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.90,0:05:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.31,0:05:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不让整天嚷嚷着恐怖袭击如何如何
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.54,0:05:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一心想给RideBack抹黑的那些人称心如意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.80,0:05:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也应该一如平日 照常活动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.27,0:05:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是非这么做不可
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.64,0:05:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.56,0:06:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.00,0:06:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得控制速度哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.21,0:06:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是Balon再坏了 就真的要被禁止活动了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.16,0:06:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会注意安全第一的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.93,0:06:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.28,0:06:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Rond de jambe
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.28,0:06:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\pos(12,12)\fs16\bord0\4c&H4A4A4A&\i1}译注: 芭蕾术语 以支撑脚为轴 单脚画圆
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.53,0:06:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.56,0:06:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对对 就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.62,0:06:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子还是笑起来比较可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.96,0:06:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子姊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.44,0:06:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不要松手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.28,0:07:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}昨晚 在笠原市内的135号县道上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.12,0:07:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我哥去查了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.32,0:07:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被抓的果然是尾形琳没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.43,0:07:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的弟弟因伤害致死而被拘留
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.28,0:07:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有GGP高层在干预这事 有点麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.76,0:07:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.02,0:07:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以单刀直入地问个问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.27,0:07:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.58,0:07:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在仙台地区
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.49,0:07:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新配备的白Ride在取缔暴走族行动中大为活跃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.98,0:08:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此次投入使用的白Ride已与原型机...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.34,0:08:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一批疑为恐怖分子所有的违法RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.52,0:08:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在千叶市被白Ride部队拘捕
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.11,0:08:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一名警官在行动中负伤...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.75,0:08:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于GGP强行大量引进RB的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.29,0:08:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎还有一部分反对的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.01,0:08:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确如此
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.63,0:08:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过单论反恐方面的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.70,0:08:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为RB的有用性无疑正在逐步得到验证
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.88,0:08:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有意见表示
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.24,0:08:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地方自治警察甚至应该积极引进白Ride呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.65,0:08:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 特别是在地方都市规模...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.19,0:08:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,横滨 仙台 神户 宫崎 都已决定追加配备
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.35,0:08:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离30座都市这个目标还差13
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.33,0:08:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会很困扰的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.51,0:08:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有急事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.36,0:08:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 退下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.18,0:08:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是乱来啊 片冈警视正
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.52,0:09:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.34,0:09:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就跟上面写的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.76,0:09:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,延长尾形琳的拘留时间 以及移交GGP管理
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.48,0:09:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名义上是协力 实则无视我们的立场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.65,0:09:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决定由我下 这就是我的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.15,0:09:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起搜查住宅 更像是一场大扫除
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.02,0:09:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连坚司那个凌乱不堪的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.75,0:09:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也搜得一干二净 真是佩服
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.96,0:09:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是...么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.28,0:09:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.15,0:09:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我始终相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.14,0:10:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要坚强一点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.16,0:10:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.77,0:10:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司其实也是个温柔的好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.82,0:10:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请立即离开
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.08,0:10:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能输哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.22,0:10:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是一心为了救祥子 救坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.76,0:10:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明仅此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.53,0:10:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却伤害了素不相识的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.00,0:10:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是换作母亲的话 您会怎么做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.91,0:10:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不要光在那跳舞 回答我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.86,0:11:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是被选中之人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.20,0:11:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被选中? 被谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.41,0:12:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了行使力量
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.80,0:12:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.24,0:12:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.89,0:12:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的力量是?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.28,0:12:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了战斗 为了夺取胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.41,0:12:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了打倒你的敌人

Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.51,0:12:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}GGP的战略是凭借军事力量进行支配
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.11,0:12:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}应该是因此而支持反GGP运动的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.43,0:12:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}原来如此 但是也有这样的传闻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.64,0:12:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}说轰动一时的RB少女 其实是GGP的自导自演
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.89,0:12:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.20,0:12:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.49,0:12:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么GGP不公布小琳的身份呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.13,0:13:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不现身吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.45,0:13:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几时察觉的?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.32,0:13:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego的...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.24,0:14:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.64,0:14:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.35,0:14:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去唤醒亡灵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.94,0:14:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里环境真糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.05,0:14:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从人道立场来看 也应该尽快办完手续
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.99,0:14:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想在周末前 应该就能转移到GGP的基地去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.55,0:14:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼下有什么需要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.79,0:14:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.56,0:14:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.84,0:14:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.74,0:14:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请别误会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.20,0:14:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无权选择
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.90,0:15:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(200,155)}{\fn黑体\bord0\shad0\fs14\1c&H3A3A3A&\i1\b1\fr2}资料删除中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.97,0:15:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.97,0:15:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙突然...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.50,0:15:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把右手慢慢地伸出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.99,0:15:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.30,0:15:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替我转告罗曼诺夫 哥布林会去向他问好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.23,0:16:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就隐匿行踪了么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.58,0:16:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要对冈仓天司郎发布通缉令吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.57,0:16:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戏言怎么能一一当真
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.31,0:16:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没那个必要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.05,0:16:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英雄“哥布林”已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.04,0:16:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认过行李之后 请在这里签字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.66,0:17:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.57,0:17:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.57,0:17:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要...再来纠缠我了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.71,0:18:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}您现在看到的 是观众提供的录像
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.48,0:18:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}虽然相比前几天的报道 图像不甚清晰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.23,0:18:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}还是有助于更好的了解整体情况
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.98,0:18:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}问题在于位于画面远处的这台GGP装甲车
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.82,0:18:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}由此可以看出GGP与此事件有着深层关联
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.68,0:18:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(160,145)}{\fn黑体\bord1\shad0\1c&HE1E1E1&\b1\fs17\fr8\3a&H6F&}RB少女在押运途中逃亡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.82,0:18:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}今天我们有请熟悉GGP的军事评论家渡边...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.83,0:18:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 佐藤 你在看电视吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.87,0:18:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速报
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.98,0:18:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被警方拘留的笠原市伤害事件嫌疑人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.92,0:18:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在移送GGP本部的途中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.89,0:18:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭反GGP恐怖分子集团BMA绑架
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.10,0:18:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少有5人在袭击中伤亡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.76,0:18:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方才 GGP发布了特殊时期戒严令
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.28,0:18:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外 遭绑架的嫌疑人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.22,0:18:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参与电视塔爆炸事件的嫌疑也很大
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.50,0:18:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然还未成年 特殊情况特殊对待
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.40,0:18:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BMA的犯罪声明如下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.65,0:19:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是BMA
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.75,0:19:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因反GGP恐怖分子的冤罪被逮捕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.04,0:19:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通称RB少女的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.29,0:19:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经被我们BMA从蛮横无比的GGP手中救出
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.97,0:19:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事件发生后已过去了20多分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.03,0:19:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌疑人是否安全 详细情况还不得而知
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.15,0:19:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于BMA在声明中断定绑架的就是RB少女这点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.76,0:19:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP以证据不足为由 避而不言
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.38,0:19:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连把一个少女带来都办不好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.22,0:19:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情报局到底在干些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.74,0:19:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.54,0:19:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓现身了 但有疑似BMA的人尾随其后
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.38,0:19:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问如何处理
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.54,0:19:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机会难得 就请他为我们带路吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.07,0:20:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哥布林中尉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.22,0:20:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么连恐怖分子 都对RB少女这么执着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.22,0:20:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基弗中尉恭候大驾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.38,0:20:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请跟我们走一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.29,0:20:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.86,0:20:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形是为了引我出来的替罪羊吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.31,0:20:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标正以80km/h的速度向西南方向行驶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.85,0:20:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以下追踪任务移交第8机组 本组转为陆路
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.31,0:21:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.80,0:21:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又见面了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.74,0:23:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是预告对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.34,0:23:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哦 菱田真是个没用的木头人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.37,0:23:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我也办不来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.72,0:23:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 这是一次都没坐上过RB的人的嫉妒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.82,0:23:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别得意忘形


Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.70,0:23:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,245)\fs23\b1\bord0\shad1\1c&HFFFFFF&\4c&H6A6A6A&\4a&H3F&}{\fad(0,120)}GET RIDE! 被選中之人


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.77,0:01:58.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:01:51.77,0:01:58.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.77,0:01:58.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:01:51.77,0:01:58.59,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.01,0:03:20.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.02,0:03:23.02,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.03,0:03:26.03,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.68,0:22:01.04,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.40,0:22:08.77,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.02,0:22:16.39,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.64,0:22:24.28,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.33,0:22:29.62,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.03,0:22:33.37,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.91,0:22:37.42,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.74,0:22:41.64,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.43,0:22:46.88,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.95,0:22:50.68,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.77,0:22:54.63,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.66,0:22:58.40,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.46,0:23:02.23,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.32,0:23:06.66,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.55,0:23:10.34,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.34,0:23:14.48,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:56.68,0:22:01.04,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.40,0:22:08.77,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.02,0:22:16.39,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:18.64,0:22:24.28,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.33,0:22:29.62,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.03,0:22:33.37,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:33.91,0:22:37.42,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:37.74,0:22:41.64,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.43,0:22:46.88,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:46.95,0:22:50.68,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.77,0:22:54.63,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:54.66,0:22:58.40,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.46,0:23:02.23,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.32,0:23:06.66,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:07.55,0:23:10.34,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.34,0:23:14.48,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.68,0:22:01.04,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.40,0:22:08.77,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.02,0:22:16.39,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.64,0:22:24.28,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.33,0:22:29.62,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.03,0:22:33.37,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.91,0:22:37.42,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.74,0:22:41.64,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.43,0:22:46.88,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.95,0:22:50.68,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.77,0:22:54.63,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.66,0:22:58.40,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.46,0:23:02.23,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.32,0:23:06.66,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.55,0:23:10.34,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.34,0:23:14.48,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:56.68,0:22:01.04,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.40,0:22:08.77,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.02,0:22:16.39,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:18.64,0:22:24.28,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.33,0:22:29.62,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.03,0:22:33.37,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:33.91,0:22:37.42,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:37.74,0:22:41.64,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.43,0:22:46.88,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:46.95,0:22:50.68,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.77,0:22:54.63,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:54.66,0:22:58.40,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.46,0:23:02.23,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.32,0:23:06.66,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:07.55,0:23:10.34,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.34,0:23:14.48,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.76,0:02:00.51,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.14,0:02:03.91,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.93,0:02:07.44,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.53,0:02:10.86,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.23,0:02:14.40,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.45,0:02:18.09,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.37,0:02:21.56,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.64,0:02:25.16,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.81,0:02:42.12,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.17,0:02:45.91,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.95,0:02:49.59,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.61,0:02:51.06,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.10,0:02:54.47,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.49,0:02:58.14,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.14,0:03:00.34,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.84,0:03:07.61,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this
