[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 09
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.18,0:00:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤势真的不要紧吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.10,0:00:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要来救我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.56,0:00:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为责任在我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.44,0:00:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用管我 一边休息去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.81,0:01:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego和恐怖分子的RB 都是冈仓先生的作品吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.05,0:01:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.68,0:01:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道那家伙对你灌输了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.47,0:01:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个甚至会自我欺骗的恐怖分子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.35,0:01:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我认为他所说的也是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.90,0:01:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.48,0:01:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego只不过是我对过去的留恋罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.95,0:01:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果却连累了你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.77,0:01:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起

Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.31,0:03:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗曼诺夫·卡伦巴克
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.32,0:03:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗干净脖子等着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.62,0:03:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,召集部下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.40,0:03:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是发布非常事态宣言 不会引起不必要的抵抗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.88,0:03:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我的决定有意见么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.47,0:03:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能免受恐怖分子的威胁 还不是靠了我们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.15,0:03:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁管他们的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.22,0:04:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,24小时内在主要交通干道设置盘查岗哨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.84,0:04:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反恐独立部队采取4级戒备
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.92,0:04:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胆敢抵抗者一律扣押
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.72,0:04:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个月内彻底消灭恐怖组织

Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.87,0:04:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(253,233)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)}一個溫暖的家

Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.26,0:04:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉中途打断节目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.70,0:04:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面为您播报一则新闻
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.96,0:04:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为应对近来接连发生的恐怖事件
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.90,0:04:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP发布非常事态宣言
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.82,0:04:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁止一般市民夜间外出
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.15,0:04:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及回收以RB为首的无牌照车辆
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.97,0:04:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP直接向警方下达了这两条指示
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.27,0:04:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外东京都内的RB进口代理店
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.74,0:04:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到了无期禁贩令 并被要求提交购买者名单
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.75,0:04:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据SNN的独立调查
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.62,0:05:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都内已有数处设置了盘查岗哨 通行受到限制
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.23,0:05:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这一系列措施
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.38,0:05:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于未对日本政府进行事前联络 也未经规定手续
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.74,0:05:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荻野外交大臣似乎将对GGP表示强烈抗议
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.95,0:05:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前 对于GGP的非常事态宣言
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.95,0:05:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各地纷纷展开抗议 群情高涨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.37,0:05:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部分地区甚至与负责维持治安的警方发生冲突
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.97,0:05:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导致有人遭逮捕等 局面十分紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.17,0:05:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但另一方面 执政党内部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.16,0:05:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于GGP非常事态宣言是否合法 意见仍未统一
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.35,0:05:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政府能否贯彻强硬态度 将成为注目焦点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.91,0:05:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外边正为GGP的限制令闹得不可开交呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.88,0:05:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.42,0:05:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在楼上休息着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.17,0:05:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把胳膊伸出来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.24,0:05:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.81,0:06:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血滴在地板上伤脑筋的可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.26,0:06:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好严重
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.30,0:06:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭到轰炸 被烈火席卷的森林
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.49,0:06:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如同古旧的舞台背景一般
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.36,0:06:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成了失去现实感的风景
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.72,0:06:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起直扑脸颊的热浪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.64,0:06:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似有灵性的摇曳火光
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.69,0:06:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更让我目不转睛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.15,0:06:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么美丽的光景
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.73,0:06:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光的共鸣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.59,0:07:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.86,0:07:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.79,0:07:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我舍不得放下的...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.85,0:07:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.56,0:07:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能在这里久留
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.46,0:07:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有事的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.70,0:08:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狡兔三窟的政治家都用这里作避难所
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.48,0:08:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连检方高层都不知道这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.02,0:08:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连地图上都没...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.75,0:08:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好随时能出逃的准备
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.20,0:08:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自说自话把人家叫出来...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.98,0:08:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又要遁去哪里?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.47,0:08:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形拜托你照顾两三天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.11,0:08:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去做帮她逃脱的准备
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.51,0:08:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能的 现在这种局势
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.29,0:08:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都是盘查岗哨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.37,0:08:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.04,0:08:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.25,0:08:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别叫人替你担心啊

Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.12,0:08:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\pos(12,12)\fs15}{\1c&HB13421&\bord2\3c&HF6DDDA&\shad2\4c&H7D504A&}致热爱RB的人们\N\N\N{\1c&HE2E2E2&\bord2\3c&H292929&\shad1\4c&H2A2A2A&\fs17}GGP的镇压不可饶恕!\N\N{\1c&H0000EB&\bord1\3c&H494949&\shad1\4c&H1A1A1A&\fs19}誓师大会{\1c&HFFFFFF&\bord2\3c&H37DF40&\shad0\fs11}(来参加吧!)\N\N\N{\fs15\1c&HD7D7D7&\bord2\3c&H281346&\shad1\4c&H3F3F3F&}GGP应该停止没收RB这种蛮横做法!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.62,0:09:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\move(12,12,12,-110)\fs15}{\1c&HB13421&\bord2\3c&HF6DDDA&\shad2\4c&H7D504A&}致热爱RB的人们\N\N\N{\1c&HE2E2E2&\bord2\3c&H292929&\shad1\4c&H2A2A2A&\fs17}GGP的镇压不可饶恕!\N\N{\1c&H0000EB&\bord1\3c&H494949&\shad1\4c&H1A1A1A&\fs19}誓师大会{\1c&HFFFFFF&\bord2\3c&H37DF40&\shad0\fs11}(来参加吧!)\N\N\N{\fs15\1c&HD7D7D7&\bord2\3c&H281346&\shad1\4c&H3F3F3F&}GGP应该停止没收RB这种蛮横做法!

Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.11,0:09:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能再坐以待毙了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.15,0:09:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.88,0:09:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田学长
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.46,0:09:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经确认小琳平安无事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.51,0:09:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在和珠代学姊在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.09,0:09:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之 暂且可以安心了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.42,0:09:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么新情报的话我再邮件通知你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.02,0:09:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳 你没事么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.24,0:09:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.25,0:10:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上钩了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.26,0:10:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没问题吗? 这么悠哉悠哉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.51,0:10:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了确保重要的食物来源
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.38,0:10:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我派我们家的顾问律师去为你弟弟辩护了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.46,0:10:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.60,0:10:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道该怎么感谢您的大恩大德...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.77,0:10:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必摆出这种表情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.77,0:10:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了对了 去年在这里搞了一次合宿
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.71,0:10:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起钓鱼 闹得可欢了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.69,0:10:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河合那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.82,0:10:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏他还穿着钓鱼专用装似的夹克 一条都没钓到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.04,0:10:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚饭的材料也到手了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.34,0:10:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊为什么会坐上RB-Z呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.30,0:10:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家老头子是个老色鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.85,0:10:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情妇东一个西一个 根本不顾家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.58,0:10:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身处那种环境 有火无处发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.68,0:11:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然过生日时说什么都给买给我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.55,0:11:05.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就故意挑了不可能弄到手的RB-Z
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.26,0:11:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果却是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.36,0:11:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很气人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.09,0:11:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是位温柔的父亲呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.23,0:11:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.60,0:11:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然当初动机不正
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.54,0:11:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在RB-Z却成为了必不可缺的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.88,0:11:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像自己的分身一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.63,0:11:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.66,0:11:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谎言
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.44,0:11:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始就觉得Fuego好像自己的手脚一般
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.10,0:11:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够自由飞舞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.93,0:11:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以渐渐喜欢上了Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.42,0:11:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得像朋友一样亲密
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.99,0:11:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我发觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.13,0:11:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仅仅是把Fuego当成自己受伤双脚的替代品
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.90,0:11:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对Fuego的感情 也只是我编造出的谎言
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.32,0:12:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我下定决心 再也不会坐上RB了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.86,0:12:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃之后打算干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.21,0:12:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再回去练芭蕾么?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.92,0:12:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.66,0:12:15.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放不放弃是你的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.28,0:12:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还没分出胜负就退部的话 我这部长可饶不了你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.84,0:12:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能赢过我就批准你退部
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.63,0:12:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过手下败将我也不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.68,0:12:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.80,0:12:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但求坚司平安无事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.26,0:12:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,错过交给她的机会了吗

Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.61,0:12:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 受了不少照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.58,0:12:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入境也非常省力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.81,0:12:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前为止一切顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.19,0:13:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是这张护照对GGP也管用就万事大吉了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.92,0:13:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要逞强
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.47,0:13:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,局势随时都可能出现变化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.09,0:13:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这边也有力所不及的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.89,0:13:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白明白 别抱过高期望地等着就是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.24,0:13:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你人在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.43,0:13:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种非常时期 议员女儿失踪可不好笑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.40,0:13:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 打电话过去怕给你那边添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.28,0:13:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.39,0:13:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没发生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.02,0:13:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓天司郎也没在我这里出现过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.47,0:14:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天开始 GGP会展开地毯式反恐作战
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.36,0:14:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论身在何处都谈不上安全
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.89,0:14:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.47,0:14:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟老头子也联系一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.41,0:14:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看他那样 其实也在担心你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.18,0:14:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.74,0:14:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.67,0:14:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是片冈珠代小姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.12,0:14:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要让GGP干涉我们的内政!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.61,0:14:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让GGP滚出这个国家!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.86,0:14:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管抗议运动愈演愈烈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.83,0:14:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为防止被用于恐怖活动
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.70,0:14:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民间RB的暂时没收还是开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.23,0:14:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由此...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.48,0:14:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真过分
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.01,0:14:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟早GGP也会闯进这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.24,0:14:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被没收吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.30,0:15:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最坏的情况 部室也会被封锁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.01,0:15:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.58,0:15:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊回来看到之后肯定会伤心的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.63,0:15:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又能怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.84,0:15:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没戏没戏 对方可是军队加警察
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.07,0:15:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那份心的话 总会有办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.20,0:15:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 祥子姊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.33,0:15:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.28,0:15:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得不要再牵扯进去比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.09,0:15:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不想再看到有谁受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.93,0:15:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想琳是最支持这个想法的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.50,0:15:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会战斗的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.51,0:15:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生 缺了它可就一片空白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.87,0:15:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因为有了它 我才会和大家相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.03,0:15:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此重要的RB被贴上恐怖主义道具的标签
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.11,0:15:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,默默看着它被没收走 我可做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.26,0:15:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候就你最起劲
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.48,0:16:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次来得真快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.33,0:16:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 找我这行尸走肉有何贵干?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.12,0:16:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做笔交易
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.47,0:16:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.09,0:16:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.28,0:16:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从不主动联系父亲的不孝女
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.05,0:16:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来求我为你干什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.32,0:17:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.95,0:17:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.26,0:17:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.08,0:17:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在那里干些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.62,0:17:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能说 会给你添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.49,0:17:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.98,0:17:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,添点麻烦算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.83,0:17:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给父母添麻烦是孩子的义务
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.01,0:17:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来听听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.10,0:17:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是我办得到的事 我都会替你实现的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.12,0:17:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢你了 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.78,0:17:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RB-Z
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.70,0:18:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.34,0:18:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.25,0:18:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问 Fuego它...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.60,0:18:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我亲自解体之后报废了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.02,0:18:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来没被销毁呀 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.95,0:19:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.31,0:19:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了 打开吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.53,0:19:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我的军队吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.64,0:19:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}明天一早 全国各地将会发起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.92,0:19:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}反对GGP的系列反恐措施的大规模集会
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.68,0:20:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}警方将动员5000名警力维持治安
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.99,0:20:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只会让GGP找到滋事的借口
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.88,0:20:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}双方之间的冲突恐怕将不可避免
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.35,0:20:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}周边地区将禁止一般市民靠近
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.11,0:20:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从震灾慰灵广场到日向町
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.88,0:20:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在国道上进行示威游行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.59,0:20:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RB也会有10台左右参加
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.45,0:20:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好像是次重大事件呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.77,0:20:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.02,0:20:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有客人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.94,0:20:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...片冈珠代小姐派我送来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.32,0:20:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是油
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.58,0:20:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强 眼下根本弄不到这种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.83,0:20:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有信
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.31,0:21:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.57,0:21:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部室的混合燃料存货差不多也该用完了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.22,0:21:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部长大人送给可爱的部员们的慰问品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.44,0:21:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外送上失踪部员精神饱满的近照
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.43,0:21:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 还有这个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.90,0:21:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是托我转交的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.32,0:21:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长 快点快点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.40,0:21:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.42,0:21:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 看上去很有精神呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.98,0:21:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.83,0:21:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子姊


Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.99,0:23:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 大家好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.49,0:23:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快不记得前半部那机关枪式的对谈了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.30,0:23:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机关枪? 好老
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.44,0:23:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种代沟也是RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.79,0:23:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明世界闹得天翻地覆 我们的部室却是小巧玲珑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.01,0:23:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好比引擎模式和电池模式的差距啊


Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.78,0:23:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,245)\fs23\b1\bord0\shad1\1c&HFFFFFF&\4c&H6A6A6A&\4a&H3F&}{\fad(0,120)}戰爭之王


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.76,0:01:40.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:01:33.76,0:01:40.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.76,0:01:40.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:01:33.76,0:01:40.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.00,0:03:02.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.01,0:03:05.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.02,0:03:08.02,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.72,0:22:01.08,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.44,0:22:08.81,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.06,0:22:16.43,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.68,0:22:24.32,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.37,0:22:29.66,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.07,0:22:33.41,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.95,0:22:37.46,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.78,0:22:41.68,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.47,0:22:46.92,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.99,0:22:50.72,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.81,0:22:54.67,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.70,0:22:58.44,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.50,0:23:02.27,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.36,0:23:06.70,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.59,0:23:10.38,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.38,0:23:14.52,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:56.72,0:22:01.08,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.44,0:22:08.81,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.06,0:22:16.43,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:18.68,0:22:24.32,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.37,0:22:29.66,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.07,0:22:33.41,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:33.95,0:22:37.46,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:37.78,0:22:41.68,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.47,0:22:46.92,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:46.99,0:22:50.72,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.81,0:22:54.67,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:54.70,0:22:58.44,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.50,0:23:02.27,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.36,0:23:06.70,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:07.59,0:23:10.38,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.38,0:23:14.52,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.72,0:22:01.08,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.44,0:22:08.81,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.06,0:22:16.43,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.68,0:22:24.32,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.37,0:22:29.66,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.07,0:22:33.41,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.95,0:22:37.46,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.78,0:22:41.68,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.47,0:22:46.92,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.99,0:22:50.72,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.81,0:22:54.67,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.70,0:22:58.44,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.50,0:23:02.27,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.36,0:23:06.70,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.59,0:23:10.38,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.38,0:23:14.52,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:56.72,0:22:01.08,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.44,0:22:08.81,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.06,0:22:16.43,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:18.68,0:22:24.32,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.37,0:22:29.66,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.07,0:22:33.41,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:33.95,0:22:37.46,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:37.78,0:22:41.68,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.47,0:22:46.92,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:46.99,0:22:50.72,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.81,0:22:54.67,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:54.70,0:22:58.44,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.50,0:23:02.27,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.36,0:23:06.70,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:07.59,0:23:10.38,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.38,0:23:14.52,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.75,0:01:42.50,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.13,0:01:45.90,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.92,0:01:49.43,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.52,0:01:52.85,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.22,0:01:56.39,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.44,0:02:00.08,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.36,0:02:03.55,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.63,0:02:07.15,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.80,0:02:24.11,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.16,0:02:27.90,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.94,0:02:31.58,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.60,0:02:33.05,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.09,0:02:36.46,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.48,0:02:40.13,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.13,0:02:42.33,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.83,0:02:49.60,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this