[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 06
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.14,0:00:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}由于民众对恐怖袭击的不安情绪日益增长
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.52,0:00:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}在GGP指导下 反恐特种机动部队
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.81,0:00:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}通称“白Ride队”的引进法案高票通过
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.63,0:00:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}而其引进时机 目前还在进一步审议中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.14,0:00:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}既然恐怖分子已经投入了高机动性的RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.95,0:00:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}作为对抗手段 引进一举也是无可奈何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.57,0:00:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}现在我们必须要考虑的 是如何防范恐怖袭击于未然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.90,0:00:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么热的天 你还是那么起劲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.22,0:00:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该说过社团活动暂停一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.02,0:00:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能对我下命令的 只有将来被我选上的那个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.28,0:00:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白Ride在装备方面
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.38,0:00:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其说是警车 不如说更接近于兵器
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.85,0:01:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此不免让人产生警方军队化的忧虑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.42,0:01:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢您的评论
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.57,0:01:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我驾驶它的时候也做不出那种动作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.53,0:01:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她却做到了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.21,0:01:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法驾驭的东西 却被琳这个初学者驾驭了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.25,0:01:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么来头 那台Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.27,0:01:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必知道 这跟你们无关
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.85,0:01:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能无关
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.48,0:01:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是同属于RideBack部的伙伴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.47,0:01:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我有知情的权利

Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.55,0:03:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 依田小姐不来这边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.55,0:03:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次那个暴力团题材的截止日期就是今天哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.25,0:03:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没戏 我接下来要去虎之门采访
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.48,0:03:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,催稿什么的太麻烦了 切换成留言模式好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.59,0:03:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事务所也关了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.99,0:03:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.08,0:03:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我找到好东西了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.48,0:03:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.51,0:03:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神秘RideBack少女
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.58,0:03:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是和片冈珠代同一个大学的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.94,0:03:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名叫尾形琳 黑色长发
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.82,0:03:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定就是她
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.21,0:03:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑发?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.29,0:03:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,编辑来编辑去 那形象深深刻在我脑海里了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.77,0:03:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 今天截止那稿处理完之后联系大学问一下...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.16,0:03:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.33,0:03:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 还是在意那边

Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.20,0:04:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(253,233)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)}電光火石{\fnzhunyuan\fs30}Ride

Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.26,0:04:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果坚司还是没来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.25,0:04:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司 在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.46,0:04:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人味好重
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.11,0:04:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都是些啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.02,0:04:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RideBack...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.33,0:05:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司连这种书都看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.13,0:05:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 真不知道坚司那孩子在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.47,0:05:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游纪去世的时候 那孩子还只有10岁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.61,0:05:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没来得及完全脱离母亲 她就早早撒手人寰了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.90,0:05:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是这样 不来扫墓也太...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.37,0:05:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子嘛 很正常
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.73,0:05:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自那以来 已经是第六个夏天了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.17,0:05:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳在大学有没有自发做点什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.19,0:05:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃...没什么大不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.56,0:06:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是普普通通地参加了一个社团
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.43,0:06:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.75,0:06:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是琳找到了值得全身心投入的东西 那就太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.87,0:06:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宿舍生活过得怎样? 和祥子关系好吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.40,0:06:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 等一会儿还要见面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.29,0:06:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好强
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.07,0:06:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.22,0:06:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是哪来的啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.10,0:06:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是通过非法渠道从国外运进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.23,0:06:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也只知道这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.73,0:06:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的4台都白送我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.35,0:06:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换 去尽情大闹一场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.56,0:06:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砸几辆巡逻警车玩玩不坏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.69,0:06:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这个 赠品
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.92,0:06:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.06,0:06:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军方和BMA都在用的特制发烟筒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.76,0:07:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你们怎么用 只要求闹大一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.11,0:07:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是Gremlin的最新型号吗 好好的高档车...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.20,0:07:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有厂商标志
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.96,0:07:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出厂前就外流的?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.75,0:07:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长 看起来相当不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.03,0:07:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.56,0:07:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.33,0:07:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 教我怎么骑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.58,0:07:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Du...Dumont牌的EW手环
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.35,0:07:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 对 按原计划 4台
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.07,0:07:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚会让他们飙起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.87,0:07:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃走的3台中 有两台的驾驶员身份已得到确认
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.10,0:07:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中一人是Abraham·Ronstadt
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.16,0:07:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原美军特种部队出身
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.23,0:07:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一人本名不明
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.50,0:07:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南非国籍 法国佣兵部队出身
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.80,0:07:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一人不在资料库中 没能确认身份
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.10,0:08:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是此人刚发射完火箭弹后的画面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.07,0:08:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放大显示
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.02,0:08:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据骨骼解析 推定为欧系人种
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.16,0:08:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外 在重心不稳的RideBack上还能发射火箭弹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.53,0:08:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这种技术来看 很可能在军队中接受过高度训练
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.52,0:08:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次现场附近安插了这种技术高超的专家
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.74,0:08:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是BMA脱离一般的恐怖分子 迈向军队化的有力证据
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.46,0:08:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后策划出更大规模的恐怖袭击也不出奇
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.78,0:08:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以军事战术研究所的身份提议
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.00,0:08:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为摘除这类作战计划的萌芽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.22,0:08:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重点在主要城市和公安地区
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.01,0:08:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽快为警察厅引进RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.79,0:09:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉来晚了 错过了一班巴士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.70,0:09:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才该道歉呢 提了那么任性的要求
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.97,0:09:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就想久违地来这里看看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.84,0:09:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我想我懂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.19,0:09:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子 还记得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.28,0:09:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年学园祭的庆功宴之后 放焰火的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.27,0:09:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为闹得太厉害 巡警都发着火冲来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.14,0:09:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家哇地一声四散而逃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.26,0:10:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和祥子也走散了 那时好害怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.46,0:10:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在只听得到海浪声 漆黑一片的海岸上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.07,0:10:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“祥子 祥子”地边走边小声叫着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.81,0:10:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但见到祥子的时候真是太高兴了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.65,0:10:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心想“原来祥子也没回去 一直在找我呀”
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.82,0:10:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然彼此拥抱着哭了一场
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.22,0:10:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在想来 也算是一段美好的回忆...吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.00,0:10:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳 你虽然是芭蕾天才
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.25,0:10:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过完全没有演戏的才能呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.34,0:10:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用这么小心翼翼地找话题啦 感觉好古怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.71,0:10:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然一时受到了很大刺激 现在已经没事了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.47,0:10:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你又说不想去人群拥挤的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.73,0:10:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那时候我没有硬来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.92,0:10:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子说不定就不用遭受创伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.84,0:11:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 琳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.27,0:11:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.01,0:11:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕 回去的那班巴士差不多要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.93,0:11:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳 你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.69,0:11:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃...还有20分钟左右吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.11,0:11:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么不好意思啦 不跑来不及了 我先走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.28,0:11:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天再联系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.45,0:11:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到你了

Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.50,0:11:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真叫人陶醉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.95,0:11:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音不错么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.72,0:11:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就鼓足干劲大干一场啦!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.11,0:12:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是尾形琳小姐对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.33,0:12:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我吗 前几天到贵部叨扰过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.61,0:12:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能借用你一点时间吗 嘻嘻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.30,0:12:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我还有急事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.47,0:12:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.81,0:12:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴走族?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.95,0:12:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RideBack?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.35,0:12:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.06,0:13:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要搭车吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.61,0:13:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 多危险啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.66,0:13:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群臭小鬼!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.30,0:13:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有种就来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.79,0:13:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长 会不会太过火了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.55,0:13:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.73,0:13:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啥好怕的 尽情大闹好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.82,0:13:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前面的暴走车辆 立刻靠左停车
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.69,0:13:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁理你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.78,0:14:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活该
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.98,0:14:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把巡逻警车都...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.47,0:14:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前无法接听
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.16,0:14:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 那个好像是我弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.85,0:14:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊弟俩都这么顽皮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.86,0:14:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.68,0:14:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那帮家伙连警察都...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.29,0:15:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作辛苦了 出什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.54,0:15:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前面禁止通行 请绕道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.89,0:15:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我是记者 经过附近时正好看到有烟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.75,0:15:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能请你出示一下证件吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.20,0:15:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉 取材必须先经过许可
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.37,0:15:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.95,0:15:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.03,0:15:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 各位辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.39,0:15:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来能挖到意想之外的题材
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.01,0:15:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓紧了哦 会有点摇晃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.85,0:15:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴走族正从稻村町地区驶向47号填海人工地
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.02,0:16:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光靠损害器物和违反道路交通法 罪名不太够啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.03,0:16:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用管那么多 事后总有办法解决的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.67,0:16:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.39,0:16:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 应该是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.77,0:16:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼 GGP的小卒也敢摆这么大架子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.43,0:16:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功赶入封锁区域 两台原地待命
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.97,0:16:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上校 马上要开始实战试运行测试了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.19,0:16:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要来作战室观看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.75,0:16:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 我就在自己房间看诸位表现了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.89,0:16:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要报告上头吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.75,0:16:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 目前还没这个必要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.20,0:16:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是一介恐怖分子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.43,0:16:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到之后再杀死一遍就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.08,0:17:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不中用啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.32,0:17:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.99,0:17:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.42,0:17:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是RideBack吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.86,0:17:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的 尝尝这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.04,0:17:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混账 我们中圈套了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.78,0:17:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大事不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.73,0:17:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 再飙快点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.77,0:17:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学 学长
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.69,0:17:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.02,0:17:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白Ride?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.79,0:18:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没正式引进呢 怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.04,0:18:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.35,0:18:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投 投降
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.11,0:18:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是对付暴走族 未免也太过火了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.58,0:18:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.20,0:18:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.96,0:18:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饶了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.78,0:18:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不行啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.36,0:19:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.23,0:19:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.03,0:19:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.92,0:19:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么呢 快回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.00,0:19:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.81,0:19:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发动了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.13,0:20:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形琳? 为什么她会在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.99,0:20:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个搭乘者是突破GGP包围的恐怖分子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.06,0:20:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用手下留情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.86,0:20:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来会是一场精彩的测试呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.37,0:20:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.45,0:20:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.95,0:20:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又被躲过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.29,0:20:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.39,0:20:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太不现实了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.32,0:20:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老姊...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.17,0:20:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚司
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.33,0:21:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RideBack少女...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.73,0:21:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经被包围了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.06,0:21:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻关闭引擎 从RideBack上下来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.97,0:21:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重复一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.89,0:21:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻关闭引擎 从RideBack上下来

Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.25,0:23:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被抓啦 被抓啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.26,0:23:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 这可怎么办是好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.03,0:23:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.82,0:23:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对强大的国家权力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.66,0:23:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无力的我们要如何反抗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.16,0:23:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长坏掉了 完毕!

Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.63,0:23:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,245)\fs23\b1\bord0\shad1\1c&HFFFFFF&\4c&H6A6A6A&\4a&H3F&}{\fad(0,120)}罪與罰


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.76,0:01:49.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:01:42.76,0:01:49.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.76,0:01:49.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:01:42.76,0:01:49.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.00,0:03:11.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.01,0:03:14.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.02,0:03:17.02,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.64,0:22:00.00,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.36,0:22:07.73,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.98,0:22:15.35,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.60,0:22:23.24,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.29,0:22:28.58,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.99,0:22:32.33,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.87,0:22:36.38,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.70,0:22:40.60,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.39,0:22:45.84,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.91,0:22:49.64,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.73,0:22:53.59,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.62,0:22:57.36,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.42,0:23:01.19,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.28,0:23:05.62,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.51,0:23:09.30,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.30,0:23:13.44,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:55.64,0:22:00.00,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:02.36,0:22:07.73,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:10.98,0:22:15.35,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:17.60,0:22:23.24,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:25.29,0:22:28.58,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:28.99,0:22:32.33,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:32.87,0:22:36.38,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.70,0:22:40.60,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:41.39,0:22:45.84,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:45.91,0:22:49.64,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.73,0:22:53.59,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:53.62,0:22:57.36,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.42,0:23:01.19,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:01.28,0:23:05.62,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:06.51,0:23:09.30,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.30,0:23:13.44,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.64,0:22:00.00,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.36,0:22:07.73,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.98,0:22:15.35,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.60,0:22:23.24,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.29,0:22:28.58,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.99,0:22:32.33,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.87,0:22:36.38,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.70,0:22:40.60,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.39,0:22:45.84,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.91,0:22:49.64,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.73,0:22:53.59,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.62,0:22:57.36,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.42,0:23:01.19,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.28,0:23:05.62,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.51,0:23:09.30,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.30,0:23:13.44,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:55.64,0:22:00.00,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:02.36,0:22:07.73,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:10.98,0:22:15.35,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:17.60,0:22:23.24,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:25.29,0:22:28.58,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:28.99,0:22:32.33,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:32.87,0:22:36.38,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.70,0:22:40.60,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:41.39,0:22:45.84,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:45.91,0:22:49.64,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.73,0:22:53.59,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:53.62,0:22:57.36,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.42,0:23:01.19,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:01.28,0:23:05.62,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:06.51,0:23:09.30,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.30,0:23:13.44,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.75,0:01:51.50,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.13,0:01:54.90,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.92,0:01:58.43,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.52,0:02:01.85,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.22,0:02:05.39,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.44,0:02:09.08,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.36,0:02:12.55,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.63,0:02:16.15,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.80,0:02:33.11,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.16,0:02:36.90,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.94,0:02:40.58,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.60,0:02:42.05,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.09,0:02:45.46,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.48,0:02:49.13,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.13,0:02:51.33,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.83,0:02:58.60,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this
