[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 10
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.84,0:00:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然与亚利桑那战役当时 罗曼诺夫的部下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.38,0:00:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伯特上等兵成功会了面
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.56,0:00:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你所见 几乎没能跟他谈上点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.86,0:00:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾 不过他当不了证人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.77,0:00:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说有你那位强硬派老爹的通行证
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.24,0:00:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能这么容易见到的理由就是这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.11,0:00:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天起 在他来这里之前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.20,0:00:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会调查一下他在HESNER公司工作时的情报
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.89,0:00:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再联系
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.95,0:00:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个幌子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.14,0:00:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 但她没受任何妨碍 平安无事这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.45,0:00:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从中也可以看出一点名堂
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.61,0:00:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没留下任何能作为证据的东西——对方有这种自信
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.39,0:00:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许还有一种可能——罗曼诺夫阵营并非坚如磐石

Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.02,0:02:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 新来的 下一站就下车
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.33,0:02:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是

Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.73,0:02:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(419,233)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)}戰爭之王

Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.80,0:03:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原创的开放式系统互联吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.80,0:03:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,326)\fs16\bord1\shad0\fsp2\fscy95}O S I
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.64,0:03:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有能逃去的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.01,0:03:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈仓先生替我们准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.42,0:03:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说这里似乎也已经不再安全了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.18,0:03:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去向警察自首
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.70,0:03:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察……不 GGP值得你相信吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.02,0:03:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不信
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.73,0:03:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哥、我爸也都讨厌GGP
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.11,0:03:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不会把你交给他们的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.61,0:03:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照预定 进行前往和平纪念公园的示威游行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.33,0:04:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搭乘RB的人 请先填好申请书
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.55,0:04:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,途中没有休息 方便问题请自行解决
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.68,0:04:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉不觉得整体感觉有点兴奋过头了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.90,0:04:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是没办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.93,0:04:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被没收RB或是被逮捕的人还是少数
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.59,0:04:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了阻止这种事态 今天才会聚集这么多人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.54,0:04:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.19,0:04:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油宣传RB和琳姊的清白
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.40,0:04:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想加油请自便 Balon被没收的话要你来赔哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.14,0:04:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要勉强 我们的宗旨是安全第一
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.68,0:04:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.57,0:04:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.16,0:04:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的护身符
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.80,0:04:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子姊给我的 琳姊的舞台照
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.57,0:04:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,示威游行要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.28,0:04:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加者请到这里来集合
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.18,0:04:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车厢里装的什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.52,0:04:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美术品
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.89,0:04:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通行证?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.14,0:04:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.12,0:05:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的安全吗 那张通行证
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.14,0:05:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.38,0:05:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 把后面打开
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.35,0:05:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,磨蹭什么 动作快点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.36,0:05:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.80,0:05:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 已经不用了 确认完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.76,0:05:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.18,0:05:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是片冈南风 人脉无敌啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.03,0:05:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.33,0:05:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有事吗 走这种大街
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.44,0:05:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏树就藏森林里 藏人就藏市镇里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.98,0:05:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 你也想见大家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.70,0:05:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.08,0:05:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天好像参加了抗议GGP的示威游行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.78,0:05:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经约好结束之后见面了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.14,0:05:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子也会来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.51,0:06:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,示威游行没参加 不过菱田说之后会来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.78,0:06:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有给你的留言
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.60,0:06:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.32,0:06:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊 真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.77,0:06:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是琳姊出了什么事 我真不知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.74,0:06:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 祥子也来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.34,0:06:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳 你还好吗 我很好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.08,0:06:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然担心了很久 不过看到录像之后就松了口气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.83,0:06:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点回来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.30,0:06:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要用邮件发送 就快超容量了 赶快
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.56,0:06:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经能骑得很好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.74,0:06:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次想跟琳姊一起ride
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.55,0:06:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于说出来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.15,0:06:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太长啦 给我适可而...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.51,0:06:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢大家...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.44,0:06:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BMA的下个目标
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.38,0:06:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预计会是政府机关 或是车站等主要交通设施
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.09,0:06:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然主要交通干道的戒严已经完成
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.87,0:06:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假定他们已经入侵到城市内部
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.78,0:07:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已按此可能向警察发出指示 展开地毯式作战
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.64,0:07:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外 在执政党议员片冈南风周围
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.40,0:07:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认到有反GGP活动的迹象
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.27,0:07:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然已经依据反恐治安维持法 发出了逮捕申请...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.73,0:07:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 罗曼诺夫上校
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.87,0:07:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南风是片冈龙之介的亲生父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.62,0:07:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你处置
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.51,0:07:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.17,0:07:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军方内部的系统是以完全独立的网络构成的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.57,0:07:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能从外部入侵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.76,0:07:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不让敌方的识别系统瘫痪 这次作战会失败的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.74,0:07:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你找到点什么了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.98,0:07:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在哈佛组建的拥有独特传输协议的网络
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.29,0:07:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要黑掉其系统近乎不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.18,0:07:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但暂时让其停止还是可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.44,0:08:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伪装成低使用频率的机器ID
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.45,0:08:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向网络内部慢慢注入能增加通信量的封包
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.36,0:08:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很花时间
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.56,0:08:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能告诉我吗 这次作战的真正目的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.98,0:08:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是约定好了么 闭上嘴一切听我指挥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.89,0:08:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看在从前的交情上 就告诉你好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.86,0:08:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次作战的确是声东击西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.52,0:08:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不打算尽力战斗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.53,0:08:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我战斗的时候总是全力的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.75,0:08:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但正如你所说 不少人还有其他目的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.48,0:08:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的目的我想我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.11,0:08:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙的背叛 我也并没有原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.06,0:08:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在烈火熊熊的ICBM基地里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.78,0:08:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓要对设计害我的人复仇
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.91,0:08:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会被无耻小人 活活烧死在那种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.91,0:08:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那家伙从他拚命弄到手的地位上拽下来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.54,0:09:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他饱尝绝望之后再杀死他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.99,0:09:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会造出Fuego
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.99,0:09:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了尾形琳吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.89,0:09:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.80,0:09:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是抛弃战场的男人 一点丑陋的留恋罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.43,0:09:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.13,0:09:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她已经发觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.24,0:09:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被枪林弹雨和火焰包围时的极限紧张感
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.17,0:09:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己在那一刻才能发挥出的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.66,0:09:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只是一个普通的18岁少女 不需要那种才能
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.52,0:09:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一天 要是那里没发生恐怖袭击的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.72,0:09:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我没突破GGP的包围的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.31,0:09:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已吃够RB的苦头了?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.72,0:09:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.01,0:09:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我也能像珠代学姊一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.93,0:09:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以普通的方式面对RB就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.74,0:10:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的那座 是国立第三剧场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.54,0:10:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的归宿是那种地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.62,0:10:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经触手难及了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.20,0:10:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呀 太容易放弃了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.65,0:10:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我也一样 不管什么不拿第一名就不罢休
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.94,0:10:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不喜欢轻易放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.23,0:10:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你留在Fuego上的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.56,0:10:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会逼你去骑RB
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.01,0:10:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但EW手环是作为部员的象征交给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.70,0:10:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你还是我们部的一份子 我就不准你乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.37,0:10:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珠代学姊...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.19,0:10:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP从这个国家滚出去!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.46,0:10:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚出去!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.90,0:10:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这样的人数 警察也不敢轻易动武吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.03,0:10:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里 感觉还好吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.51,0:10:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经冷静多了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.46,0:10:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临场发挥能力意外得好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.20,0:10:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.17,0:10:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是国立第三剧场
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.26,0:10:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊以前演出过的舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.37,0:11:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.62,0:11:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实相比开着Ride起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.77,0:11:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更想看的是在舞台上跳舞的琳姊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.75,0:11:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过说出口的话 会被琳姊讨厌的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.19,0:11:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.92,0:11:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不能跳舞之后 最痛苦的是琳姊自己呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.39,0:11:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我没看她跳过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.24,0:11:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过能让Fuego跳舞 我想是因为练过芭蕾的关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.27,0:11:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反过来说 开着Fuego跳舞 对芭蕾应该也有帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.30,0:11:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳的话 再回去跳芭蕾肯定也会成功的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.03,0:11:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 感觉那家伙无论干什么都会成功
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.86,0:11:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之所以会放弃 或许只是因为小琳还没整理好心情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.37,0:11:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候能直言相劝 才是真正的朋友的表现吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.64,0:11:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子和凉里都是小琳的朋友吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.00,0:11:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对对 有所顾虑的话就还算不上真正的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.01,0:11:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看这家伙 明明是我学弟 也敢对我直言不讳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.25,0:12:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要当琳姊的朋友 我还没做好心理准备...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.27,0:12:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友还需要什么心理准备嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.84,0:12:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点没错 在我们看来已经是交情很好的朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.02,0:12:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 莫非你就是RB少女?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.38,0:12:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.15,0:12:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.60,0:12:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪够得上...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.17,0:12:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很早就开始崇拜你了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.01,0:12:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.57,0:12:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然没错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.70,0:12:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 神秘RB少女在这里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.28,0:12:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.13,0:12:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗 是哪个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.88,0:12:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.30,0:12:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,善后就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.24,0:12:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走 尾形
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.35,0:12:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在刚才 执政党最大派系的领袖
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.94,0:12:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈南风议员 似乎遭到了逮捕
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.38,0:12:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈南风议员被作为反GGP政府恐怖活动的支持者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.13,0:12:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现于疗养中的医院遭到拘禁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.59,0:13:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换言之 就算对上经过高度训练的优秀Rider
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.16,0:13:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这台Grimoire的战斗能力也丝毫不会逊色
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.21,0:13:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝佳的对手很快就会自己送上门来

Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.88,0:13:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白Ride
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.00,0:13:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,示威游行还没结束
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.79,0:13:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 好戏还在后头呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.62,0:13:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们再加把劲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.29,0:13:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说是传说中的RB少女复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.31,0:13:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突破GGP包围的恐怖分子?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.39,0:13:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会很危险吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.83,0:13:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样娇小的女孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.88,0:14:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 变得那么引人注目了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.53,0:14:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多要到约好的时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.00,0:14:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}由于要进行反恐例行车检 将在本站停靠5分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.67,0:14:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}抱歉给各位乘客增添诸多麻烦 还请稍等片刻
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.65,0:14:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真急人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.76,0:14:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就能见到大家了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.11,0:14:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 真的不用去吗 您父亲在的医院
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.39,0:14:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去帮忙监视示威游行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.96,0:14:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片冈先生 部长叫你过去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.65,0:14:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有RB少女在!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.16,0:14:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 没什么好怕的!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.08,0:14:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错没错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.22,0:14:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.16,0:14:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RB少女万岁!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.68,0:14:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹 差不多回来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.70,0:15:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}RB少女 RB少女 RB少女...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.17,0:14:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 她根本听不见
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.70,0:14:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 菱田 看那边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.51,0:14:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白Ride...GGP也来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.75,0:15:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.67,0:15:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据情报称 通缉中的尾形琳就乘着RB在示威人群中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.82,0:15:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.74,0:15:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指挥车通知各车
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.42,0:15:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指名通缉犯就潜伏在示威人群中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.86,0:15:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑着RB 有逃跑、抵抗的可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.30,0:15:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以等级四待机
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.71,0:15:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.44,0:15:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有行动了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.64,0:15:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那帮家伙也太猖狂了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.15,0:15:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP从这个国家滚出去!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.54,0:15:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会让你们胡作非为啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.56,0:15:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么呢 快回去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.75,0:15:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是先溜为妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.55,0:15:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.62,0:15:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}例行检查结束 即将开车
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.20,0:15:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲人全是嫌疑犯 你也真够辛苦的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.85,0:15:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.33,0:15:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探查到罗曼诺夫上校的过去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.98,0:16:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GGP正在渐渐老朽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.52,0:16:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热爱战争的旧体制的代表人物就是他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.80,0:16:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.38,0:16:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲的事就交给我去办好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.21,0:16:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换 希望你助我一臂之力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.66,0:16:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,揭发HESNER公司 当然只能靠你们自己的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.71,0:16:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自视太高了 以为这样我就会屈服于你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.02,0:16:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是交易 新秩序的体现需要一点戏剧性因素
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.61,0:16:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,登上舞台的人 自然需要角色和报酬
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.09,0:16:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有那个资格
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.00,0:16:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特制警棍
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.24,0:16:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大事不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.80,0:16:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田 想想办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.41,0:16:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.36,0:16:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹 快离开那里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.44,0:16:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菱田学长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.63,0:16:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往公园外去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.75,0:17:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1号车 目标逃上了公路
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.23,0:17:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以违反道路交通法逮住她
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.36,0:17:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.88,0:17:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊 还有珠代学姊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.87,0:17:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.08,0:17:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.02,0:17:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1号车直追 2号车迂回去断她后路
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.29,0:17:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.50,0:17:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.20,0:17:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹 快停下!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.00,0:17:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往这边来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.81,0:17:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Balon?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.03,0:17:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.98,0:17:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被追赶着?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.20,0:18:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被包抄了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.62,0:18:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 快停车
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.68,0:18:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊 那个啊 请重新开始跳舞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.53,0:18:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好想看 琳姊的舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.84,0:18:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么 凉里妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.34,0:18:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请看着 琳姊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.73,0:18:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不在的那段时间里 我特训的成果
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.61,0:18:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会“飞”的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.09,0:18:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.01,0:19:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹...怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.01,0:19:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.47,0:19:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.35,0:19:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.15,0:20:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.66,0:20:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.96,0:20:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.45,0:20:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再联系
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.31,0:21:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹她...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.93,0:21:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.90,0:21:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不是 要不是你造出了这种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.86,0:21:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹她...凉里妹妹她...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.49,0:21:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉里妹妹她...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.73,0:21:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾形
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.35,0:21:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留恋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.92,0:21:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我和你的留恋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.88,0:21:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是留恋杀了凉里妹妹


Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.15,0:23:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,245)\fs23\b1\bord0\shad1\1c&HFFFFFF&\4c&H6A6A6A&\4a&H3F&}{\fad(0,120)}陰有時有雨


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.81,0:01:08.63,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:01:01.81,0:01:08.63,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.81,0:01:08.63,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:01:01.81,0:01:08.63,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.05,0:02:30.05,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.06,0:02:33.06,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.07,0:02:36.07,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.13,0:22:01.49,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.85,0:22:09.22,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.47,0:22:16.84,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.09,0:22:24.73,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.78,0:22:30.07,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.48,0:22:33.82,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.36,0:22:37.87,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.19,0:22:42.09,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.88,0:22:47.33,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.40,0:22:51.13,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.22,0:22:55.08,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.11,0:22:58.85,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.91,0:23:02.68,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.77,0:23:07.11,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.00,0:23:10.79,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.79,0:23:14.93,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:57.13,0:22:01.49,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.85,0:22:09.22,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.47,0:22:16.84,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:19.09,0:22:24.73,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.78,0:22:30.07,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.48,0:22:33.82,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:34.36,0:22:37.87,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:38.19,0:22:42.09,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.88,0:22:47.33,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.40,0:22:51.13,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.22,0:22:55.08,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.11,0:22:58.85,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.91,0:23:02.68,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.77,0:23:07.11,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:08.00,0:23:10.79,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.79,0:23:14.93,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.13,0:22:01.49,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.85,0:22:09.22,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.47,0:22:16.84,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.09,0:22:24.73,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.78,0:22:30.07,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.48,0:22:33.82,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.36,0:22:37.87,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.19,0:22:42.09,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.88,0:22:47.33,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.40,0:22:51.13,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.22,0:22:55.08,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.11,0:22:58.85,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.91,0:23:02.68,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.77,0:23:07.11,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.00,0:23:10.79,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.79,0:23:14.93,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:57.13,0:22:01.49,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:03.85,0:22:09.22,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.47,0:22:16.84,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:19.09,0:22:24.73,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.78,0:22:30.07,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.48,0:22:33.82,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:34.36,0:22:37.87,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:38.19,0:22:42.09,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.88,0:22:47.33,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.40,0:22:51.13,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.22,0:22:55.08,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.11,0:22:58.85,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.91,0:23:02.68,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.77,0:23:07.11,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:08.00,0:23:10.79,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.79,0:23:14.93,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.80,0:01:10.55,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.18,0:01:13.95,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.97,0:01:17.48,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.57,0:01:20.90,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.27,0:01:24.44,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.49,0:01:28.13,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.41,0:01:31.60,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.68,0:01:35.20,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.85,0:01:52.16,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.21,0:01:55.95,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.99,0:01:59.63,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.65,0:02:01.10,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.14,0:02:04.51,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.53,0:02:08.18,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.18,0:02:10.38,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.88,0:02:17.65,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this