[Script Info]
Title:RIDEBACK BDrip 04
Original Script:X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== RIDEBACK 鐵馬出夢來/背騎少女 BDRiP 作品ASS字幕訊息 ===
;
;字幕版本使用X2字幕組TV字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝
;參與過的製作人員
;翻譯：眠森
;時間/後期：llnite
;BDrip：tct66
;看片監督：Zhudada
;
Style: Default,ZhunYuan,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H004A4A4A,&H00060685,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,7,1
Style: staff,華康新綜藝體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF6A3853,&H00383018,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,97,0,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,15,1
Style: logo,華康新綜藝體,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,1,0,0,100,98,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_jp,DFMincho-UB,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,1
Style: ed_ch,DFNMingXBold-B5,18,&H00EFEFEF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H001A1A1A,1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,3,9,30,30,10,1
Style: op_eng,AvQest,27,&H0000FFEB,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,10,6,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.65,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}各位观众早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.10,0:00:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}大地震至今已有6个年头  在今天这个特殊的日子里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.98,0:00:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}各地都将举行安魂祭...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.75,0:00:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  连杆都有裂纹了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.96,0:00:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下没救了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.65,0:00:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没送去店里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.50,0:00:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.67,0:00:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引擎要大修  已经没那么多经费啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.79,0:00:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这台机体又是我自己组装的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.53,0:00:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能的话我还是想自力修好它  不过...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.18,0:00:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}接下来是政经新闻
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.09,0:00:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}GGP维和部队的最高负责人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.18,0:00:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}罗曼诺夫·卡伦巴克上校的就任仪式将于...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.67,0:00:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  把桌上东西收拾一下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.69,0:00:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.58,0:00:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天有社团活动  我怕自己忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.65,0:00:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天明明是星期天呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.01,0:00:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次的大赛中我好像找到一点感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.74,0:00:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RideBack的驾驶心得
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.83,0:00:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引发出它的真正力量的窍门
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.59,0:00:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说呀  琳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.98,0:01:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得今天是什么日子吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.07,0:01:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是车站商厦的厂家直销大减价
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.11,0:01:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我全忘在脑后了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.89,0:01:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明约好一起去的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.14,0:01:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啦  好搭档  别放心上
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.30,0:01:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就我一个人粗粗看下好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.67,0:01:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我反而感到高兴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.53,0:01:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能有东西让琳这么痴迷
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.53,0:01:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔  这个超好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.25,0:01:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.41,0:01:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是RideBack吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.77,0:01:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.23,0:01:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs20\fad(0,200)}...警方将要引进的特种车  通称“白Ride”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.23,0:01:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\pos(12,12)\fs16\bord0\4c&H4A4A4A&\i1\fad(0,200)}译注: 即警用(白色涂装)RideBack\N参见ja.wikipedia.org/wiki/白バイ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.98,0:01:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}首次对媒体公开

Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.50,0:03:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么动静啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.47,0:03:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是来了个让人颇感兴趣的新人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.21,0:03:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到他装出一副漠不关心的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.98,0:03:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能打听一下他的过去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.74,0:03:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,办不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.73,0:03:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前试探性地问了句“去过海外吗”
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.12,0:03:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他狠狠瞪了一眼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.85,0:03:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.19,0:03:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再联系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.04,0:03:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  难得人家假日里还特地跑来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.49,0:03:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在抱歉  今天社团活动停一次
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.50,0:03:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.51,0:03:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过份了  发条短信也好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.80,0:03:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临时决定把Balon和Fuego送去市区的店家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.64,0:03:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问...Fuego哪里坏了么?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.69,0:03:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  只是顺便一起维护一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.64,0:03:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把Fuego留下吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.21,0:03:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.30,0:03:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方便的话  能载我去市区么?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.74,0:04:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊  有什么事要办吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.83,0:04:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子去逛街了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.42,0:04:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也一起去

Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.56,0:04:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(307,233)}{\fn華康中黑體\bord0\shad0\b1\fsp0\1c&H646466&\1a&H1F&}{\fad(0,330)}祥子{\fnzhunyuan}、{\fn華康中黑體}千鈞一發之際

Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.22,0:04:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  又有空来了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.69,0:04:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没勉强自己吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.66,0:04:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.13,0:04:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到附近之后再电话联系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.12,0:04:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是接替“白Bike”的“白Ride”吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.64,0:04:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好微妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.20,0:04:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音太大啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.83,0:04:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真货会如约亮相吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.50,0:04:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门口那台模型太不够看了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.36,0:04:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依田小姐  都说声音太大了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.98,0:04:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让各位久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.07,0:04:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,HESNER公司副总裁主持的联合记者招待会
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.70,0:04:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正式开始
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.66,0:04:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盘查引起的堵车?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.12,0:04:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非GGP司令的就任仪式就是今天吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.04,0:04:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}这里是GGP本部的外面
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.44,0:05:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}为参加仪式  罗曼诺夫新司令即将出发
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.06,0:05:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}前往会场的路线上一路戒备森严
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.50,0:05:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堵车?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.57,0:05:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  说不定还要等上30分钟左右
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.85,0:05:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.19,0:05:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在正好在电视塔下面
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.82,0:05:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在大厅的咖啡馆等你好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.71,0:05:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要来点甜甜圈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.51,0:05:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等我啦  再说凉里妹妹也要来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.63,0:05:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法  就拿红茶消磨时间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.24,0:05:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.41,0:06:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  祥子  怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.49,0:06:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都看不见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.25,0:06:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.12,0:06:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子  喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.15,0:06:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  那是啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.61,0:06:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,市区...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.82,0:06:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里不是祥子姊在的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.23,0:06:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家请保持镇定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.68,0:06:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请遵照工作人员的指示行动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.55,0:06:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍下来了?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.63,0:06:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自然
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.79,0:06:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个...不是在拍电影吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.94,0:06:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.47,0:07:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况如何
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.40,0:07:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一级戒备  部署完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.47,0:07:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大楼发生爆炸  外加周围散布有大量烟雾弹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.21,0:07:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生地的情报整理尚未完成
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.32,0:07:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才犯罪声明在网上发布了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.69,0:07:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.20,0:07:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去安抚一下大发雷霆的司令大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.65,0:07:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊  菱田
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.13,0:07:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能怎么办  堵车堵得这么厉害...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.17,0:07:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.61,0:07:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}本日下午2点02分
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.45,0:07:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}电视塔37层的展望台发生爆炸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.12,0:07:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}人质的人数目前还不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.47,0:07:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}但据称大楼内被武装恐怖分子占领
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.09,0:07:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}我现在身处市区边缘
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.92,0:07:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}市内若干处发出的黄色烟雾将整个市区
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.64,0:07:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}经确认  反GGP组织
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.22,0:07:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}自称“BMA”的恐怖组织网站上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.27,0:07:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}已经发表了犯罪声明
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.37,0:07:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}该组织...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.68,0:08:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们无法容忍双手沾满鲜血的刽子手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.66,0:08:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗曼诺夫·卡伦巴克上校的此次就任
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.08,0:08:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为释放人质的交换条件
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.12,0:08:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要求与上校公开辩论
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.21,0:08:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能坐视这个屠夫手掌大权
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.82,0:08:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}内阁厅方才已向警方、GGP军及其维和部队
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.70,0:08:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}发出了反恐维和行动的请求
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.06,0:08:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}目前市区禁止一般车辆进入
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.98,0:08:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  还是打不通
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.45,0:08:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}...这里是○○医院
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.06,0:08:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}大量被爆炸冲击波吹倒而受伤者被送入该院
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.22,0:08:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}详细情况目前尚不明了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.24,0:08:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}但电视塔中心区域似乎损伤较重
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.06,0:08:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}受伤人数预计也将继续增加
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.50,0:08:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.58,0:08:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.10,0:08:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.47,0:08:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开Fuego去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.59,0:08:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.03,0:08:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能体会你的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.33,0:08:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在道路也被封锁了...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.60,0:09:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.66,0:09:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在那边还有恐怖分子在到处转呢  太危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.25,0:09:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别乱来啊  尾形
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.81,0:09:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琳  STOP
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.14,0:09:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救完祥子马上就回来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.74,0:09:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊  这个戴上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.91,0:09:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是去了啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.71,0:09:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定要平安无事啊

Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.21,0:10:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是杀人凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.25,0:10:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要老老实实听从我们的指示  就不会受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.73,0:10:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是杀人凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.93,0:10:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要老老实实听从我们的指示  就不会受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.42,0:10:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快 通知警察
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.60,0:10:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.95,0:10:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}目前以电视塔为中心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.04,0:10:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}半径2km范围内被设为封锁区域
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.80,0:10:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}GGP军及维和部队的反恐怖包围网正在形成中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.24,0:10:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}各位居民请尽快撤离封锁区域避难
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.99,0:10:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}重复一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.27,0:10:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}被列入危险区域的是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.16,0:10:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}西24区
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.72,0:10:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}25区
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.01,0:10:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}26区
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.32,0:10:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}37区
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.63,0:11:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}51区
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.43,0:11:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得这群恐怖分子很蠢吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.67,0:11:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的就任之日出这种问题  实在抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.99,0:11:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我非得对人质出手相救不可啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.56,0:11:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明恐怖分子越是活跃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.06,0:11:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白Ride的引进就越是顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.64,0:11:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的工作也越发轻松
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.53,0:11:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺像模像样的战争啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.11,0:11:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依田小姐  我们去避难吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.55,0:11:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有记者之魂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.75,0:11:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还不想为它赌上性命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.30,0:11:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  接通啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.18,0:12:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.94,0:12:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  祥子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.42,0:12:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  琳  再等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.49,0:12:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  琳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.39,0:12:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.27,0:12:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在在哪?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.75,0:12:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚到车站  这就去救你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.81,0:12:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大厅二楼的最深部
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.49,0:12:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  不要过来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.23,0:12:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有荷枪实弹的...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.12,0:13:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子  喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.85,0:13:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.25,0:13:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.55,0:13:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,RideBack?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.20,0:13:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平民禁止入内  立刻回去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.85,0:13:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的朋友被关在大楼里了  刚才电话里...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.52,0:13:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.49,0:13:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会救她出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.94,0:13:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之现在先离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.83,0:13:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.86,0:13:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.81,0:13:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  站住!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.46,0:13:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,E-15呼叫总部
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.28,0:13:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一台RideBack无视避难命令
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.45,0:13:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲进了封锁中的大楼!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.47,0:13:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的眼睛...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.49,0:14:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.57,0:14:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.89,0:14:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.34,0:14:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.01,0:14:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.99,0:14:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.22,0:14:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.92,0:14:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子  你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.05,0:14:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  你终于来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.99,0:14:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.39,0:14:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉来晚了  我们快从这里出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.50,0:14:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.61,0:14:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子  坐我后面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.70,0:14:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准动
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.83,0:14:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,市面上的普通RideBack?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.93,0:14:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关掉引擎下车来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.83,0:15:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么长时间究竟藏在哪里...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.26,0:15:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子  抓紧我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.16,0:15:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发什么呆  快开枪!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.72,0:15:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}这里是E-24分区
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.17,0:15:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}一台疑似恐怖分子的可疑车辆刚向大桥方向驶去了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.63,0:15:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}是红色的RideBack
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.24,0:15:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经开始了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.35,0:15:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无视避难警告会不会不太妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.26,0:15:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天上是不会掉下独家新闻来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.90,0:15:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  难道要去楼顶吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.63,0:15:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.96,0:16:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.46,0:16:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}就在刚才  GGP特种部队突入了大楼之中
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.99,0:16:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}封锁地点的记者佐佐木小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.56,0:16:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.43,0:16:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}这里是中心区域2km开外的南大桥桥畔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.90,0:16:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}通往市内的道路已被GGP全数封锁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.44,0:16:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}目前无法进入
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.44,0:16:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}电视塔一带被烟雾笼罩 无法得知其中状况
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.21,0:16:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊  求求您
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.97,0:16:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  我们被错认成恐怖分子了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.32,0:16:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可思议
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.54,0:16:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和Fuego这么亲密无间的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.46,0:16:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像头一回乘它的那次一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.54,0:16:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像是自己手脚的延伸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.80,0:17:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依田小姐  看那边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.00,0:17:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  后面
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.79,0:18:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}南大桥处的情况出现变化了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.69,0:18:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}一台似是RideBack的物体
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.98,0:18:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}和直升机一同自市内来到了大桥上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.60,0:18:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}从这里无法清晰辨认
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.46,0:18:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}但很有可能是逃出来的恐怖分子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.19,0:18:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳  下车吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.43,0:18:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要好好解释  误会一定能解开的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.96,0:18:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  琳
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.66,0:18:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次不“飞”了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.71,0:18:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.46,0:18:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子  绝对不要松手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.27,0:19:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了  这光是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.58,0:19:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}直升机...直升机被击坠了!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.21,0:19:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}RideBack从火焰中一跃而出
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.45,0:19:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}高高飞舞在半空
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.72,0:19:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳姊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.66,0:19:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么啊  那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.67,0:20:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子  已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.85,0:20:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祥子?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.89,0:20:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Fuego  Type-L么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.77,0:20:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被它选中了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.32,0:20:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的调制
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.31,0:20:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是会挑选主人的特殊设置
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.79,0:20:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.80,0:20:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.46,0:20:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}本日下午2点02分发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.92,0:20:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}电视塔大规模恐怖事件
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.99,0:20:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}于下午4点30分  在GGP军及维和部队的突入行动下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.39,0:20:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}击毙五名疑似主谋的恐怖分子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.43,0:20:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}由于以最小损害阻止了该起恐怖活动
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.64,0:21:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}政府向GGP表示了感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.89,0:21:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}针对佐世保、小仓等一系列BMA的恐怖活动
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.89,0:21:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}今天就任的罗曼诺夫上校
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.23,0:21:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}一方面向死者表示哀悼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.53,0:21:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}另一方面宣言  今后对此类恐怖活动将绝不屈服
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.80,0:21:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs20\fad(0,200)}坚持剿灭到底
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.23,0:21:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.55,0:21:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要走  琳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.35,0:21:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那道光...

Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.89,0:23:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大事不好  大事不好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.20,0:23:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镇定点  菱田
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.69,0:23:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可又是爆炸又是恐怖分子的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.20,0:23:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还突破了GGP的包围网
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.49,0:23:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧  没你这个配角的事


Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.03,0:23:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,245)\fs23\b1\bord0\shad1\1c&HFFFFFF&\4c&H6A6A6A&\4a&H3F&}{\fad(0,120)}神秘RideBack少女


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.76,0:01:46.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}X2
Dialogue: 1,0:01:39.76,0:01:46.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,284)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fs49\fsp3\fscx115\fscy85}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}X2
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.76,0:01:46.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord14\3c&HCECECE&\shad8}字幕組
Dialogue: 1,0:01:39.76,0:01:46.58,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,280)\fn華康新綜藝體}{\fad(0,1620)}{\fscy85\fsp1}{\bord8\3c&H090ACF&}字幕組


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Staff↓

Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.00,0:03:08.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}本片由X2字幕組贊助播出 僅供交流試看 有愛君請支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.01,0:03:11.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}翻校：眠森   時間&RMVB後期：LLNITE
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.02,0:03:14.02,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn華康新綜藝體\fad(500,500)}BDrip：TCT66   看片監督：ZHUDADA


Comment: 0,0:00:00.17,0:00:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓

Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.28,0:22:01.64,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.00,0:22:09.37,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.62,0:22:16.99,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.24,0:22:24.88,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.93,0:22:30.22,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.63,0:22:33.97,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.51,0:22:38.02,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.34,0:22:42.24,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.03,0:22:47.48,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.55,0:22:51.28,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.37,0:22:55.23,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.26,0:22:59.00,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.06,0:23:02.83,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.92,0:23:07.26,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.15,0:23:10.94,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.94,0:23:15.08,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(20,345)}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:57.28,0:22:01.64,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼が笑っても
Dialogue: 1,0:22:04.00,0:22:09.37,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}気付いたら　貴方を思ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.62,0:22:16.99,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}彼と繋ぐ手も
Dialogue: 1,0:22:19.24,0:22:24.88,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(8,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}感じてる　貴方の温もり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.93,0:22:30.22,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}思い出を切り取って
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.63,0:22:33.97,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(12,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}胸から追い出したって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:34.51,0:22:38.02,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(13,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}記憶を蹴飛ばしたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:38.34,0:22:42.24,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}未だに貴方を…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.03,0:22:47.48,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(7,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}今　時が過ぎ去り　季節をめぐり
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.55,0:22:51.28,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(10,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}あの笑顔　白く霞んでも
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.37,0:22:55.23,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心はそう　貴方を忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.26,0:22:59.00,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}もう二度と会えなくたって
Dialogue: 1,0:22:59.06,0:23:02.83,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}笑い合う写真簿を倒しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.92,0:23:07.26,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(9,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}溢れ出す思いを隠しても
Dialogue: 1,0:23:08.15,0:23:10.94,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心は忘れない
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.94,0:23:15.08,ed_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(14,342)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}貴方との記憶


Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.28,0:22:01.64,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.00,0:22:09.37,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.62,0:22:16.99,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.24,0:22:24.88,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.93,0:22:30.22,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.63,0:22:33.97,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.51,0:22:38.02,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.34,0:22:42.24,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.03,0:22:47.48,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.55,0:22:51.28,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.37,0:22:55.23,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.26,0:22:59.00,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.06,0:23:02.83,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.92,0:23:07.26,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.15,0:23:10.94,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.94,0:23:15.08,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(620,15)}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶

Dialogue: 1,0:21:57.28,0:22:01.64,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}面對他的笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:04.00,0:22:09.37,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}不知不覺間　又在想你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:12.62,0:22:16.99,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}牽著他的手
Dialogue: 1,0:22:19.24,0:22:24.88,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍能感到　你的溫暖
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.93,0:22:30.22,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}切斷回憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:30.63,0:22:33.97,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}逐出心中
Dialogue: 1,0:22:34.51,0:22:38.02,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}驅散記憶
Dialogue: 1,0:22:38.34,0:22:42.24,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(626,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}卻還是對你…
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.03,0:22:47.48,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}時光飛逝　季節輪換
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.55,0:22:51.28,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你的笑容　已然隱約
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.37,0:22:55.23,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(628,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}心中仍然　難以忘懷
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.26,0:22:59.00,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(627,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再無法相見
Dialogue: 1,0:22:59.06,0:23:02.83,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(630,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算合上相視對笑的相簿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:02.92,0:23:07.26,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(629,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}就算再怎麼欺騙自己
Dialogue: 1,0:23:08.15,0:23:10.94,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(624,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}仍然難忘
Dialogue: 1,0:23:11.94,0:23:15.08,ed_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(625,18)\fs20\1a&HCF&\shad0}{\fad(300,300)}你我的記憶


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓

Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.75,0:01:48.50,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Squeez'n step on it hard
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.13,0:01:51.90,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Try to feel my heart beat
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.92,0:01:55.43,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}High,as high as you can
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.52,0:01:58.85,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All your blood will turn to fountain water
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.22,0:02:02.39,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We're surrounded by plot in this universe
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.44,0:02:06.08,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Wash away the stain of blood with tears
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.36,0:02:09.55,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}We cannot look, or they will spell on you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.63,0:02:13.15,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}Wind of fuego will lead us through
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.80,0:02:30.11,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.16,0:02:33.90,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}I found guide-in line in the raging world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.94,0:02:37.58,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}There you see, in the sky even in this insane world
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.60,0:02:39.05,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,50)}Ride on Back
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.09,0:02:42.46,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}All we need is your sympathy
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.48,0:02:46.13,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)}We make the history of our own
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.13,0:02:48.33,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}I found the light, was real, I am united
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.83,0:02:55.60,op_eng,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,500)\fs23}There you see, in the sky, even in this
