Hodr...
With just five units?
I won't stop you, but you'll be heading into enemy territory.
I know.
However, I believe it would be most effective for the Valkyrie Platoon
to make a surprise attack on Binonten while you take on the Mizoram Stronghold here.
I can come in from the north.
There's a giant canyon in the northern wall.
The Artemis can get through the canyon.
I need to take down the wall as soon as possible.
Yes, I understand.
What are you doing?!
Don't block my path!
There isn't much time left, Hodr.
Rygart did?
Yes.
Zess...
Tokubetsu na Mono wa
This world has
Nani mo Nai Kedo
nothing worth noting
Sono Te ni Tsukamu ni wa
But we have plenty of love
Juubun Sugiru Ai o
on our hands
Shinjiru Mono o
Those who
Motte Iru Mono wa
have faith
Yuruginai Ai no Tame ni
will act on behalf
Tsuranuku Omoi o
of their unwavering love
Unmei ni Tachimukaeru Nara
If I could fight destiny,
Kono Subete Kakeru Omoi de Yuku
I'd act on all of my feelings
Book Two
The Split Path
Binonten, the capital of Krisna.
They pride themselves on having mined the most amount of reactive quartz on the continent.
And being in the middle of a great oasis, they are also blessed with fishing.
A grave resource shortage was predicted in the neighboring Commonwealth of Athens
and they began to invade the Krisna Kingdom.
The General Heckel's platoon was in a stalemate at the Mizoram Stronghold,
but Zess' Valkyrie Platoon utilized the ability of their five Artemis units
and launched a surprise attack on Binonten.
Meanwhile, in Ilios, the capital of Athens,
the executives were analyzing the war under Secretary of War Loquis.
In short, this excuse-filled report says that 150 Golems weren't enough to take down 50?
We've already lost 2,000 soldiers.
We can't possibly disclose this to the citizens.
No, we can say that the soldiers were shot down on their way back and received heavy injuries.
Time is the real problem.
If we spend any more time on the invasion, Orlando may intervene.
We'll have to dispatch General Borcuse at that point.
H-However, Borcuse is...
Please excuse me for interrupting in the middle of a meeting.
I just received word that the Valkyrie Platoon is attacking Binonten
under the command of General Ares' subordinate, Captain Zess.
It seems like they left the western border three days ago
to make a surprise attack on the capital.
What an achievement.
Zess broke through the northern canyon with the new Golems.
Striking Binonten is a great feat.
He is indeed the Secretary of War's younger brother.
I'm impressed.
He acted on his own again...
Zess, do you so strongly desire fame?
Listen up!
I tell you this again and again:
Our mission is to protect the capital!
If you let an enemy inside, do not let them advance!
Yes, Ma'am!
Everyone get to your inner-wall defensive stations!
Elza Squad, go cover the defense squad at the western gate!
Sir!
The rest of you, follow me.
We'll defend the northern wall!
Sir!
General True's squad will sortie from the west!
All units, come to the western gate!
General True, please put that down!
It's still in testing!
General True!
Exactly! I will go test it!
I see.
It's quite heavy.
General True.
Could you stay here this time?
General Baldr, is that an order?
Of course not.
You, Imperial Guard General Sakura, and I are all equal.
Only His Highness can give us any orders.
I was just making a suggestion.
So you understand.
Then I apologize, but I'll be ignoring your suggestion.
The sword fits perfectly in the
heavy-lance sheath on my back.
It must be itching to be used by me.
General True!
The Emperor called both you and I back here when General Sakura was already here.
I believe he wishes to preserve our strengths.
Your cowardice is precisely what has allowed our enemies to advance!
My squad is heading out there to
protect the capital and its citizens!
Three units damaged.
Seventeen left.
Can you draw them out?
No.
It appears they've been ordered not to engage fire.
It was a perfectly executed surprise attack, but they reacted surprisingly fast.
Did the gate open?
I'll take a look.
I see one Golem.
An unknown unit.
Unknown?
It's holding a red and white flag.
A messenger?
A signal?
He seems to be requesting a negotiation.
Operation...
"Let's get Prince Bashful and the dull girl together"?
Is that a code?
I'll go negotiate.
Captain Zess, that's too dangerous!
I'll go too!
Stay back, Erekt!
I'll get both sides' units to retreat until they're out of range.
Even during the Assam war, Zess always kept his cool.
But he's flustered right now...
Why are you here...
when you don't like to fight?!
Who's there?
If I recall correctly...
You're the heir to the Tupel family.
If you're a man from Athens,
why won't you fight one on one?
Uh...
And you're some... celebrity.
Thanks.
I don't like people who can only fight in groups,
but I hate cowards even more.
Would you fight back if it were one on one?
I don't know.
It's just something my dad taught me.
If I can put up with it until they get bored,
no one has to die.
What if they hit you until you die?
Would you still not fight?
I haven't thought it out that far!
Does he have a spine or not?
Why did they jump you?
So many questions.
I don't know.
It's because I'm different.
Different?
So he's that guy?
Hey!
If you stay within my ten maile radius, I don't think anyone would pick a fight with you.
Just don't get closer than three mailes.
Not a bad deal, is it?
I'm Zess.
Rygart...
It's been four years.
But it looks like we don't have the time to celebrate our reunion.
Rygart!
Answer me!
How are you moving that thing?
Zess, my question comes first!
Why are you invading Hodr's kingdom?!
Athens has a very justifiable reason for this invasion.
I can't stop it.
Don't give me that!
You've come this far into this kingdom! What's there to be justified about?
Look!
This war was originally triggered by Orlando in the east.
They were secretly communicating with the soldiers who started the war in Assam.
What's worse, Krisna allowed the Orlando Army
to advance through Krisnan lands to take part in the war.
In short, Krisna helped Orlando in their ambitions.
Helped?!
W-Wait a minute!
Do you seriously think Hodr has any ambitions?!
Of course not!
I know very well that he doesn't even care about the throne!
Orlando took advantage of their
international military training with Krisna
to travel through their territory.
Hodr was set up!
Please, Rygart!
Knock some sense into him and make him surrender!
You should be able to do that!
General Baldr, they're not making any moves yet!
As per Queen Sigyn's strong request, we will be on standby for as long as we can!
The real problem is General True who went to the western gate.
I can't just agree with that!
You need to retreat and tell Athens to stop the invasion!
That's the proper way to settle this!
I'm still only 25.
I don't have the authority to do that.
We can't always be stupid students who simply voice our ideals and reasons.
Unfortunately, once a war starts, it won't end until it's settled.
I can't accept those conditions.
Conditions?
The enemy... is getting ready from the west?
Rygart, you were just used to buy them time.
Zess, are you saying that knowing the conditions—
Hey!
Listen up, Rygart!
The fall of Krisna is already set in stone!
The question is whether it's now or later!
I'll count to five.
Go back and make Hodr surrender, or fight here!
General Borcuse is going to be dispatched for the
second invasion. He's a merciless master of war.
He'll attack with over 200 units!
There's no time!
Stop resisting and surrender!
Zess...
I'm starting.
One!
He's aiming his gun!
General Baldr!
Our enemy has attacked from the north.
We'll surround them and destroy them!
We Draupnir Heavy Knights strike
like lightning and adapt like water.
Charge!
Run!
Roger, Sir!
Two!
Zess, you won't fire.
15 units all at once.
Krisna sure has resources to spare.
I'm so nervous.
You have no reason to be.
You're not gonna hit a single enemy.
I've hit something once!
Let's go.
Three!
You of all people would back away.
Go back!
Go back and convince Hodr!
You can't shoot.
You know you're wrong.
Fish at the west, huh?
You're a genius, Zess!
I'm fishing tons!
Why won't you retreat, Rygart?
Four!
Five!
Rygart!
Idiot, don't move!
I don't want to kill you!
Stop!
It's fast!
How can that black thing accelerate so fast?
Captain Zess!
I'll overtake him from the front!
Wait, Erekt!
Open the gate! Charge!
Erekt.
Their real army is coming.
He doesn't have a weapon.
Leave him be!
Okay!
Private Dan, cover for the black Golem!
Yes, sir!
If I recall correctly, he's some man named Rygart
who was personally welcomed by General Baldr and His Highness.
Is he confused?
How far does he plan to go?
And he's fast!
Damn, we've lost six.
This is a terrible location.
We're completely overpowered.
General True!
We should retreat!
Give me a break!
They only have three units!
If we can get the upperhand, we'll turn this game around!
They're too high up for our Golems!
At this rate, we'll be annihilated!
Like hell I can back down here!
Cleo, at least land one shot!
You're so incompetent!
Okay!
I got one!
Fall back!
I'll hold them back!
Survive and inherit my will!
Protect the capital!
What are you saying?
If you don't retreat, we aren't allowed to retreat!
Retreat!
Okay, they're starting to move back.
Follow them!
I'll obliterate them!
Please retreat safely.
Queen Sigyn, please come to your senses!
Please come back to the castle!
He shot at me.
Zess, you asshole.
Should I hide here for a while?
No, if I abandon this...
Why's this a different color?
Translate into my language, dammit.
I can read the number.
Five?
You!
You ruined my chance to capture the king!
What the...?
How is it... so high?
What the hell was that?
It landed without an empennage to slow it down?
No, the notable thing is that height!
If they were to mass produce this...
They'd easily overtake our capital's final defensive line!
I have to finish you, here and now!
I'll break you into a thousand pieces!
He's only wearing a makeshift light armor...
Rygart...
I know that damaged him.
I hit him at least four times.
T-That wasn't as tough as I thought.
I should at least report this to Zess later.
H-He's still standing!
Holding that claymore with a single arm!
Tell the defensive captain at the west gate to provide support for the black Golem!
Yes, Ma'am!
Don't die yet.
What a surprise...
Even General True's Golem with six ligaments had trouble handling that claymore.
The horsepower of that Golem's ligaments are out of this world.
Is it gonna come?
You bastard!
What?!
He's swinging around his lance?
Doesn't he know how to fight?
It's coming!
I need to turn to the side.
Asshole!
I can't damage him when he uses that claymore as his shield.
I can't do anything from so far away.
How much ammo have I wasted on him already?
I'm going to run out.
Please give up.
W-What?
Don't tell me...
S-Stay back!
I'll open the gate!
A hard inner frame?
I'll give you another one!
What... the...?
Why the hell is he so strong?!
I-It took its distance again.
T-This is bad.
He took my arm.
I can't get close anymore.
Damn!
I can do it!
Rygart?
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
Who are you?
Are you okay?
Oh, right.
You can't speak through the quartz microphone.
I am Dan and I serve General Baldr.
I came to save you under his orders.
It slowed down...
Take cover behind me.
Hey, wait!
What are you doing?!
You don't need to kill him!
Let me go!
We're in the middle of an operation and we can't afford to take a prisoner.
It's not showing any signs of surrendering either.
Enemy backup could also be hiding somewhere nearby!
We must exterminate the threat and continue moving.
I understand that!
I-I know!
Let's just abandon this here!
This is armed!
Do you want to be hit from behind?!
Surrender, you asshole!
You barbarians...
Huh?
You fucking barbarians!
Barbarians?
What's she talking about?
I'd rather die than be humiliated!
H-Hey!
Zess...
It was an honor to have fought alongside you.
Wait!
Hold on a minute!
Cleo, I think you should retire early.
I don't care what you say. You're not cut out to be a soldier.
Stop! Don't do it!
They're much faster and have a much wider range...
We'll be at a geographical
disadvantage if we keep moving forward.
Let's retreat to the meeting spot.
Yes, sir.
I think we could hold out a little longer.
Are you worried about the other three?
I'm more than happy that we took down seven.
And I never like splitting up a platoon.
How's Dan?!
I'm gonna fall!
You won't.
You will if I let go.
Lee's late...
Lee's way too late.
We retreated while under fire from the enemy, so I don't think Cleo saw...
But from afar, I saw the black
Golem's lance shatter Lee's Artemis.
How can that be...?
I lost one of my subordinates because I let him go.
I've made my decision.
I'll surrender.
Your Highness, as incompetent as I may be, I'd like to say...
that I do not approve.
All my subordinates still wish to fight.
Please give us another chance.
What are you up to?
I received orders from Queen Sigyn to decipher the ancient language.
This is one of the original parts of the Under Golem, right?
Yeah, these writings were etched on the chest armor.
I assume the ancients etched them in.
I must say, I was surprised by this unit's capabilities.
But I heard it's going to be demolished since it can't move anymore. It didn't even get named yet.
Barbarians, huh?
I was taught that both sides did cruel things
during the independence war 80 years ago, but...
I wonder if the education in Athens is more biased?
The soldier in that unit was young...
The girl we just buried was probably around 15 or 16—
Stop, I don't wanna hear it!
I'm sorry!
Oh, no.
Sorry, don't mind me.
Let's switch, Erekt.
I can't make the captain do the look out.
Goodness Cleo...
She abandoned her one and only job.
Is she still blue?
Lee and Cleo were from the same school.
I heard Lee was an honors student
who always dragged Cleo to class
because all she did was tell fortunes.
All because of my error...
Captain Zess, your strategy was flawless.
Lee is the one who made the error.
Dying is a part of a soldier's job.
You're being too soft on those two.
I understand that, but I also have a two year-old daughter.
When I picture her going out to war one day,
I just can't help but treat them softly.
I have always wanted to ask you...
I understand Lee, but why did you approve of Cleo's enlistment?
You know how most of the generals disapprove of the Artemis for being a defective Golem?
That's rather off-topic.
I wouldn't say it's defective, but it's more
stressful to control than any other Golem.
Erekt, how long did it take you to get used to it?
A month, I'd say.
Lee and Argath took two months.
It took even me a week to get used to it.
A week?!
I'm impressed.
Cleo...
did it in a day.
Rygart, after breakfast, can you come to the hang—
Sorry.
I don't think I can do anything even if I'm here.
I'm going home.
Good luck.
Good bye, Rygart.
I'm glad to have seen you again before I die.
Cut down on the leg armor!
You can take off the upper body armor as well.
But General, if we take off more armor,
even a normal gun could take this down.
I don't care!
If I don't make my Golem lighter, I can't get anywhere near the enemy!
I won't have them control the battlefield anymore.
Did you know Dan from work?
Y-Yeah, something like that.
I'm his wife.
I just can't believe it...
A Golem pilot's corpse isn't allowed to be shown to non-personnel.
I feel as if he's still...
Please take your time.
I'm sure he'll love the company.
Well, you can be mad at me all you want,
but at least you're lucky enough to have a kid on the way.
My brother and I never get any girls.
You must feel sort of responsible since you're here.
Responsible?
I just came here to give my prayers to the idiot who showed up and died.
You're just as His Highness said.
You become dishonest with yourself when you feel hurt.
He also told me about your father.
He was disappointed to learn that you were an unsorcerer,
but he had sold all of his magical devices by the next day
and tried to show you how to work in the fields with two arms and legs.
You always speak ill of your father, but you actually respect him.
That's what His Highness told me.
In any case, Dan's death isn't anyone's fault.
Sadly, it was caused by his lack of judgment.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not worried about it!
Don't make me repeat myself!
See ya.
Rygart.
What do you want? I'm done here.
I'd like you to participate in the next sortie.
Sortie?
Yeah, right! That has nothing to do with me.
Even if His Highness has decided to surrender?
Athens has proposed a peace treaty.
The execution of the Krisnan Royal Family.
I do feel bad for Hodr, but...
But I...!
Queen Sigyn believes that ancient Under Golem can still operate.
Only you are capable of moving that.
Please fight alongside us, Rygart.
I...
I was just coincidentally born in the countryside of Krisna, and I'm...
I will not let His Highness be beheaded in Athens—
Shut up!
If you're going home, you should've said something to me.
Sorry.
Don't make that face.
I didn't come to stop you.
If I had known they'd be coming for the capital so quickly,
I wouldn't have called you here.
I thought I had more time to talk.
Oh yeah, here.
What's that?
Well, a parting gift.
Please take it.
It's not like the money from back then.
Back then?
You don't remember?
Well, it has been five years...
You know that time you said you were going to quit school because you couldn't pay,
and I told you that I could ask my father to do something about it?
You got really mad.
My dad taught me to never borrow money from a friend!
Even if I'm being chased by loan sharks!
Oh...
Did I?
That's embarrassing.
I was ashamed for being so thoughtless,
but it made me happy.
Farewell, Rygart.
Till we meet again.
Hodr knew...
He knew that we'd never meet again.
I'm so happy to see you.
He picked a fight with destiny.
I'd say he's an admirable father.
I couldn't fight it.
It's the same writing as the one on the Golem's chest.
The words the ancients went out of their way to etch...
"Let us fight destiny."
Rygart...
Rygart.
There's nothing shameful about running away.
Some things are just out of people's hands.
If you think you're gonna die, just run.
What are you doing, Rygart?
Sorry, Dad.
Korekara no Sekai ni wa
Dare mo Inai
There is no one in the future
Koe Dake o Senaka ni Kanjite
Hearing voices only from behind,
Miwataseba Daichi ni Saku
Hito no Negai
I look up to see wishes
blooming in the land
Fumitsubusu Mono o Sagase
I seek out the ones who
try to stomp on them
Mamorenai Yakusoku
Dake wa Shinai Keshite
because I never make
promises I cannot keep
Hokori Takaki Yume
Kagayaki Korosanu Youni
They're proud dreams,
so I'll make them shine brighter
Kakaeru Kodoku no Tsuyosa
Inochigake no Mirai
while bearing lonely strength
for the irreplaceable future
Furimukazu ni Susumu Beki da to
"Don't just turn around
and move forward"
Kimi ga Yubi Sashita Kanatae to
You pointed me toward
the horizon I needed to follow
Hashiridashite Kigatsuitanda
I began to run and noticed too late
Omoi wa Tsunagaru Tabi Kieru
that feelings die when they connect
Futatabi Aeru Hi no
Tame ni Ima o Ikiru yo
I will live in the present for
we may meet in the future
Dare mo Inai Kaze no Naka
Hitori de Samayou Toride
Wind blows with no one in sight,
and I wander lost in this stronghold
Dare ka Ite mo Onaji Koto
Samayou Basho wa Majiwaranai
Even if there were others, I still
wouldn't wander into their wandering
Furimukazu ni Susumu Beki da to
"Don't just turn around
and move forward"
Kimi ga Yubi Sashita Kanatae to
You pointed me toward the
horizon I needed to follow
Hashiridashite Kigatsuitanda
I began to run and noticed too late
Omoi wa Tsunagaru Tabi Kieru
that feelings die when they connect
Futatabi Aeru Hi no
Tame ni Ima o Ikiru yo
I will live in the present for
we may meet in the future
ALIVE SERIOUS AGE
Alive in this serious age
If you will acknowledge the above, swear loyalty to King Krisna IX,
and to protect the lives and wealth of the citizens all in the name of the Lævateinn,
step forward.
Secondary Heavy-Knight number 1728, Rygart Arrow.
Protect Krisna under General Baldr as the primary pilot
and secondary person in charge of the Under Golem.
Kneel and accept the Lævateinn as proof of a heavy knight.
Hey, get on your knees.
No, it's fine.
Give it to me.
But, the ritual's...
You're...
an idiot.
I know, stupid.
Hey, hey, hey...
Can he fight with something that heavy?
It's totally mysterious as to why he can even walk.
The Under Golem shall receive the name Delphing.
Zess...
I'm going to protect Hodr's kingdom.
Preview
He's a baby Giant Eagle Owl.
Sorry, do you mind if I stand on your shoulders?
Goodness, you don't even know the
name of your own kingdom's prince?
Rygart!
Zess!
Book Three
A Scar made by an Assassin's Dagger
A
That black Golem's... going to kill me.