Chapter Five
Death's Horizon
I might lose my temper and accidentally shoot my comrades. Is that okay?
Knock it off!
Who the hell do you think you are!?
Impressive dodging.
I'd give you above 60 points for defense, but not quite 80.
He sliced the quartz in two!
What the hell IS he?
I was opposed to releasing him myself.
Seems like everybody hates him.
But I suppose he is pretty messed up.
He's my son.
Do NOT trust him, you hear me?
No matter what!
Nike!
Girghe...
Tokubetsu na Mono wa
This world has
Nani mo Nai Kedo
nothing worth noting
Sono Te ni Tsukamu ni wa
But we have plenty of love
Juubun Sugiru Ai o
on our hands
Shinjiru Mono o
Those who
Motte Iru Mono wa
have faith
Yuruginai Ai no Tame ni
will act on behalf
Tsuranuku Omoi o
of their unwavering love
Unmei ni Tachimukaeru Nara
If I could fight destiny,
Kono Subete Kakeru Omoi de Yuku
I'd act on all of my feelings
Book Five
Death's Horizon
So, Girghe,
I'd like to hear your report.
I did step aside amidst the chaos, and once I regained myself, wandered about.
During which, found myself under enemy fire, and fled.
That is all.
That's not what I heard from Rygart.
You destroyed seven Golems, partially destroyed two officer's units, and nearly crippled another.
...Oh, right, I did that too.
Girghe, you are hereby forbidden to carry a firearm or approach a Golem without my explicit approval.
Captain Narvi, may Girghe be allowed to oversee the repairs to his Artemis?
Come with me, Girghe!
Yes, ma'am.
What's with that guy?
Mr. Loggin, I have an important message.
Good to see you came back safely, Rygart.
Likewise.
You know...
I'm not sure how to put it, but...
He's really something.
Just what did he do, exactly?
About a year ago, I was on my way home from patrolling the border when it happened.
Girghe had already been imprisoned.
I went to his cell in hopes that I could learn why he did it,
but he would only stare into space or sneer at me. He refused to speak.
Girghe was using one of ten Golems during a routine marching exercise.
Suddenly, he fired on a comrade, and used him as a shield.
He then dispatched the remaining eight Golems without receiving so much as a scratch on his own.
After that, he turned himself in.
That's the gist of it.
But is that what really happened?
I mean, he was the only one who lived, right?
No. Only the first victim died.
He avoided the remaining eight's vitals.
Girghe never had any grudges or rivalries with those other men.
There are several weapons before you.
Pick whichever you like.
Very impressive.
What!? General True is dead!?
What about his remains?
The enemy took possession of them.
Speaking of which, Nile...
How do you intend to tell Captain Narvi?
The decision is yours.
She loved the man like a father.
Can you guarantee she won't become a hindrance to future operations upon hearing this?
I'm afraid not, sir.
Being a hindrance would be the least of our worries.
I see. So we're left with two choices.
Either Loggin takes over as captain,
or we keep her in the dark.
We were soundly defeated.
Indeed. It was a disgrace.
I even allowed Sir Iris to die.
What?
I'll make them pay...
Were it not for Colonel Io's assistance,
the General would have been in grave danger.
I will slaughter every last Krishnan pig...
That concludes my report on the Krisnan Artemis and the Black Golem.
Leto, what's our current situation?
Sir.
Our right wing retreated along a separate route, but were annihilated by General Baldr's forces.
Of our forces that fought in the Arracan wastes, only 60% remain.
However, we still managed to rendezvous with the main force.
Correct. Our force now numbers 120 strong.
So in short, we may consider this skirmish a draw?
The Krisnans are not to be taken lightly.
A skirmish? We lost far too many men for a skirmish.
But the war has indeed just begun.
And what of the General?
He's chosen to spend the night in the Hicherion.
Sorry, Iris...
I just can't contain my excitement.
Especially with those two enemy Golems running around.
Mr. Rygart, we've received orders from the capital to withdraw.
Please begin preparations to move out.
We're withdrawing?
Yeah.
If we remain here, it'll become difficult to maintain our supply line.
Also, we need to escort the wounded back to Binonten.
Gotcha.
Oh, by the way...
What?
Could you stop calling me "Mr. Rygart"? It's kinda awkward.
What should I call you, then?
Just call me Rygart.
Awkward?
Girghe, we're pulling out.
You have permission to approach your Artemis.
But you're not to board it until I give the order!
Roger that, Captain.
Very well!
Where's General Baldr?
What's the matter?
Borcuse is on the move.
He's headed towards Pegusa.
Pegusa!?
Are you sure?
We've confirmed that he's taking a detour there.
This way.
Rygart.
Wait a second! There's a tiny village near Pegusa.
Have the residents been evacuated yet?
If they don't make it in time, will Borcuse attack?
Why, is there something about that village?
That village near Pegusa... is my hometown.
My little brother, Regarz, lives on the outskirts.
What?
I see. Inform General Baldr at once.
Rygart, I'm sure they'll inform the villagers.
Right now, we need to get moving.
Rygart! Pack it in!
Right...
Wait! Stop right there!
Rygart!
Rygart deserted us to save his brother!?
I'm very sorry, sir.
Send a squad after him.
Get me Kurozawa.
Umm, Sigyn...
Could you continue your story from yesterday?
Which one?
You mean the one where Rygart climbed into a training Golem while playing hide and seek,
and got thrashed around for an hour?
No, not that one.
I was talking about the one where Rygart and
Hodr tried to sneak into the girl's dormitories,
and Zess had to rescue them.
Oh yes. One day, out of the blue,
Rygart boasted, "Tonight's the night!"
"For what?" I asked.
And he said, "I climb the mountain because it is there.
Men are born to create legends."
Uh-huh...
Ridiculous, isn't it?
Anyhow, security at the academy was quite strict.
The girl's dorms in particular. No boys were allowed.
No less than eight female guards were stationed around the clock.
There was also a rumor that a boy had been shot dead ages ago trying to sneak inside.
They were so fired up.
So did Zess save them from being shot?
Supposedly, they invited him along...
That's ridiculous. I hope you get shot.
So did they make it inside?
That night, I heard shots from a Pressure Gun.
I looked out my window, and saw two silhouettes running away.
They were chased off, like I expected.
Eventually, Zess came to their rescue, and they got away safely.
That's worlds apart from the Zess I know.
Zess was never one to show emotion to myself or others. He was very mature.
But whenever he was around Hodr and Rygart, he turned into a child again.
Especially around Rygart. They fought all the time...
Sigyn?
Yes?
Um, nothing.
Regarz!
Regarz...
Borcuse.
And here I thought I'd just swing by town...
What are you doing here?
Please step aside, sir!
Hold your fire!
Nobody is to move a muscle!
Anyone who interferes will be executed.
What a peculiar stance.
Those are some clever moves!
But you're wide open when you come down!
When it comes to jointed
weapons, I have a bit of an edge!
What!?
How could the General...
What the hell happened?
What's wrong? I'm wide open.
If you're going to kill me, now's your chance.
Tell me, why did you come to this backwater village alone?
Something tells me you aren't lost.
What went through your mind when you saw the villagers?
Did you think, "That's just a part of war"?
There must be some reason you've come here alone.
But you were just too late.
What will you do?
He's trying to grab my arm!
General!
Where the hell is Bardess!?
It was a smart move to let my Hicherion go airborne.
If I had tried to stand my ground and guard, the frame would've given way from that hit.
All I've got left is the Eastern Blade.
Now what? Are you going to fly off?
I still can't figure out why you came here by yourself.
But that makes this little detour worth it.
Those maneuvers can't be done with quartz ligaments.
A relic from ages past, I suspect.
That might be just the thing Orlando needs!
What a fortunate find!
Charging right at your opponent... You bore me.
You can't even close the gap between us.
You've gone and ruined my good mood.
Tie him down.
Chains won't cut it! I want five Golems holding him down too!
I want to transport it home with minimal damage.
Tear open the cockpit and drag the pilot out.
Then kill him.
Sir, how many times have I told you not to charge into battle alone?
I couldn't accurately determine the Black Golem's combat prowess unless I fought him myself.
But once I did, it became painfully clear.
It's not the pilot that makes that Golem so powerful.
That wasn't the fighting style of a soldier.
My interest is now held by that man in the Artemis.
Shall we return to the camp?
Yes, lets.
Let's go, boys.
Sir!
Alright! Squads four and five, move out!
Yes, sir!
Alright, we'll take it from here!
We were too late.
40 units headed southwest. But there's still about 20 left.
Plus about 200 infantry.
It's just a matter of time until they yank him out of there.
Kurozawa, do you think we can attack?
Are you out of your mind!? Forget it!
We've only got 4 Golems, 15 scouts and 5 engineers!
If we charged in there, they'd tear us apart!
Rygart's done for. We have to let him go.
C'mon, let's get outta here!
It pains me to say this, but I agree with Nile.
If we rush in, it'd be nearly impossible to escape.
He was a good man. Not that I knew him too well, though...
But our only option now is to retreat.
Kurozawa.
Remain on standby for now.
I want to stick it out a bit longer.
Understood.
Thank you.
No problem.
We've managed to evacuate 80 percent of the citizens so far.
Worst case, we can escort the remaining 20 percent into the castle in under four hours.
Is there even any point to defending our sovereignty now?
Even General True died because of me.
Your Majesty, please do not give up hope.
The Krisnan people fought hard to regain their independence 80 years ago.
That sense of pride will not waver, even if we surrender!
Do you think it will fade under Athenian rule?
No. There would soon be another conflict. And that is why we must fight!
I know that.
An urgent message from our scouts!
What is it?
Excuse me.
They've broken through our advance camps.
A massive Athenian army broke through our borders, and are headed our way.
Speed up the citizen's evacuation.
One more thing, ma'am.
Now what!?
Heavy Knight 1st Class Rygart has headed into enemy territory to rescue his brother,
and the Millennium Squadron is
proceeding to recover the Delphine.
What is Rygart's... no, the
Millennium Squadron's situation?
Unknown.
What happened to the guards placed with Rygart's brother?
I had specifically arranged for protection.
I'm very sorry, sir.
Your Majesty...
Send a message to all our remaining forces.
Withdraw to the capital immediately.
Are we to abandon our first line of defense?
I authorize it.
What do you think you're doing?
We're coming with you, sir.
I'm not recruiting men for a suicide mission.
Yes, but we heard you resigned as general, sir.
In our current situation, no forces can be spared to rescue Rygart.
This does not concern you men.
Yes, sir. We know that.
But the seven of us have been authorized by the Vice General to act independently.
In other words, we may do as we please.
So let's go, General!
Let's save Rygart and return to the capital, General!
I thought I made it clear I am no longer your general.
We're aware of that, sir.
Thus, we can't acknowledge your order to not accompany you.
Thank you.
Dammit!
The pilot's regained consciousness!
Pin him down!
They're restraining me!
Loggin, open fire!
Come on!
No good!
It doesn't matter! Keep shooting!
Enemy attack! Take cover!
Look at me, Rygart!
Jump!
Regarz...
After him!
Sorry, Narvi!
Shove it!
Retreat!
The next time you ignore my orders will be your last, got it!?
Did you find your brother?
So all you did was drag your
comrades into your own mess?
Let's go. They're right behind us.
Right.
The enemy?
Take cover!
Did they catch up already!?
No, it's too soon. Must be another squad.
Girghe, what the hell are you doing!?
Don't expose yourself!
Loggin!
You're mine!
Nile, get behind her!
Narvi!
You little shit!
Don't even try it!
Son of a bitch!
He cut through the heavy armor!?
That's no ordinary sword!
What's your problem, Girghe!?
Let's go back! I'm worried about the others!
Worried? Now there's a surprise.
Not something I'd expect from a guy who just ran off on his own.
Besides, you got us into this mess.
That's why we need to go back right now!
Pathetic.
You couldn't even find your brother.
Girghe...
I've heard all about you.
What are you trying to say?
Look at you. You even sacrificed the comrades who came to your aid.
You and I are fellow traitors.
Here's some advice from your senior traitor.
Don't worry about it.
The dead are nothing but pathetic weaklings.
These weakling's very existence is evil; a sin.
They survive only by dragging down people like us.
So don't worry too much
even if you caused their deaths.
Even if the others lose their lives here, it's not your fault.
They're just buffoons.
Die!
Goodnight!
Who the hell's piloting that thing?
Your elbow joint didn't break. Did you reinforce the frame?
I must say, I'm grateful to the king.
Don't get carried away!
If he had penetrated any further, I'd be dead.
You had no issues throwing aside your rifle, yet you still cling to your spear?
Too slow.
You were a formidable adversary.
So this is how it ends, huh?
Spare me the pain and get it over with quickly.
I shall.
We're more alike than I had thought.
Your dad said the same thing...
Really now?
Yeah! You act so high and mighty, and
you're spouting crap like that all the time!
You make me sick!
But...
But what?
But you're just a little shit!
Oh, I'm well aware of that.
There! That's exactly what I'm talking about!
Unlike me, you're a genius who can accomplish anything, but all you do is fuck around!
While everyone else is fighting for their lives, you just sit and watch!
Couldn't have said it better myself.
Then tell me, Rygart. What are you  doing?
What do you fight for?
Spare me the crap about defending your homeland. What is it you really want?
What do I want?
Yes. The real reason that you've tried to hide.
Did you really think nobody noticed?
I...
If you come back unharmed... I'll stop being angry.
It's the talk of the castle. The way our dear Queen looks at you...
What're you talking about?
That beautiful head doesn't turn for just any man.
Not that it's any of my business, mind you.
Hey, I know! How about this?
If you can beat me, I'll grant your wish. Your one true desire.
I'll storm the castle, grab the Queen, and place her in your arms!
Doesn't that just sound wonderful?
You don't get it. I'm here to protect the royal family.
Anyone who would attack them is my enemy!
Then let's settle the score right now, once and for all.
Sure. I'm happy to oblige.
Kneeling before your enemy? A classic counterattack stance.
Either that or a bold move by one man up against a hundred.
No matter.
I'll crush you like a bug, Golem and all!
His footwork is unbelievable!
If I tried to get up, I'd be dead!
Hang in there!
Just until Girghe extends his upper body!
He said the same thing.
Your old man told me not to mourn the dead!
He didn't mean it in quite the same way, but it still makes me furious!
You said you'd grant my wish if I won, right?
Then if I do...
Become a general!
Surpass your father!
There he is! Capture him!
Got it!
Damn it!
We gotta go! We can't stay here!
Hm, the aim's a little off...
Trying to kill me? Well, too bad!
I'll crush you!
Girghe!
Get back, Nike!
That Artemis is bad news!
I'll snap you in two!
I see now... Those are no ordinary ligaments!
Nike!
Come on, Delphine! Get up!
Further resistance is useless! Give yourselves up!
YOU!!!
Run for it, Girghe!
Are you insane!? I said get out of here!
Girghe!
Korekara no Sekai ni wa
Dare mo Inai
There is no one in the future
Koe Dake o Senaka ni Kanjite
Hearing voices only from behind,
Miwataseba Daichi ni Saku
Hito no Negai
I look up to see wishes
blooming in the land
Fumitsubusu Mono o Sagase
I seek out the ones who
try to stomp on them
Mamorenai Yakusoku
Dake wa Shinai Keshite
because I never make
promises I cannot keep
Hokori Takaki Yume
Kagayaki Korosanu Youni
They're proud dreams,
so I'll make them shine brighter
Kakaeru Kodoku no Tsuyosa
Inochigake no Mirai
while bearing lonely strength
for the irreplaceable future
Furimukazu ni Susumu Beki da to
"Don't just turn around
and move forward"
Kimi ga Yubi Sashita Kanatae to
You pointed me toward
the horizon I needed to follow
Hashiridashite Kigatsuitanda
I began to run and noticed too late
Omoi wa Tsunagaru Tabi Kieru
that feelings die when they connect
Futatabi Aeru Hi no
Tame ni Ima o Ikiru yo
I will live in the present for
we may meet in the future
Dare mo Inai Kaze no Naka
Hitori de Samayou Toride
Wind blows with no one in sight,
and I wander lost in this stronghold
Dare ka Ite mo Onaji Koto
Samayou Basho wa Majiwaranai
Even if there were others, I still
wouldn't wander into their wandering
Furimukazu ni Susumu Beki da to
"Don't just turn around
and move forward"
Kimi ga Yubi Sashita Kanatae to
You pointed me toward the
horizon I needed to follow
Hashiridashite Kigatsuitanda
I began to run and noticed too late
Omoi wa Tsunagaru Tabi Kieru
that feelings die when they connect
Futatabi Aeru Hi no
Tame ni Ima o Ikiru yo
I will live in the present for
we may meet in the future
ALIVE SERIOUS AGE
Alive in this serious age
Preview
Book Six
Bastions of Sorrow
A