Book Four
The Land of Disaster
I'll bandage your wounds. You'll feel
some discomfort, but please bear with it.
This should suffice for the time being.
Thank you.
I used to be a Field Medic.
My apologies, but I'm only
versed in emergency first-aid.
Once we return to Irios, you can seek
some more sophisticated treatment.
Erekt, what happened to Cleo?
I'm sorry, but I wasn't able to confirm her condition.
General True uses most of his own money to support the orphanage.
Did you grow up there as well?
Moving right along, you need to be
devoting your time to mastering the Delphine!
I know. I can't even ride a motorcycle,
so the Delphine's all I can rely on.
Since I'm not that keen on dying.
And I don't care to be lectured by a war child anyway.
Why you... And you call yourself a man of Krisna?
Don't you have any balls?
Wanna check?
Y-You imbecile!
The shutters can be open and closed via quartz ligaments...
Don't you think the stars are breathtaking tonight?
Not really.
These are blueprints for Golems and the like.
You don't want to look through your enemy's secret files?
Even if I did, I wouldn't be
able to make sense of them.
And besides, well, I'm not really looking for anything like that...
Anyway, why would you leave me
alone in here after I stole your gun?
Would you prefer the torture chamber?
That's not what I mean.
I betrayed your trust and tried to kill your friend.
Indeed you did.
But I realized something then.
You've never killed anyone before, am I right?
I have no complaints with you staying here.
You're free to make yourself at home.
But if you try to hurt Rygart
again, I won't be so forgiving.
Now then...
Can you eat fish?
Huh?
Yes...
Then let's have supper underneath the stars.
Tokubetsu na Mono wa
This world has
Nani mo Nai Kedo
nothing worth noting
Sono Te ni Tsukamu ni wa
But we have plenty of love
Juubun Sugiru Ai o
on our hands
Shinjiru Mono o
Those who
Motte Iru Mono wa
have faith
Yuruginai Ai no Tame ni
will act on behalf
Tsuranuku Omoi o
of their unwavering love
Unmei ni Tachimukaeru Nara
If I could fight destiny,
Kono Subete Kakeru Omoi de Yuku
I'd act on all of my feelings
General True! Explain this formation!
Calm down, Narvi. Just hear me out!
I'm asking BECAUSE I've already heard!
You're deploying almost all of the
western border defense personnel...
So why am only I being placed on standby in the capital!?
Like I said, just relax!
I'm not excluding you.
You're just going to depart a little later than we are.
So you're telling me to let
you run about unsupervised?
That's not a very nice way to put it.
I've been a general since before you were even born!
You're helpless without me around!
Have you calmed down yet?
I would very much like to have you with me,
but I've volunteered my youngest
and finest soldier for something else.
Volunteered?
The 1st Autonomous Squadron...
Correct.
Your mission will essentially be national defense.
But you will act as an elite commando unit
under the direct control of the King himself.
Heavy Knight 1st Class Narvi,
you've been designated as captain.
Understood.
That's quite a lot of authority, and the
opportunity to prove myself isn't bad either.
I might even be able to enter General True's direct command someday.
Your team will consist of...
Heavy Knight High Class Nyle.
Will you be able to follow Captain Narvi's orders though she is your younger sister?
I will.
She may be somewhat crude, but I will
consider her orders yours, and give it 110%.
I am SO lucky!
Not only is my departure to the front lines delayed,
but I get to gaze upon a bespectacled Lady Sigyn!
Heavy Knight High Class Loggin. Thank you for your support.
Yes ma'am!
Heavy Knight High Class Rygart.
Please follow Captain Narvi's commands.
You got it.
I just gotta do as I'm told, right?
Rygart, carrying our personal
grudges into battle leads to trouble.
If you need to get something off your chest, now's the time.
Huh? Oh, I know.
So if Captain Narvi demands to see my
jewels, I suppose I've got no choice, right?
If you ever show them to me, I'll blow a hole in them.
You mean to tell me this has happened before?
Lady Sigyn snapped...
Counting the soldier not currently present,
this squad will consist of five people.
And regarding the fifth member.
It's still not official, and I myself am opposed to the decision.
But as per the Chief of Staff's strong request, Girghe will--
Girghe!?
Hey, what's going on!?
Girghe, he...
Knock it off!
Who the hell do you think you are!?
Impressive dodging.
I'd rate you over 60 points in defense, but less than 80.
There are several weapons before you.
Pick whichever you like.
Quit screwing around! Like you're giving me a choice!
He sliced the quartz in two!
Give it a rest already!
You fucking psychopath!
It broke...
I  figured as much.
Shit!
This is bad!
Very impressive.
I have to reevaluate your defense.
Above 70 points, but less than 150.
You asshole!
Crap!
Sir Girghe, I don't recall approving of any such exercises.
But please allow me to participate as well.
That was the optimal position to fire from, Lady Narvi.
So very textbook, it makes me sick.
Loggin, your attacks are much too predictable.
But your exemplary covering fire has sealed my escape.
And now...
If I didn't stop, your golem would be short a head.
...and I would've been killed instantly.
There's only one outcome for us Heavy Knights, huh?
I've no desire to fight you blind, Sir Nyle.
Breaking in this Golem has
made for excellent practice.
This guy is my subordinate?
Whew... That was a close one.
What the hell is his problem?
He made a clean cut, but I couldn't do the same.
Rygart.
Is it true you support Girghe being in your squad?
Yeah, but my approval alone doesn't mean anything.
But why? He's a bigger threat than our enemy.
True.
True?
That may be true, but I vowed to do
whatever it takes to drive off Athens.
It'll be fine. Just you watch.
Whoa... They stretch...
So you guys march tomorrow, right?
That's right.
You were at the graveyard this morning, weren't you?
No, must've been someone else.
Don't force yourself to carry the burden for other's deaths.
I told you, you've got the wrong guy.
Do I now?
Yep.
I see you've met your fifth member.
Yeah, but I wouldn't exactly say we "met".
I see...
I just don't understand the guy.
Indeed.
He must have a screw loose or something.
He used to be a prisoner.
I was opposed to releasing him myself.
Seems like everybody hates him.
But I suppose he is pretty messed up.
Last year, he killed several
comrades during a training exercise.
For no reason whatsoever.
None at all?
I'm not really sure how his mind works.
Was he one of your men?
No...
He's my son.
Do NOT trust him, you hear me?
No matter what!
If he acts the least bit suspicious, don't hesitate to kill him!
Forget it!
I'll take full responsibility.
Not happening!
If you don't, you'll wind up dead yourself!
I said forget it!
He...
NO!
No parent should ask someone to kill their own child.
If you want him dead, then do it yourself.
Make up your mind by the next time we meet.
Decide if you're gonna kill him or talk it out.
Stay alive until then, Pops!
I will...
General True, don't do anything stupid!
Since you can't use pressure guns, you'll
have to rely on throwing weapons!
Focus your aim!
If you don't improve your CQC,
you'll die a hundred times over!
Your defense sucks!
My hopes for the future
Hodr!
Hey, Hodr!
overflow from within.
Don't make that face.
I'll come back unharmed for sure.
As my cruel fate hangs heavy overhead.
So I want you to promise me, Hodr...
Don't you dare surrender under those ridiculous conditions. At least wait for me to return.
Alright.
I've made up my mind.
In this fleeting tranquility,
Until you come back, I'll put aside our
differences with Orlando and seek military aid.
I submit to slumber
And I think only of you.
I begin to realize my reasons for fighting
Tomorrow's the day...
I had locked deep in my heart,
And whilst I dream of you,
who rules my unconscious thoughts,
You leave tomorrow, right?
Yeah. I'm actually kind of sad that I gotta leave.
My forgotten grief of the waking world
What'll you do when you return home?
I have to help my dad out on the farm,
so I guess it's back to the life of a dirty peasant for me.
Oh well. It was fun while it lasted.
I-I see...
fades into the sky.
Good luck.
You keep at it here, okay?
You'll become a first-rate magician. I just know it!
First-rate...
You bet! You'll be the commoner's star of hope!
You'll be the best magician in the entire palace!
I... don't really care about being top class...
All I really want... is someone to buy me books every now and then.
Or someone to take me to the library once a month or so. That's all.
So I wouldn't really mind marrying say... a farmer...
Huh? What'd you say?
Don't mumble like that. Speak up so I can hear you.
...never mind.
Oh, okay then.
See you 'round!
I really... wouldn't mind...
He leaves today.
Good morning. Today's the day, isn't it?
Y-yeah, it sure is.
What's wrong? Are you angry about something?
I'm not angry.
But I am upset.
Okayyy...
So why are you upset?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Did I do something?
It isn't your fault.
But you're still upset?
Yeah.
Well, I'm stumped.
If I die out there, it'll haunt you in your sleep.
What can I do to cheer you up?
"Die"...
If you come back unharmed, I'll stop being angry.
Hm?
Alright, you got it.
Fall back to the left!
They've blocked our retreat!
At least save the General!
What was that noise?
Nicely done.
What!? General True's battalion was ambushed by Athens?
That's impossible!
It's still 30 thousand Mehl to the border.
Why would they be ambushed here!?
Did they slip through the border somehow?
What happened to the True Battalion?
It was almost completely annihilated.
General True... Perished in battle.
Millennium Corps, moving out!
I've received your report.
Splendid work, Colonel Io.
My men and I cannot take all the credit for this victory.
Furthermore, the enemy's resistance
is fiercer than we anticipated.
We lost several of our finest soldiers.
You dispatched nearly 50 units from the enemy's main forces.
Those men did not die in vain.
We've received permission to take a short break.
Your unit's been pushed especially hard, so let them rest for a while.
Sir!
You guys are pathetic!
Women don't like guys with such low stamina!
Piss off. Don't go comparing us to a freak like you.
Aren't you all frustrated that a dainty
little gal like me stole your thunder?
"Gal" my ass, you 25-year-old midget!
25 years old.
Still. Makes. Me. A.
A y-y-y-young--
Hm?
A young lady!
Nike!
My ear! MY EAR!!
I was so scared, Colonel! Really, really scared!
But I tried my absolute hardest!
I-Indeed. Good work.
Are you proud? Am I a good girl?
Yes, of course.
You took an enemy General's head.
Once we return, I'm certain you'll be awarded a medal of honor for your achievements.
Then... Can I have my usual reward?
I wanna be praised by you Colonel, even more than
Secretary General Loquis or General Borcuse.
Pardon me, Colonel.
We did receive permission to rest, but is it really
prudent to do so in the middle of enemy territory?
It's fine. The general's forces are
keeping watch for us, so rest assured.
We've been marching for 25 hours
straight. I imagine we're at our limits.
It will likely take about six hours for the
enemy remnants to retreat to their army.
You have precisely four hours to rest!
After that, we resume our attack.
We'll crush Baldr! And then the war will be over!
Krisnan Kingdom's Arracan Desert
That's the signal from our scouts!
Athens forces spotted! Estimated 50 units!
50 Golems?! That's 20 less than we've got!
Captain Elsa! Let's swarm the enemy!
Restrain yourself!
Wait for General Baldr's orders!
Prepare to intercept them with your Pressure Guns!
We've got the high ground!
Do not leave your positions!
Yes sir!
Krisnan forces spotted. Approximately 70 in number.
They're in perfect position to meet our
attack. Impressive as usual, General Baldr.
Charge.
All units, commence operation!
Fire!
They're attempting a Pincer?
General, Captain Elsa, over there!
You can see from here? Is that really him?!
Yes. It distinctly resembles the Commander's
Golem that we spotted crossing the border.
Impossible...
General Baldr.
Forget it, Elsa. It's a blatant challenge!
Yes, I believe it is.
However...
Staring each other down like
this could cost us valuable time.
If we don't act now, we'll never have a chance like this again.
Please lend me 10 Golems before their reinforcements arrive.
Alright. Take 20.
But you're to retreat immediately at the first sign of danger!
Understood?
Yes sir!
What's going on here?
All units, open fire!
What a spectacular attack.
A classic blitz maneuver.
However, your misdirected attack
didn't turn out like you had expected.
Such is war. Your carefully
calculated decision has backfired.
A clear head can be just as much of a hindrance.
A lesson you've just learned the hard way.
E-Elsa squad... annihilated.
A mere six golems defeated Elsa and 20 of ours!
A-And Athens' didn't reform their ranks!
Those bastards didn't even bother protecting their commander!
No, they didn't.
They simply stood by... and watched our jaws drop.
Elsa losing to a mere six golems, and
the bizarre actions of their flanks...
It's no wonder the men are terrified.
Borcuse... Did you plan to gamble for this outcome from the start?
General Baldr, you always
make such rational decisions.
But that is your one and only strength!
My men do not fear opponents who think rationally.
Fear deals a crippling blow to soldiers.
Be it a single man, or a force of one
million soldiers, it makes no difference.
Man can deny neither hunger nor fear.
Nike. You may begin.
Yes, but sir...
General, I do not feel that such actions are necessary!
They are.
Do it, Nike.
Sorry, Colonel.
Oh well, she's already dead anyway.
Technically, you could just call this disassembly!
Borcuse...
That's Captain Elsa's...
Captain Elsa...
Your men are panicking.
And you'll come under fire
whether you charge or retreat.
At this juncture, it's already checkmate for you.
Forgive me, Elsa.
All units, CHARGE!
Did I stutter? All golems, prepare to attack!
Reconnaissance, Supply Teams, and Infantry, standby!
Kill every last enemy before you!
B-But sir, the enemy's...
Alright! Let's move!
Y-Yes sir!
Roger!
Let's take back the Captain's remains!
They've rallied their spirits.
Victory is officially ours.
Perhaps.
However, the soldiers' fear has transformed into rage.
They'll likely fight to their dying breath.
General Baldr, you're so
straightforward it makes me sick.
Moving to intercept.
Colonel Io. We'll continue our discussion later.
I appreciate your concern, but I have no need for it.
Move out!
Roger!
What the fuck is our left flank doing!?
Just ignore their rear guard!
At this rate, we can't link up with the right flank!
We'll make a detour and pursue the enemy's main forces!
Borcuse!
All that's left is to wait for their
separated flanks to enter firing range.
Right.
The day is ours.
God dammit! We're not finished yet, Athens!
Bolster your defenses! Here they come!
Alright, fire!
Don't retreat! Just leave it to the rear support!
Not yet! Hold on a little longer!
They're holding out pretty well!
I'm gonna earn myself a medal today!
Colonel! Hostile to our left!
F-Fire!
Stand your ground!
General Baldr! The enemy's left side ceased their attack!
Is it Rygart?
The left side's being decimated by the enemy!
Dammit, left flank! Get it together!
Just... one hostile?
Ah, it is indeed a single unit.
Hmph. Krisna certainly has
some interesting characters.
Bardess! What kind of man laughs as he watches his comrades die?
Sir! I was merely laughing at my own comment.
I'm terribly sorry, General Borcuse.
Do you understand, Rygart?
Once the third layer of armor's been compromised,
you may treat it as if the frame itself has been damaged.
At that point, you're to purge the armor and withdraw.
I'm already down to my last layer.
But... I have no choice!
I have to become a cold-blooded killer!
He stopped me!
Fire!
Dammit! Purge or not, the armor's not gonna last any longer!
W-What the hell kind of jump is that!?
Guard your vital points and close the distance!
Shit, the nail darts aren't cutting it.
Just piercing them isn't good enough.
Aim for his landing point!
Scatter! We're being sniped!
That's enough, Rygart! Now fall back!
Hey Narvi, that tremor just now was from the Delphine's landing!
They've already started!
We were supposed to initiate the attack...
Loggin and Rygart's team had more
distance to cover. Just what IS that golem?
Nyle, enemy spotted!
Right!
We can't pull off a rear attack,
but we can come in from the side!
Looks like 23 units out there. You sure about this?
Of course! While Baldr acts as a decoy, our squad will take them down!
It's the ideal situation. I can make
a splendid report to General True!
Begin the attack!
Girghe!? What the hell are you doing?
I said begin the attack!
Girghe!
I can't do it.
What?
My legs are cramping. I can't move!
I...I'm scared!
I've never fought in real combat before!
Excellent work, Rygart.
The enemy's left formation has collapsed.
General Baldr's forces have begun regrouping.
This thing's only got six minutes of juice left.
Is this your idea of a joke, Girghe!?
You're scared !?
Since when have you been such a spineless pansy?
Yeah, c'mon man.
Show us that same strength you tried to kill us with!
More like we're screwed if you don't...
T-That was during training! I knew the exact number of enemies!
And besides, that was just a mock battle!
We're in trouble, Narvi! The enemy's spotted us!
Our surprise attack's a bust. Should we retreat?
No, the enemy's still disorganized! You and I can still break through!
Baldr's already noticed us and begun moving!
We'll launch a pincer attack!
Move out!
Roger that!
A golem with a broken blade for a horn that disrupted our tactics...
It's a complete mystery to us, but it's
power and mobility are astounding.
I guess I could call it the Broken Blade for the time being.
That's... Borcuse?
Colonel, the enemy's retreating!
Damn you, Baldr.
He was trying to lure us out.
We can't just watch our right flank be
killed. Very well. You may join them!
Yes sir!
Colonel Io, wait!
It is time.
Aw man, the withdrawal signal?
You're mine!
Two down!
All that's left is for Nyle and I to crush the right flank!
Didn't quite go according to plan though.
Perfect!
Huh?
Nobody's here.
Seems like Baldr's team's in pursuit,
but they're way ahead of us now.
The enemy... retreated?
Dammit! We're late!
Is he running away?
Forget it. Once you drop down to five minutes, you
could run out out of power while in enemy range.
Do not join the pursuit teams.
Why do I feel relieved?
A-Are you okay?
Haven't slept in three days, that's all.
Attach segment 5-86 with the new rivets...
Cleo... help me swap out these parts...
Oh, you mean help you get changed?
Thanks.
What beautiful, black hair...
I think blonde hair is prettier.
You really... think... so?
Untainted by any other shade. Purely black...
Personally, I... truly admire it.
She's Zess' friend, just like that man Rygart.
But she's still my enemy.
I don't understand.
Retreating while we were crushing them? What a load of crap.
Nike, this is a strategic withdrawal.
We're merely going to join up with the
rear guard and some reinforcements.
"Strategic withdrawal". That's such a convenient phrase, isn't it?
What really happened was you all were
getting worked by the black golem.
Nike, stop!
With just one shot,
he found the ideal angle, the collar's thin
armor, and the perfect firing distance.
Nike! 11 o'clock, 80 degrees!
An Artemis?
Nike, run!
You little prick!
Nike!
He's using her as a human shield!
We can't budge an inch like this!
Colonel!
He's a dead-eye.
He's a tough one! Don't go getting picked off now!
I'll squash you like a bug!
Oh boy. It sure is nerve-wracking being this high up.
Well? Can you see the enemy?
It's fine to rely on the Delphine's eyes, but
once I'm down to a minute, I'm coming down.
Now then.
Huh?
I found them!
Girghe...
Korekara no Sekai ni wa
Dare mo Inai
There is no one in the future
Koe Dake o Senaka ni Kanjite
Hearing voices only from behind,
Miwataseba Daichi ni Saku
Hito no Negai
I look up to see wishes
blooming in the land
Fumitsubusu Mono o Sagase
I seek out the ones who
try to stomp on them
Mamorenai Yakusoku
Dake wa Shinai Keshite
because I never make
promises I cannot keep
Hokori Takaki Yume
Kagayaki Korosanu Youni
They're proud dreams,
so I'll make them shine brighter
Kakaeru Kodoku no Tsuyosa
Inochigake no Mirai
while bearing lonely strength
for the irreplaceable future
Furimukazu ni Susumu Beki da to
"Don't just turn around
and move forward"
Kimi ga Yubi Sashita Kanatae to
You pointed me toward
the horizon I needed to follow
Hashiridashite Kigatsuitanda
I began to run and noticed too late
Omoi wa Tsunagaru Tabi Kieru
that feelings die when they connect
Futatabi Aeru Hi no
Tame ni Ima o Ikiru yo
I will live in the present for
we may meet in the future
Dare mo Inai Kaze no Naka
Hitori de Samayou Toride
Wind blows with no one in sight,
and I wander lost in this stronghold
Dare ka Ite mo Onaji Koto
Samayou Basho wa Majiwaranai
Even if there were others, I still
wouldn't wander into their wandering
Furimukazu ni Susumu Beki da to
"Don't just turn around
and move forward"
Kimi ga Yubi Sashita Kanatae to
You pointed me toward the
horizon I needed to follow
Hashiridashite Kigatsuitanda
I began to run and noticed too late
Omoi wa Tsunagaru Tabi Kieru
that feelings die when they connect
Futatabi Aeru Hi no
Tame ni Ima o Ikiru yo
I will live in the present for
we may meet in the future
ALIVE SERIOUS AGE
Alive in this serious age
Preview
Book Five
Death's Horizon
A