It would've been too hard to say
goodbye, so I'm going by myself.
I really enjoyed the talk we had
around the campfire last night.
I thought to myself, "I wish
that this could go on forever. "
But then I got scared all of a sudden.
If something happened and we
were split up, what would happen?
Maybe I'd been relying on
you guys too much all this time.
Would I be able to make it on my own
once this journey ended and I was on my own?
I gave that a lot of thought.
And that's why I'm going by myself.
On the cape to the north, there's
a house standing there by itself.
Go there.
You should hurry. He doesn't have much longer.
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
And now, although it pains me to say it,
I will have to insist that you two die here.
Are you here by yourself?
You got a big pair on ya.
Come. Don't disappoint me.
I want him to understand how we feel.
W-What are you talking about?
I'm saying that this place will be your grave.
" Evanescent Encounter (Part 2)
(The Cycle of Death and Rebirth, Part 2) "
This oughta be fun...
Now I see.
You utilize movements that confound
any attempt to predict them.
But in the martial arts, you must
make better use of your intellect.
When you rely solely upon instinct and reflex,
you involuntarily make your limitations known.
Quit talkin' like you're hot shit!
And now, would you care to
show me your Muju Shin Kenjutsu?
Show me the skill that
struck down Enshiro Mariya.
How did you know about that?
Of course. You're with the Shogunate.
Shit!
Get back here!
Crap...
Who the hell are you?
Mugen...!
We have the girl.
Come to the church on the island. Got it?
Say what? Look, we're kinda busy here!
If you don't hurry, we won't be
responsible for what happens.
You should go there before
she ends up in little pieces!
Don't piss me off!
Go!
I'll take care of things here.
Screw that, you go!
You know, I don't really want
to think about stuff like that.
If you did, that jerk Mugen would...
Sorry... I'm sorry.
Look after Fuu.
What's the matter?
Which of you is going to fight me?
Don't get yourself killed!
You and I have unfinished business, you hear?!
--Get moving!
--Y-Yes, sir!
It seems that we can finally fight
without any distractions now.
How did you know I use the Muju style?
Fate is a fascinating thing.
If you hadn't killed Mariya, the Muju style
would have been mine by now.
As I thought. You're Kagetoki Kariya.
You're going to turn Muju Shin
Kenjutsu into a band of assassins?
Are you telling me to walk the path of darkness?
No, I am telling you that there is no other way.
Serving Master Kariya is the same
as serving the Shogunate itself.
You're splitting hairs.
It would no longer be a martial art.
" Nothing but Swords in One's Mind "
This is no longer the Warring States period.
This land at peace has no need of
kenjutsu styles meant to kill people.
All martial arts schools are in decline.
I ask that you endure this, Jin.
I can't believe it. You were--
Indeed I was.
You're ordering me to kill my pupil?
I intend to pass on the dojo to him. I can't...
As you may have guessed,
it was I who put him up to it.
I see your skills have grown, Jin.
Master...!
In any event, your destiny is to die at my hand.
Very well.
And I expect to see this
so-called Hand of the Gods at work.
Gladly. I've been sitting idle for far too long.
I can't do it... I can't.
Hey, you're that guy from--
I was ordered not to touch you
until you got to the church...
...but the guy that I wanna kill so bad
I can taste it is right under my nose.
I can't hold it in!
I can't... I can't do it...
Why?
Why would a man as skilled as you are
stoop to being the Shogunate's dog?
In this day and age, do you think that
a man can live by his sword skills alone?
In that case, are you saying that you have
a lord that is worth risking your life for?
There is nothing but lords who prize empty
honor and think only of self-preservation.
There are none who are
worth laying down my life--
You're exactly right.
I'm not their puppet.
I'm pretending to be used by them,
when in reality I am using them, that's all.
The age of the samurai will
probably come to an end soon.
I hate to say it, but it looks like
I was born into the wrong era.
I was, as were you.
What's the matter? Is that Ryukyu sword style
of yours useless in tight spaces like this?!
You're a man of considerable skill.
I haven't enjoyed myself
this much in quite some time.
This match will probably be
settled by a razor-thin margin.
It is by a razor-thin margin that you will lose.
His speed is astonishing. And I don't
see a single opening in his defense.
One move... There is only
one move that will end this.
A samurai who smells of sunflowers?
Sunflowers have no smell.
So wouldn't that mean that there's
no samurai who smells of sunflowers?
You're wrong! That can't be true!
Hang in there for a little while longer.
I'll put you out of your misery soon enough.
You people are just wasting
your time by doing this.
Mugen always hacks away without
giving the hostage a second thought.
Oh, he does, does he?
Then I suppose that means that it won't
make any difference if I kill the hostage.
Well, even if I don't kill you, there's always
the option of leaving you half dead.
After all, all that matters
is that you're alive.
Mugen!
You're gonna give her back.
So, we meet at last. That makes me so happy.
Who the hell are you people?
Don't play dumb with me.
Even if you've forgotten, the three of us
will never forget until the day we die.
Listen. We three brothers were fairly
well-known down in the domain of Satsuma.
And then...
We were in charge of that raw sugar ship.
The ship that you and Mukuro boarded.
Thanks to you, our older
brother ended up like this.
We were suspected of being responsible
for the raid and were driven out of Satsuma.
Our chances for government
service went up in smoke, too.
Our only reason for living now
is to track you down and kill you.
Look, about your other brother...
I sent him to the bottom of
the sea a few minutes ago.
Y-You bastard!
Don't you understand? We don't give
a rat's ass about this girl's life.
Hold it.
I'll put down my sword.
In return, let the girl go.
What did you say?
You can't...
Get going. You haven't met
the Sunflower Samurai yet, right?
I can't do that... I can't leave you.
Cut the crap. What do you think
we came all this way for?
Get your ass moving!
But... They're going to...
I ain't gonna die. Have some faith in me.
--Mugen...
--Beat it.
Get going.
Run, bitch!
Aw. you're gonna make me cry.
You're throwing your life away for a woman?
Have it your way, then.
I'll kill you nice and slowly.
Oops! Maybe I cut too deeply.
Come on, let me have some more fun with you!
Bastard...
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels
Spring is announced when the
wild plants break out in a dance
Summer comes to Uji, and in the fields
are patterns of grass set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
I can still see the too-distant blue sky
when I close my eyes (It was so warm)
As I reminisce, I take your hand
as I pluck flowers and sing
Within the memories that
are now coming back to me
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Spring is announced when the
mountain leaves break out in dance
Summer comes to Uji, and textiles with
plains grass patterns are set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels