Come on, let me have some more fun with you!
Bastard...
" Evanescent Encounter (Part 3)
(The Cycle of Death and Rebirth, Part 3) "
Shit...
I'm gonna teach you how we felt...
...when we had to live in disgrace.
I'm going to ruin your life.
Just like you ruined ours!
Who's there?
Um... Are you Seizo Kasumi?
No, I'm not.
This is no place for a young lady
like you. You should go home.
I came here to see someone.
I came from so far away to see him...
Wait a minute, are you--
Wait here a moment.
Careful, now!
I can't have you croaking on me that easily.
And now I'm going to teach you your lesson.
I'm gonna teach you how it feels to be
disgraced, and yet have to go on living.
What a load of crap...
I've lived with every kind
of disgrace you can think of.
There ain't one damn thing
that you can possibly teach me!
You want me to have a taste of how
you feel? Quit talking like a pussy!
When you point a sword at somebody,
you kill them or they kill you. End of story.
I don't wanna hear any bitching from
somebody who can't deal with that!
Hey, that was dirty, keeping
a dagger hidden in there!
Aw, man... So much for my ace in the hole.
Is someone here?
Yes. A young girl who says that she has
traveled a great distance to see you, Seizo.
What would you like me to do?
If you like, I can have her come back later.
No, that's all right. Send her in.
I'm sorry, you'll have to
forgive me for not getting up.
Who might you be?
I'm sorry, but my eyes
can't see much these days.
Ever since I was a little girl,
my mother and I lived by ourselves.
I had always been told that
my father had died long ago.
But that wasn't true.
He was alive, and he had
abandoned Mother and me.
That's what Mother told me when she lay dying.
Even now, when people ask me about
my father, I say that I don't have one.
I don't consider myself his daughter.
Even if I met him, I wouldn't want
to hear any excuses from him.
I'll never be able to
forgive him for what he did.
I'm sure that he doesn't know about how
we suffered or how Mother got sick and died.
That's why I swore that when I met him,
I would make sure that he understood.
That when I met him, I would
belt him one, no matter what.
That's what I had planned, but now...
This isn't fair... I can't do anything to you.
Not when you're so sick.
Fuu...
I don't think we'll see each other again.
Goodbye.
God, please hear my prayer...
Once is all I ask.
When I grow up, please let
me meet my father someday.
As I suspected, you must be Seizo's daughter.
He's talked about you a great deal.
Seizo has always been...
W-Who are you?
--Wait!
--Don't!
Let go!
Seizo Kasumi, I presume?
I am Guard Captain Kagetoki Kariya.
By order of the Shogun,
I have come to take your life.
Cut away. I'm as good as dead already.
Do you have any last words?
Fuu.
I have no right to ask for your forgiveness.
But a day hasn't gone by when I haven't
thought of you and your mother.
I'm sorry.
Come out here!
After killing Kasumi, my orders are to
eliminate all family members and retainers.
W-Wait a minute!
That hurt, damn it!
You don't know when to quit!
You wanna play hide and seek again?
Are you ready?
No, not yet!
Found ya!
This ends here!
You're pissing me off!
Mugen...!
You have my gratitude for leading me here.
If you are truly the daughter of a samurai,
choose to die a brave death.
Y-You son of a...
Jin!
You have my compliments.
You managed to save your life
by somehow avoiding a fatal blow.
In your current condition,
though, you can't hope to best me.
Why are you here?
Are you trying to throw away the life
that you so narrowly managed to keep?
There are no lords worth risking your life for.
As I recall, that's what you said.
Yes... For my whole life,
I've fought only for myself.
My study of the sword was for no one but myself.
But now...
This is the last lesson
that I have to teach you.
That lesson is the one
and only way to kill an enemy
that you have no hope of winning against.
You probably won't defeat him, but it is
possible that you will take him with you.
You leave a small opening in your
defense and allow yourself to be struck.
When that happens, it will create a brief
opening, and that is when you strike.
Your chances of survival are virtually zero.
If at all possible,
don't ever use this technique.
I swear, I always get the
short end of the stick...
You bastard...
Jin!
I can't believe it...
You allowed yourself to be struck...
Mugen!
What, it's you guys again?
I can't move anymore.
I think this might really be my time to go...
Mugen?
Mugen! Mugen!
You're alive...!
Oh, it's you? I thought you
were Death for a second...
It seems like all I ever do is cry.
And here I was trying to make it on my own...
You dumb broad...
Did you meet the Sunflower Samurai?
You did, huh...?
A promise is a promise.
Now it's time to settle things with you.
So it would seem.
Ain't we a sorry sight...
You can say that again.
The truth is, Seizo wanted to bring
you and your mother with him.
But if he had, you would have been hounded
by the Shogunate's Christian hunts, too.
That's why he came here by himself.
The picture I had of my father in my
memories was of a big and strong man.
But when I actually met him,
he wasn't anything like that.
He was really small and frail.
But I still sensed that he really was my father.
Are you awake?
Yeah...
It would seem that this isn't Hell...
This feels so weird...
Up until now, whenever I met
somebody who was tougher than me,
I couldn't rest until I'd killed the guy.
But now...
I don't feel like killin' you at all.
I, too, feel as if I've finally found what
I've been searching for all this time.
I have been alone my entire life...
You are the first friends I have ever made.
Hey, you two are awake!
You've certainly gotten a lot of sleep.
You've been out for nearly a whole week.
We have...?
I'm starving... Gimme something to eat.
Well, see ya.
Until we meet again.
Um, listen... There's something
that I haven't told you.
As in?
Way back when we started this trip,
we made a bet, remember?
Toss this coin, and if it comes up heads,
hack away all you want.
But if it comes up tails,
both of you will stay with me.
Are we clear?
It's tails!
The thing is... It actually came up heads.
--Say what?!
--You didn't...!
That's all.
She had us completely fooled.
What did we even come on this trip for?
Well, bye! I hope we meet again!
Yeah, good morning!
I wake up alone beneath my down covers
And drop the record needle onto another new life
The streetlights that still burn dimly are a
guideline that's a restlessly ticking hour hand
Boredom is a bunch of facts,
scenery I've seen once
Actors and actresses looking back on the past
I wouldn 't miss it for the world
Get up, get up!
Walking, sleeping, keep on movin ' slowly
Good morning and good sunshine
The borderlines that blur
from midnight to morning
Are individuals looking for different answers
The cycle that walks around the Earth
is the sun beyond that white line
Isn 't there something missing?
Something I don 't understand?
Uncertain, I go off in search of them,
and found myself playing in my bare feet
And the night wakes up once again
From dawn to dusk, hello!
Wanna melt down this totally
outrageous darkness?
The moon 's jasmine jumps across the
faintly moving sky, lands, and goodnight
Get up, get up! Walking...
Sleeping, keep on movin'...
"The End "