Vagrant Mugen.
And vagrant ronin Jin.
The aforementioned two parties will
hereby be executed by beheading,
and their heads put on display!.
Well? Feeling any regret?
Do you feel like throwing yourselves at
my feet and begging for forgiveness now?
If living means bowing down
to the likes of you bastards...
...then I'll die on my feet
with my head held high!
That was well said. I'm with him.
Very well, then.
As you wish, I'll send you
straight to the afterlife!
"Tempestuous Temperaments
(Sturm und Drang)"
Hey, aren't my dumplings ready yet?
Yes, sir! Coming right up!
Hey, baby, let's have some fun!
C'mon, don't give me that frown...
--No way!
--Sorry for the wait!
What kept you, idiot?
I-I'm sorry...
--Where are my dumplings?!
--Coming!
Man, this place is boring...
It sure is.
Isn't there anything fun to do around here?
Geez, what's the deal with
these customers today?
Now, now, Fuu, ijust bear with it.
But they--
That blonde boy is the son
of the prefectural governor.
Check it out, it's brand new!
Hey, nice!
I kinda want to do a test cut with it.
What're you lookin' at?
Hey! I'm talkin' to you, old man!
Ouch! Hot!
That got him!
Hey, you people!
G-Governor, I beg of you!
If I lose this construction ijob,
my whole family will have to commit suicide!
Please, sir!. Please!.
What's this supposed to be?
Um, well...
This chicken feed isn't money!
Hey! Go and get rid of that insolent peasant.
Don't. You might not want
to hear it, but ijust let it go.
See those bodyguards of the governor's?
They're famous even in Edo as being
top-class fighters, even among the Yagyu.
Even if those samurai over there worked
together, they couldn't take them down.
Understand?
Welcome!
Water.
Water?
Yeah, water.
Um, I'm sorry, but we don't serve
customers who only order water.
If you've got no money, try somewhere else--
50 dumplings. How about it?
Let's make a deal. I'll take
care of those guys for you.
--But...
--What?
Maybe for 20...
Are you kidding me? I won't go a dumpling lower.
Hey, where's my tea?!
Yes, sir, coming right up!
What was that for?
I'm sorry. It wasn't on purpose.
I don't wanna hear it.
How are you gonna make up for this?
Um...
Well, maybe I'll take a finger for my trouble.
--C'mon, hold still...
--H-Hey, what're you doing? Cut it out!
Master, let me do it.
I was hoping to give this a test cut anyway.
S-Somebody...
Help me...
Don't make a fuss.
You'll lose more than a finger.
Well, now, what'll it be?
Your nose, maybe? An ear? Or maybe even your...
That money should be enough for you.
Like they say, it costs six mon to
cross the Sanzu, the river of the dead.
Damn it...
Move it. You're blocking the road.
Who the hell are you?
Are you trying to interfere?
To serve your lord and do
his bidding... Is that honor?
Of course it is.
Even if that lord is a piece-of-shit nobody?
--What did you say?!
--Hey, watch that tongue of yours!
Cutting down a man who's done nothing wrong...
Is that what you spent all those
years honing your skills for?
Why, you little...
To be blunt, I think you're worthless.
--We don't have to answer to you!
--Say your prayers!
A hundred dumplings!
Geez, your lives ain't worth squat.
Say what?
That's the price I'm getting for your lives.
What's that work out to, five dumplings a pop?
The numbers don't add up...
Are you trying to make me mad, buddy?
You sure got some balls.
Maybe I'll break in my sword on you!
Let's see you try.
I won't give you any of that crap
about attacking me one at a time.
Come at me all at once!
--You son of a...
--Don't screw with us!
C'mon!
Oh, crap!
Hey, what's the matter?
What are you, some kinda moron?
You don't get it. You ijust
don't get it, do you, buddy?
My old man's the governor around here.
Folks who lay a finger on me pay the price.
Hell, I guess they don't live
to see the next sunrise.
Get it now?
That's right, this ain't the
damn warring states period.
Folks who swing swords around in this
day and age are nothing but anachronistic--
Do you understand what I ijust said?
Not a word.
You've got to! It's common sense around here!
Your common sense don't mean jack to me.
I hail from the Ryukyu islands.
W-Wait, wait, wait! Wait just a minute!
Do you want money?
I'll give you as much as you want!
So ijust wait! Okay?
You...
I'll keep these.
S-Some...
Somebody! Somebody seize that man!
You bunch of cowards!
Listen, my old man's got three Yagyu
badasses on his payroll right now.
What's the matter? You scared?
You feel sorry now?
--I'm sorry!
--Hey, gimme your hand.
All right, listen up!
You guys ain't worth my time.
You have until the count of ten
to go bring those badasses here!
I'll be waiting right here,
counting on his fingers.
Here's one...
And two...
And three!
And four!
This is boring...
What the hell, let's do 'em all!
W-Wait a minute!
Y-You wouldn't happen to be one of
the Yagyu swordsmen, would you...?
I see you're in the middle of something.
Pardon the interruption.
Are you one?
One of those so-called badasses?
You've got the wrong man.
If it's the Yagyus you want,
they died ijust recently.
They're dead?
I was the one who killed them.
All the better!
Mr. Ryuijiro?
Burn...!
Burn to the ground!
Talk about your tailor-made settings...
Aren't you going to run?
Hey, don't put yourself out on my account, ijack.
Crap!
Damn, that's cold!
Huh?
What the hell? What's going on?
Don't you remember?
That was a dream, right? There was a fire, and--
That was no dream.
Oh, right. And you were there in a
bathtub with your dong hanging out...
That was a dream.
I only wish it were a dream.
My son ended up burning to death in that fire.
I have to pay you back in full for that.
As luck would have it, this place used to
be called the torture department store.
I'm gonna take real good care of you
until your execution tomorrow.
Fuu.
This is bad news for you, too, isn't it?
No, it's no big deal.
You don't have any relatives,
so if you like, why don't you come with us?
No, that's okay. This helped me make up my mind.
I swear, you're the lowest of the low...
Say what?
Your stance leaves you wide open,
and your movements are completely inefficient.
Everything about the way
you fight is a total mess.
You son of a...
I swear, I've never fought
anyone as wild as you.
Are you trying to piss me off...?
You're also the first person
I wasn't able to kill.
The name's Mugen. Remember it.
--Mugen.
--Yeah.
My name is Jin. You'd do well to remember it.
Please!
Forget it. No one's allowed
to see the prisoners.
Could you bend the rules for me?
Just for a minute. A few seconds, even.
--Pretty please!
--Forget it!
I'm begging you! I'll do anything!
Anything?
You will?
Then how about some se--
Not that.
What the hell?! You said you'd
do anything, you little bitch!
What's your problem, you bald old fart?!
I'm not bald! This is a hairstyle!
Thanks for the help, Momo!
Oh, wow... They really put you
through the wringer, didn't they?
Hey, you're...
...that girl from the teahouse.
Do you want to know why I'm here?
--Not really.
--Oh, really? Goodbye, then.
I'm kidding! Hold up!
Listen, if you promise you'll do something
for me, I'll help you get out of here.
Are you serious?
--And?
--I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sure she said something
about seeing the prisoners--
--Find her!
--Yes, sir!
Huh? It's not turning...
So, what's this promise you want us to make?
There's a samurai who smells of sunflowers.
I want you to find him for me.
Sunflowers?
--Find her?
--Is she over there?
Hurry.
What happened?
It broke off.
I found her!
--Oh, crap!
--Hold it!
Why the hell did she even bother coming here...?
What's it say, what's it say?
Public execution?
At sunset today, it says!
What am I gonna do?
What're you talking about?
I can't sell this stuff to amateurs!
All right, damn it! You know I'm an Edo-ite!
Take 'em and go, you little thief!
Really?!
Thank you so much!
I'm gonna borrow this for a minute, mister!
Hey!
Have you made your peace?
Hell, every time the sun
comes up, I think to myself...
" Is today gonna be the last
time I'll ever lie in the sun?"
Vagrant Mugen! And vagrant ronin Jin!
The aforementioned two parties will
hereby be executed by beheading,
and their heads put on display!
Well? Feeling any regret?
Do you feel like throwing yourselves at
my feet and begging for forgiveness now?
If living means bowing down
to the likes of you bastards...
...then I'll die on my feet
with my head held high!
That was well said. I'm with him.
Very well, then.
As you wish, I'll send you
straight to the afterlife!
What the--?
Hey. I'll put our fight on hold
until we get outta here.
You intend to kill all these men?
I swear, you really are the lowest of the low...
You two fools!
Don't even think that you'll
make it out of here alive!
--Hey, what's going on?
--What's happening?
Fire! A light! Somebody give me a light!
Here, take this!
Come back here!
Hey, hold it!
Hold it right there...
What are you doing?! Kill them! Kill them both!
W-Wait a minute! Is it money you're after?
I-If you want money,
I'll give you as much as you want!
You'd try the patience of a saint...
...but I'm no saint!
Crap, there's no end to these guys...
Hey.
What's she--?
Okay... Now it's your turn.
Right.
Hey, wait a minute!
Hey, you two haven't forgotten
your promise to me, have you?!
There's something that I have to see to first.
Yeah, lemme kill this bastard first.
Hey, wait a minute! What if you
two end up killing each other?!
Who would go with me then?!
All right, then.
Toss this coin, and if it comes up heads,
hack away all you want.
But if it comes up tails,
both of you will stay with me.
Are we clear?
Gimme that.
Don't you think you tossed it a bit too far?
The man doesn't know the meaning of restraint.
Kiss my ass.
I mean, it's taking forever to come down!
Ouch!
There they are! Hold it!
You're under arrest!
Crap!
It's tails! I win!
Spring is announced when the
wild plants break out in a dance
Summer comes to Uji, and in the fields
are patterns of grass set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
I can still see the too-distant blue sky
when I close my eyes (It was so warm)
As I reminisce, I take your hand
as I pluck flowers and sing
Within the memories that
are now coming back to me
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Spring is announced when the
mountain leaves break out in dance
Summer comes to Uji, and textiles with
plains grass patterns are set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels