Place your bets, place your bets!
This is the last of our savings,
got it? Be careful with it!
Bet on three!
Don't be stupid. Five.
You do everything you can to
get on my nerves, don't you?
That's my line.
You bastard... One of these days,
I'm gonna make you cry uncle.
Cry uncle? Does anyone actually say that?
I've never heard that expression.
--Say what?!
--Hey, this isn't the time!
Let's play!
No way! We actually won!
Awesome!
I could have sworn that an animal--
No, it must be my imagination.
"A Risky Racket (Surrounded on all Sides)"
Welcome!
--Tempura noodles for me!
--Shippoku noodles!
Hanamaki noodles for me. With a
double order of shrimp tempura.
Got it! Coming right up!
Our first food in three days...
We'll be doing more than smelling it this time!
We're gonna be able to eat it, too...!
--Hey, watch it!
--That's what you get for spacing out!
What a jerk!
Thanks for waiting! Three bowls comes to 50 mon!
--Here we go!
--Good.
Hey, now, pay up front.
Sure, sure, not a problem.
--Huh?
--What's the matter?
C'mon, pay the man.
I can't believe it!
I've been pickpocketed!
It was that guy just now!
Say what?!
Where'd the bastard go?!
Hold it.
Excuse me?
My apologies.
Bastard!
Son of a--
W-What's your problem?!
Ouch...
Wrong guy...
Geez! What's the big idea,
beating up innocent people?
Piece of cake.
You dumbass!
Look at you, clutching your wallet
and looking around nervously!
It's the same as shouting, " Look at me,
I'm carrying something valuable! "
I-I'm sorry, big guy...
I swear, I've never seen
anybody as stupid as you.
Listen, it's times when you're
carrying something this valuable
that you gotta walk along with a look on
your face that says it ain't worth anything.
--Hey, watch it!
--Sorry, buddy!
Watch where you're going!
So anyway, you do it like--
--It's gone!
--Huh? What's gone?
That little punk!
You idiots, what're you standing
around for?! Go after him!
Y-Yes, sir!
C'mon, let's give up already. It was
money we won by gambling, anyway.
No way in hell.
A man can't fight on an empty stomach.
There's no sign of him!
Big guy! He's not over here, either!
You morons! Are you trying
to ruin my reputation?!
If the boss finds out about this,
cutting off all the fingers on both my hands
won't be enough to make up for it!
I don't believe it...
Hey! Where the hell are you, you little punk?!
Get your ass out here!
Hey, does a young guy live here?
You people barge into a
stranger's home without asking...
Have you ever heard of the word " manners"?
Besides, I don't have a son.
I'll have to ask you to leave!
Our apologies.
--Any luck?
--He isn't here.
--Must've been a bogus tip.
--Oh...
We'll go give the area another once-over.
You stake out the place from over there.
What? By myself?
--Yes.
--Good luck.
Hey, wait!
Hey, this is the real deal!
Shinsuke, what are you doing
with something this dangerous?
I need the money.
Let me think... My broker fee will be 70.
I'll fence it for you for that much.
Seventy percent?! You're kidding!
You can't go through legal
channels with this, you know?
Besides, how would a rookie like
you be able to fence this? Huh?
All right.
Come back tomorrow. I'll have
the deal set up by then.
Shinsuke?
What, you're still up?
Have you been out working until this hour?
Something like that.
If this latest job works out,
it'll make me a lot of money.
Then I'll be able to buy you better medicine.
A while ago, some strange
men came here to see you.
Who were those people?
Beats me.
Then what did they want with you?!
What're you doing? Don't
overexert yourself. Go to sleep.
Shinsuke, you aren't--
Aren't what?
You aren't doing things that would make you too
ashamed to look people in the eye, are you?
What're you saying?
I'd never do anything like that.
Don't worry about me,
just worry about your health.
Hey.
See him?
No, no one came.
I guess that's that.
There was a stable up the road, remember?
We'll spend the night there.
Sure...
Who are you?
Um, I'm sorry.
Are you... Shinsuke's girlfriend?
--I'm...
--I see...
I suppose he's that age now.
That's so good!
I've never seen anyone look so happy
over eating dried sweet potatoes.
I'm sorry...
--If you don't mind eating
these, eat all you like.
--Yes, ma'am!
Still, I'm amazed that he found
himself such an adorable girlfriend.
About that...
He doesn't have a father,
and I have this frail body...
That's given him a difficult life,
even though he's really still at that age where
a boy wants his parents to take care of him.
Well, well... So, he's doing
the things that young men do.
Has he talked to you about anything lately?
A-About what?
No, never mind. I'm sorry.
It's just that he's seemed
a little strange lately.
I've been giving her this medicine every day,
following your instructions
to the letter, Doctor,
but she isn't getting any better.
I never said that this would cure her.
With this medicine, the best you can hope for
is that she might regain some of her strength.
There's nothing I can do. That's all
you can buy with the money you have.
There are better medicines available, of course.
For instance, there's Korean ginseng,
which is said to be a cure-all.
It costs a hundred times as much
as this medicine here, though.
Can you afford something like that?
I'm sorry, but I am running a business here.
Hey, are you the guy they call Hikoichi?
What do you want?
I'm looking for something.
Where'd you hear about me?
It's something that's way too much for
a small-time fence like you to handle.
Oh?
Don't play dumb with me!
I know that pickpocket punk
came to see you yesterday!
I... I don't know who you're talking about!
What do you think you're doing?!
Oh, you'll feel like talking soon enough.
I told you I don't know who he is, didn't I?!
Stop it! Put it out!
See? You feel like talking now, don't you?
Hey, you!
Do you remember who I am?
--Who are you?
--The girl whose wallet you stole!
You can't get away from me.
--Let go of me!
--The hell I will!
--You bitch!
--Hey there.
You're a hard man to find.
You've been a bad boy. You oughta
return what doesn't belong to you, got it?
Who the heck are you guys?
Careful, miss. I think you
know what I'll do if you shout--
--Help me! Somebody!
--You crazy bitch!
Big guy!
Bastard!
You little--
--What's all the ruckus?!
--Oh, crap! It's the heat!
What's going on here?!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Damn it...
Back off!
Stay away! If you come
any closer, I'll slit her throat!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Give yourself up peacefully!
Kiss my ass! Don't come any closer! Got it?!
Do you hear me?! If you come near me,
I'm really gonna kill this girl!
--Hey, you're bleeding!
--Shut your mouth.
But...
It's no big deal!
What do you want us to do, big guy?
Should we storm the place?
Don't be stupid! What the hell are you thinking?
We have to get the stuff back
without the cops spotting us!
Are you in pain?
It's nothing.
That look on your face says otherwise.
Don't you get it?
If I have to, I'm gonna kill you.
I met your mother.
If she knew you were picking pockets,
I bet it would break her heart.
Did... Did you tell her that I'm a pickpocket?!
Of course I couldn't tell her that.
I don't want to make a
good mother like her worry.
Don't talk like you know what I'm going through.
I do.
You should be grateful that your mother's alive.
Where are your parents?
My father hasn't been around for a long time.
And my mother died a year ago.
I disobeyed my mother all the time.
I made her worry about me all the time.
All those things that I really wanted
to tell her... That I wanted to ask her...
Now I'll never be able to.
I need money.
There weren't any legitimate places
that would hire a kid like me.
The only people who say that
money doesn't matter in this world
are the ones with lots of it.
Without money, you can't even buy good medicine.
And that's the ugly truth of the matter.
Attention, criminal!
This is your final warning!
If you haven't surrendered within a minute
of sundown, we will storm the place!
Got that?
--What's the deal?
--Well, you see, a girl was taken hostage.
See, there she is!
That little--
This explains why we haven't seen her all day.
Hey!
Stay away! You hear me?!
We found you, you pickpocketing bastard!
Hey, hold it! Where are you going?!
I got unfinished business with that guy!
You ought to surrender.
There's nowhere for you to run now.
Forget it. I can't get arrested
by those guys, not now.
Then I'll be a decoy!
You run away while I have everybody's attention.
Why would you--
We can't have that.
You're not getting away this time.
We don't have time to fool around.
Hand over the stuff right now!
Outta my way!
Who is that guy?
An idiot.
Found ya!
Who are you guys? Move it!
Wait! Let the boy go!
Wha--?
--Big guy!
--Enough of this! Kill 'em all!
You can have it back!
Ow!
--Stop in the name of the law!
--You're under arrest!
You guys are startin' to piss me off!
This way!
My opium...!
Hey.
If I ever see you again,
I'll repay you for what you did today.
So...
...don't forget about me, okay?
Same to you! Remember me!
He got away! After him!
Stop in the name of the law!
You can't get away!
Back off! Stay away from me!
Stay away!
Oh, it's you. Is something wrong?
No, I...
Shinsuke hasn't come home.
Did something happen to him?
It's no big deal. I just came by to say hello.
Well, see you. I'll come back later.
He isn't coming back, is he?
He isn't coming back.
It's all right. Deep down,
I've always expected it.
I had a feeling that something
like this would happen someday.
He was doing something bad, wasn't he?
And he paid the price for it,
right? That's why he--
You're wrong. He's-- Shinsuke was--
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels
Spring is announced when the
wild plants break out in a dance
Summer comes to Uji, and in the fields
are patterns of grass set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
I can still see the too-distant blue sky
when I close my eyes (It was so warm)
As I reminisce, I take your hand
as I pluck flowers and sing
Within the memories that
are now coming back to me
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Spring is announced when the
mountain leaves break out in dance
Summer comes to Uji, and textiles with
plains grass patterns are set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels