I can't believe those two...
Where are they off loafing around this time?
They damn well oughta bring
back a loaf, that's for sure...
They're finally back, huh?
Hey, where have you two--
Help me...
Hey!
Pull yourself together! C'mon!
We went easy on her 'cause she's a woman,
and she turns around and makes fools of us...
Hey, look.
Hey, what's the big idea,
barging in here like this?
Who are you?
I-I was traveling,
and I came across this abandoned hut.
Cut that out!
Who are you two?
A woman came here, am I right?
I don't know anything about a woman.
Don't play dumb with us, damn it!
Little lady, if you lie to us, you're gonna
get more than a needle in your eye.
I said that I don't know who
you're talking about, didn't I?
--Let's go.
--Huh? But we haven't...
It's okay.
Big guy!
" Unholy Union (Karmic Justice) "
What's up with this line?
Our Father, who art in Heaven...
Next!
Hey, what do you two think you're doing?
What's this?
What's it look like? It's a Fumi-e,
a picture you step on as a test.
--Do you get it now?
--Nope.
Look, it's a test to determine whether
or not you're a hidden Christian!
If we're clear on that, step on the thing!
No way.
What did you say?
I can't stand being told what to do.
Don't cause a commotion.
Step on it and be done with it.
--Screw that.
--In that case, don't step on it.
If somebody tells me not to step on
something, it makes me want to do it, but...
Quit screwing around!
Take these two away!
You want a piece of me?
You're willing to expose the extent of your
stupidity by starting a pointless squabble?
Try to rein in your attempts at self-promotion.
What did you say?
I see that it is time for me to step in!
What the...?
To right the wrongs in this land,
I have crossed the seven seas!
Yes, I am the man who has been called
God's representative here on Earth!
I am the grandson of Francisco Xavier!
Xavier the Third!
What're you--
He's wanted across the country
for interfering with Fumi-e tests!
He is?
Hiyo!
Arrest that man!
To oppose my work...
...is to oppose God's work!
The punishment for which is death!
What the hell was that about?
Don't ask me.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I don't know what I can do to repay you.
That's okay, you don't need to do anything.
I get chased and captured by
guys like those all the time, too.
Actually, I have a couple of would-be
bodyguards to deal with that.
They're useless bums, though.
They always show up too late.
They went out for supplies
and still haven't come back.
I'm Fuu.
My name is Yuri.
Um... What is that?
Hm? Oh, this?
Somebody once told me that I
shouldn't show it around too much.
Where did you get that skull?
I guess you could call it an heirloom,
or something that someone left behind.
Is this something important?
Try looking into the eyes of the skull.
--What do you see inside?
--An X?
A cross. The Cross of Golgotha.
It's a Christian good luck charm.
They've been handed down
for years at Ikitsuki Island,
the homeland of the hidden Christians.
Ikitsuki Island?
It's a little island in Nagasaki province.
Yuri, I'm looking for a samurai
who smells of sunflowers.
I wonder if you mean Seizo Kasumi?
You know him?!
Thought you could pull one over on us, did'ja?!
You two bitches tried to make fools of us!
We're gonna pay you back and then some!
Hey, don't kill her. We're clear on that, right?
Stop it!
You wanna fight, huh?
I-If you don't back off right now, I'm gonna use
my Maiden Swordplay of Certain Death on you!
Hey, wake up, damn it!
You're too late!
You're sure she wasn't pulling one over on you?
She told me. She said that she knew
the samurai who smells of sunflowers.
In any case, it's gotten late.
If we keep aimlessly wandering around,
we'll only end up lost.
But we have to...
Excuse us, did a woman come to this village?
She was being chased by a
couple of fishy guys with guns.
I'm sure you must be mistaken.
If people like that had come here, this whole
village would be in an uproar by now.
You sure you didn't dream the whole thing?
It wasn't a dream!
It's late. If you like, please feel free
to stay the night at my home.
Well, I guess we'll take you up on that.
This is odd.
Their security is far too tight for
a village deep in the mountains.
You sure you're not getting
worried over nothing?
I hope you're right.
Hey, are you in here?
Thank you!
Okay, everyone. Please listen.
Up until now, it was believed that you could
gain entry into Heaven
merely by believing in God.
But no more! Oh, what a calamity!
In recent years, Heaven has grown overpopulated.
And now, due to the land shortage, it is no
longer possible for just anyone to get in.
And so, the passport that will
get you into Heaven is these guns!
It is the the number of these
divine guns that you produce
that will decide whether
or not you will enter Heaven!
My words, those of Francisco Xavier's grandson,
are true beyond the shadow of a doubt!
Well, well, what have we here?
What do you think?
If these were European imports, they would
cost you somewhere around 20 ryo.
But for you, I'll cut you a special deal
and let you have these for 1 5.
I like how you do business.
Consider this the down payment.
Why are you doing this?
What do you hope to get out of it?
Money, of course! Money!
Honestly, nothing rakes in
the money quite like religion.
Simply mention God's name,
and you can get away with anything.
And by working with hidden Christians, I don't
have to worry about being exposed, either.
Truly, I am thankful to God!
Just look at this! Look at my collection!
Shotoku Taishi's dentures! They cost 5,000 ryo.
The three arrows of Motonari Mouri!
Complete with certificate of authenticity!
These cost 7,000 ryo!
A folding screen that belonged to the Buddhist
priest Sojun Ikkyu. This was 20,000 ryo.
The straw sandals belonging to Nobunaga
that Hideyoshi held to his chest to warm up.
Hideyoshi and Nobunaga!
Two famous names on one item!
They cost me 30,000 ryo!
Oh, no matter how much money
you make, it's never enough.
And you think that you can buy
my heart with that money, too?
Indeed I do.
It seems that poor people don't understand this,
but there is nothing that money cannot buy.
Of course, even love can be bought.
I am going to make you my wife.
I won't!
Do you want to end up the
same way that your father did?
You see, the theory goes that if money
doesn't work, there is always violence.
What's the matter? Aren't you
supposed to turn the other cheek?
Understand, Momo?
Make sure that you deliver this to those two.
Yuri! Are you all right?
Fuu? What are you doing here?
I will wait until nightfall.
Whether today will be the anniversary of your
wedding or your death is entirely up to you.
I can't believe that I got
you mixed up in this, too...
No, I came here because I
wanted to ask you something.
I have to know. I have to know about
the samurai who smells of sunflowers.
You little furball!
Where have I seen your mug before?
Hey.
Hey, stay out of this!
Isn't this Fuu's pet flying squirrel?
Her pet what?
" Help me --Fuu "
More to the point...
...where the hell are we supposed
to go?! That little moron!
For us Christians, Ikitsuki Island
was our final sanctuary.
Hidden Christians who had been
persecuted and had nowhere else to turn
began gathering there in large numbers.
My father and I were among them.
As was Seizo, who was also known as
the samurai who smelled of sunflowers.
" Police"
In the confusion that followed,
my father and I escaped here to this area.
That was the last that I saw of Seizo.
Do you know where he is now?
I don't. That happened many years ago.
I don't know if he's still on the island,
or if he died that night.
The next Fumi-e test will be at Shimonoseki.
I'm looking forward to seeing
another entertaining show there.
An over-the-top performance is the best
way to obtain new believers, you see.
Give our best regards to the governor.
What, that whole thing was a sham?
W-Who the hell are you two?
Oops!
We're looking for our companion.
Hey, now!
You're gonna take us to her.
Say, you mentioned earlier that you
came here with your father, didn't you?
My father... is dead.
He was killed by that man.
Father was a gunsmith.
He had learned that Xavier the Third was
making deals with the local lord in secret,
and Xavier had him eliminated to silence him.
Perhaps... this is our fate.
You're kidding...
When I saw a chance, I took it and tried
to escape, but I was captured right away.
Maybe this is all a trial meant to test us.
Have you made your decision?
The party is starting!
Now, say it before the eyes of God.
Say that you swear to be faithful to me
in sickness and in further illness.
She'll do no such thing!
Are you some kind of idiot?!
What do you think you're doing?
Take her away to be executed this instant!
That girl is possessed by a demon!
--A demon?!
--A demon!
Don't! I beg you!
Yuri! Don't listen to what he says!
Listen to what's in your heart!
I won't marry you!
I'd sooner die than become your wife!
What did you say just now?! What did you say?!
Accept your punishment for betraying God!
Don't you dare do it!
Foul demons! I'm going to send
you both straight back to Hell!
Fire!
Mugen! Jin!
Who are you?
Hey, you're that nut job from the checkpoint...
So, you're deceiving these believers
with your fraudulent religion
and making money by
selling those illicit firearms.
It's all over! They saw us make the deal!
They what?!
--Fraudulent?
--What did he mean, illicit guns?
It can't be...
Do they expect us to believe
the word of outsiders?
It's a lie! It's nothing but slander!
What he said, too!
Shoot, shoot!
I'm over here!
Oh, my God!
Did you see that?
--Hey, he's Japanese!
--It can't be!
So, now we see you for what you truly are.
His claims of being the descendant
of Francisco Xavier were a blatant lie!
He was using God's name to exploit
us to make money for himself!
W-Wait, wait! Let's all calm down, okay?
Okay, I might actually be Japanese,
but you said you had been saved
because you believed in me, right?
If that's the case, doesn't that make me
your savior regardless of what I am?
If you're our savior, you're supposed to
be bearing a cross in order to save us.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry...
I repent, I'm sorry for what I did!
It was wrong of me!
So please, forgive me...
I was kidding!
As if I'd repent so easily, you bunch of morons!
I'm sick of you people and
your God this and God that!
You only turn to Him when it suits you!
If you love God so much, then I'll send
the whole lot of you to go see Him!
Amen!
You're going to Ikitsuki Island, aren't you?
Yeah.
I'll pray that you will find Seizo, no,
the samurai who smells of sunflowers.
Still, who the hell is this guy, anyway?
It would be easier to find him if we knew.
Well, he's...
The sunflower samurai is... He's my father.
Well, goodbye, Yuri.
Farewell.
C'mon, you two! Let's go!
May the grace of God be with you.
Mata yo ga akereba owakare
Yume wa tooki maboroshi ni
Anata o oikakete ita hikari
no naka de dakareru tabi
Atatakai kaze o tayori
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels
Haru o tsuge odoridasu sansai
Natsu o miru Uji nohara karakusa kawaku wa
Aki no tsuki nobotta manmarusa o-iwai
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Fuyu o sugi mata tsukihi o kazoeru
Mada mabuta no oku ni aru itsuka no natsu
toosugita aozora (Atatakakatta)
Te o tsunagu hana tsukamiutau itsuya omoide
Ima yobisamasu, kioku no naka de
Iza arukidasu, anata no moto e
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Haru o tsuge odotte sanba
Natsu o miru Uji nohara karakusa kawaku wa
Aki no tsuki nobotta manmarusa o-iwai
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Fuyu o sugi, mata tsukihi o kazoeru
Mata yo ga akereba owakare
Yume wa tooki maboroshi ni
Anata o oikakete ita hikari
no naka de dakareru tabi
Atatakai kaze o tayori