Okay, you people! Dig the wax
outta your ears and listen up!.
C'mon!
Listen up! If you learn
one thing today, learn this.
I do what other people can't do.
Those people who can't,
they say I'm not with it.
Well, they're right. I'm not with it.
All you unwashed masses will
probably figure it out after I'm gone.
You'll realize that the man named
Nagamitsu was a real-deal bigshot.
That's the kind of man that you're
gonna go down fighting against.
So let's make sure that you
at least die with some style!
Say your prayers...
...Jin!
Huh? W-Wait! My name isn't Jin!
I'm--
"The Art of Altercation (Self-Conceit)"
I'm starving...
I wanna take a bath...
Sleeping outdoors is a crime in Edo...
In any case, we have to raise at least
enough money to pay for lodgings...
That's it, I'm done. I can't walk any further...
Welcome.
" Pawn Shop "
What do you think? It's really
cute, huh? It's lacquerware, too.
I can't give you anything for it.
It's scratched here and here,
and the lacquer's wearing off, too.
Do you have anything else?
Sorry, but I don't take anything
unless it's brand-name.
Besides, a sword like that
wouldn't fetch a high price.
Told ya so.
Anything else?
He's gonna hold onto 'em, that's all.
You can get 'em right back.
Forget it.
Don't be such a tightwad. C'mon!
Stop that.
My word!
Ew, gross... What're you doing?
These are very uncommon! Rare items
that you see once in a lifetime!
So... How do we go about earning money?
Are you listening?
Big guy?
Hey! Look at that babe. My heart's pounding.
Got it, Shinpachi?
I'm on it, big guy.
Pardon me, would you like a pear?
I think my boss wants to talk to you.
Who?
--He's trying to pick me up?
--Pretty much.
Why doesn't he come over here himself?
Well, the big guy is kinda shy.
No thanks.
Listen...
Forget it, no way. Ask all you want,
the answer will still be no.
This woman is going to take some work.
But the thing is, that only makes
her all the more worthwhile.
--Yo, honey.
--Uh, look...
Who, me? I'm a man who's gonna be big.
Believe it or not, big.
No, more than that. Bigger than the biggest.
My name is...
Nagamitsu Sakon Shogen!
This is his idea of shy?
I found him! It's the real deal this time!
You need me?
I'm staying at this address,
so come by, all right?
I'll be waiting for you! Later!
Oh, good grief! I swear, it's tough
to be a girl with sex appeal.
Being hit on... Well, that's one hassle
that you guys would never understand.
Refill over here.
From the customer over there.
Hey, that lady's pretty hot...
This won't do at all. Water
has more flavor than this.
Just who do you think I am?
Um, who are you?
People call me Budou Kiba.
Grape fang...?
Thanks for the drinks.
This won't do. Two fine men
shouldn't be drinking all by themselves.
You need a feminine flower to have a
good time getting drunk, don't you think?
Excuse me...
When that which is given and that
which is received are in balance,
that is when men and women
are bound together.
Would you care to join me for a drink?
Somewhere with a little more atmosphere?
Well, I guess I don't have a problem with that.
What're you talking about?!
C'mon, Jin! Say something, too!
I know a place with delicious foreign drinks.
And we won't be bothered there, either.
Hey, lady!
Young women are praised for
their looks, and nothing more.
It is only women who are mature in years
who gain respect for being beautiful.
--Shall we go?
--C'mon, let's go!
I swear, it's tough to be a
man with sex appeal, ain't it?
You morons! Fine, see if I care!
Jerks...
I'm gonna go see this guy, you hear?!
So, you're him.
The one they call the Glasses-Hunting Samurai
who's been causing trouble around here lately.
An ambush, huh?
But the thing is, those aren't the real deal.
Those glasses of yours are fake!
And that means... that you aren't Jin.
I'll be the first to admit
that I'm a man who will use
whatever's around me as a
stepping stone to become big.
Nevertheless... my policy is
to avoid unnecessary fighting.
Don't talk so big! I'm here to punish you!
--C'mon!
--You got it, big guy!
Anyway, a man's gotta do what a man's gotta do!
Die!.
Big guy!
Way to go, big guy!
Midair Finishing Move!
Um... Flying Dragon Sword.
I had it all planned!
Still, it was a needless fight...
So you came after all!
Shall we go forth to Roppongi Hill?
"The European Store"
What the hell is this? It's all red!
It's called grape wine. It's a drink
that comes from beyond the sea.
Delicious.
A beautiful drink for beautiful lips.
If you wish to have beautiful eyes,
you should gaze upon beautiful things.
No matter how deeply wounded you may be,
there is joy in love that is even greater.
And the instant she manages
to become her true self,
that's when a woman experiences
the ultimate in elegance.
I've been longing for the
warm touch of skin lately...
However, my policy is to only drink with boys
who can hold their liquor better than I can.
I think I'll have another.
Top me off, too.
Oh, I see that you're a strong drinker.
Your friend here is awfully quiet.
He's always like that.
I don't feel like going home tonight...
" Hilarious Anime Samurai Champloo "
Do you know why I brought you here?
This area is gonna be my front lawn one day.
And that over there?
That's gonna be my house one day.
Edo Castle.
With that in mind, will you
be the Harem of my Heart?
Um... I don't think I follow you.
If you want to know all about me...
...you should take a look at that.
That's my autobiography. A work in progress.
Well, I call it "The Path to Being Big. "
Yes, my past, present, and even my
future plans are all written in there.
At any rate, I won't be satisfied with being
second or third in anything that I do.
I want to become bigger than anyone else
and make the name Nagamitsu
known throughout the land!
So tell me. Who's the
biggest man in the country?
Gawatoku.
The Shogun Tokugawa, and that's a fact!
And so, I jumped aboard the last
ship from the province of Aki.
I made my way to Edo alone.
Along the way, I defeated some
roughneck on his horse on a sandy beach,
as well as that Kogarashi bozo,
and my reputation started to climb.
Yes, until the day when people throughout
the land are abuzz with rumors about me,
my final objective is...
Come out and face me, Tokugawa!
I'm too late, huh?
Anyway, there I was, wailing away at what I
thought was Edo Castle, when suddenly...
Uh, mister? That's Osaka Castle.
That's what happened.
Still, because of that,
I met my first follower, Ogura.
At around that time, I heard
whispered rumors of a legendary man
who was undefeated in a thousand duels.
And that man's name was...
Enshiro Mariya!
It would've been perfect.
If I could defeat Enshiro and take
over his legend of 1,000 victories,
" Kisarazu Mujushin Kenjutsu Dojo "
I have you now, Mariya!
I'm too late, huh?
My perfectly laid plans ran
headlong into a wall that day.
I learned from the remaining disciples
that Enshiro had already been killed.
The man who struck down the
legendary, undefeated Enshiro
was none other than his top pupil.
A teacher-killer being allowed to assume his
undefeated legend? Isn't that preposterous?
After that, I added a new
entry in my autobiography.
Right! This one right here!
" For now, slay the betrayer of the
man with the undefeated legend!! "
my own legend will echo through the country!
Yo, Nagamitsu!
And if I can only make it big,
everything will be within my reach!
When I talk like this, people might think
to themselves, " Nagamitsu is a lonely man. "
I'll admit that I might be lonely.
But I'm alone of my own free will.
And if I'm gonna be lonely anyway...
...I ought to be lonely inside that castle!
I've had it up to here with
being lonely inside a tenement!
Big guy!
And that's why you're attacking
every samurai you come across.
Not every samurai!
I know that this samurai wears glasses,
which is rare even here in Edo.
Yes! And that man's name is--
J-J-Jin!
Right! Jin!
Um... Gosh, I hope you find that--
J-Jin!
Right, right. That guy.
J-J-Jin.
Well, it's late, so I'm gonna head back.
Okay! I'll be waiting for you
here again tomorrow night, then!
Is it a good idea to let her go?
Don't be dumb. I'm taking my time on this one.
What a fine woman.
That indomitable spirit in her eyes reminds
me of you-know-who when she was young.
Where could those two have
run off to at a time like this?
Well, bigger doesn't necessarily mean better.
No, that's impossible...
Jin would never do something like that.
" Inn "
You guys!
Aw, quiet down...
My head...
You reek of booze!
That woman...
The bitch rolled us.
Would you two... get your act together?!
Get out there and earn it back!
Okay! Step right up! Take a look!
The two master swordsmen you see before you
will amaze you with their
astounding sword techniques!
If they succeed, feel free
to leave money in here.
Okay, I've got us a crowd.
So, what're you gonna do?
--You take the bottom one.
--Very well.
I-I'll be fine, I'll be fine...
Hey, I need to ask you something...
Yeah, what?
Well, it's about Jin...
Has he ever told you anything about his past?
I don't know anything.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Well, it's not an easy topic to bring up...
Could he really be a bad person?
" Pawn Shop"
You have her rigged up as a low-rider, I see...
Customized palanquins are always lower in value.
Say what? Don't try to take advantage of me.
Old man, you haven't pawned them yet, have you?
Oh, you must have raised some money, huh, sir?
I'll only be a minute.
At this very moment, a door has opened.
And the name of that door is destiny.
You couldn't bear to wait until nightfall to
meet me, so you followed me, didn't you?
Oh, don't feel bad. I understand how you feel.
What's this guy's name?
--Jin. What about it?
--Jin?!
Jin of the Mujushin Kenjutsu school?!
I'm Bunta Ogura, student of
the Mujushin Kenjutsu dojo!
Answer me!
You're right. I am Jin.
You traitor! Prepare to pay
for killing our master!
Let's step outside.
Ogura?
No one interfere.
I've looked everywhere for you.
In order to find you, I even became
the follower of a lowlife like that man,
and bided my time.
Why did you betray him?!
Why did a man as great
as you betray our master?!
I wasn't the one who betrayed him.
Even so... I won't make excuses.
In any case, the fact of the matter
is that I was the one who killed him.
Bastard!
Holy crap... Ogura was that tough?
Kill me!
But don't forget that lots of students
are out there, and they're after your head.
I've made my peace with that.
Tell that to the others like you.
That's why I'm letting you live today.
Some day... we'll avenge him.
So, it was all true...
Big guy!
Luigi!
Luigi! It's been so long, Luigi!
What's Luigi doing here?
--O-Sen!
--So there you are!
Honey, stop goofing off here.
Hurry up and come home.
I'm so sorry about all that.
My husband is a fool.
Hey, wait a minute!
Listen, men are all idiots, so make sure
you get them whipped right away.
--Let's go.
--Yes, ma'am!
Farewell, Harem of my Heart.
Don't worry, I'll make sure to write
about you in my autobiography.
What do you think you're doing?
Your children are waiting for you
with empty stomachs, so hurry it up!
Y-Yes, dear...
Our money.
I'll forget about Enshiro.
An even better one would be... Musashi, I guess.
He's already dead.
--How about Nobunaga?
--Good idea!
Honestly...
Men are such idiots.
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels
Spring is announced when the
wild plants break out in a dance
Summer comes to Uji, and in the fields
are patterns of grass set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
I can still see the too-distant blue sky
when I close my eyes (It was so warm)
As I reminisce, I take your hand
as I pluck flowers and sing
Within the memories that
are now coming back to me
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Spring is announced when the
mountain leaves break out in dance
Summer comes to Uji, and textiles with
plains grass patterns are set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels