" Gamblers and Gallantry (Fallen Angel)"
I wonder if those two are out
working like they're supposed to...
Fuu! Deliver this order, okay?
Coming!
Perhaps this is none of my business...
This canal isn't as deep as it appears.
If you intend to throw yourself in and drown
yourself, it would be wiser to choose another.
Did it look to you like I was
going to throw myself in?
I was looking at the canal, that's all.
What? You don't believe me?
My goodness... Did I have such
a dejected look on my face?
Honestly, I would never
do something that painful.
Thank you for the warning. Bye.
C'mon! C'mon! Shove him! Shove him!
Do you wanna win this thing or don't ya?!
Don't touch me!
--You little punk!
--Screw you!
Excuse me.
Oh, there you are! You're my part-timer, right?
Boy, are you a lifesaver!
Okay, mind the stall while I'm gone!
I was led to believe that
this job involved blade work.
Oh, there's cutting, all right.
Relax, in this rain, you won't
be getting many customers.
Wait! Hey!
Okay, it's all yours, buddy!
One grilled eel, please.
Oh, you're that samurai from earlier.
" Eel "
Oh, that's the one! I want
that spirited one there.
Listen, you'll never catch
an eel using brute force.
You anticipate the eel's movement...
Now!
Eels are like women. If you try to use force
to hold them down, they'll only run away.
You fix it in place like this, and then...
Allow me to slice it.
Wait just a minute!
Eels are Hamamatsu's pride and joy!
It's bad luck to hack away at one
with a huge thing like that!
--What'll it be, ma'am?
--Three grilled eels, please.
Coming right up!
Here, start putting the pieces on skewers.
Five grilled eels, and I'm in a big hurry.
Coming right up!
Two for me.
Get the sauce ready! Hurry! Hurry!
Step right up! Come one, come all!
Doubles your energy! Makes your family healthy!
Get your grilled eel,
the specialty of Hamamatsu!
How about some eel tonight?!
Boy, business was booming...
Not a bad night's work, I'd say.
Hey, wait a minute. I didn't come here to work.
Allow me to cook one for you.
When you cook something, you make
sure it's good and cooked, don't you?
I'll eat it, anyway.
You went to all that trouble.
Well, here goes.
Yuck. This is impressive.
I've never eaten eel that
tastes this bad before.
Maybe that also takes talent,
in a manner of speaking.
Have some water.
I'd rather have tea.
I'm done.
Thank you. This has given me
some wonderful memories.
Bye.
Memories?
I'm starting work in a brothel tomorrow.
So today is the last day that I'll
be able to wander around freely.
My husband fell into debt,
and I'm the collateral.
I suppose this sort of thing
happens all the time.
Well, I should go. Bye-bye.
C'mon, let's see some more
spirit when you pull that thing.
I'm back!
I know I'm not gonna like the answer,
but what are you doing here?
I'm training. Can't you tell?
Beetle sumo wrestling.
I'm gonna train this guy up proper
and enter him in matches.
Weren't you going to work as a bodyguard?
Oh, I quit that.
What do you mean, you quit?!
What about our money?!
Oh, quit your nagging. I'm gonna
make a bundle with this bad boy.
You jerk! Get yourself a legit job!
Excuse me.
You came all the way here just to return this?
That's right.
Thank you. But I won't
need that anymore, either.
I'm not allowed to go out in the outside world.
It could rain or pour outside,
and it wouldn't matter to me.
If you like, go ahead and use this for yourself.
Look at you, you're soaked to the bone.
Kohana. You have a customer.
All right, I'll be right there.
One more thing...
Your name. I never asked what it was.
My name is Shino.
But I don't need that name anymore, either.
What's yours?
It's Jin.
Thank you, Jin. Goodbye.
Yeah, baby! If you don't win, you don't eat!
Why the heck do I have to come here
and watch a couple of bugs duke it out?
Just because he made it drag that rock
around for a day doesn't mean it's gonna--
Get in there, Rodriguez!
Get your ass in there!
--Yeah!
--No way!
It actually won!
Did I forget something else at the stall?
No.
You came here for a good time, then?
I'm sorry. I appreciate it, but you're
interfering with business, so please leave.
I don't have time to chat with you.
Please, don't come here again.
Welcome, sir! Have you spotted
a girl who strikes your fancy?
--Act now, and...
--I have no money.
We have a window-shopper, boys!
We don't run this business to give broke
samurai some free eye candy, got it?
If you need some action,
come back with some money!
--What's your problem?
--You're bad for business!
Don't show your face around here again!
Well? Whaddya have to say now, huh?
After paying off what we owe for staying here...
...we still have plenty left!
This needs to go into savings!
Don't be so tightfisted!
I'm gonna use this as seed money
to make another pile of money!
Jin!
What happened to you? How'd you get hurt?
It's nothing.
How can you say that? Look at you!
That money--
When did you--
Hey, it's my money. I won it fair
and square in beetle sumo wrestling.
--Let me borrow it.
--Say what?
What do you want it for?
I need to buy a woman.
You! I thought I told you not to come here!
Back again for another
lesson, huh? Weren't we clear?
You that eager to get your ass kicked again?
Welcome, kind sir! Is Kohana
the girl you've selected, sir?
Um, allow me to take your swords.
House rules, sir.
Take your time, sir.
What do you think he meant by that?
What did Jin mean, buying a woman?
I'm glad to hear it, aren't you?
Hear what?
That bozo's never shown any interest in girls,
so I was gettin' a little suspicious.
About what?
--That maybe he's a homo.
--No way!
Well, this is good news.
That's a load of my mind.
How can you say that?! Anyway, what does
he need with another woman when I'm around?
Oh, so you're saying that you wanna be his girl?
I-I didn't say that...
Big talk, coming from a
girl who's flat as a board.
I'm the type of girl who looks
more slender in clothing.
--You big liar.
--I am not!
Then let's see what you got.
Fine, I'll give you an eyeful!
No, I shouldn't...
Oh, you're jealous, huh?
Of course I'm not jealous!
What in the world would give
you the idea that I'm jealous?!
Lone wolf wannabes like him
that always have blank expressions
and you can never tell what they're thinking
are so not my type!
You fell asleep?!
Would you like some sake?
No.
I see.
That's all right. Let's just sit like this.
If you like, but you're paying so
much money for time with me...
It doesn't look like this rain will
stop anytime soon, eel man.
I don't run an eel stand.
I'm on a journey, and I was only
working there to earn money for lodgings.
Oh, so you're a traveler.
But I've been held up in this city
for a while now because of the rain.
Oh, I see. Once the rain stops, you'll leave.
I hope that the rain will never stop.
Then, I would be able to stay here forever.
I didn't mean that as a joke.
I'm sorry... Nobody talks
like that in this day and age.
Miss Shino... Don't you hate this job?
Sure, there are things about it that I hate.
But the thing is, I laugh when I'm actually sad.
I'm frustrated, so I laugh it off.
I swear, my business is
terrible because of this rain.
The only customer I've had today
is some samurai who wears glasses.
He's got a thing for Kohana, my new girl.
She was sold to me to cover her husband's debts.
A wife can't file for divorce
against her husband,
so I guess it was her bad luck
to be stuck with a lousy husband.
Let's leave this place.
What are you saying?
I can't let you do this anymore...
Don't make it sound so simple.
Do you have any idea how much it
costs to buy a prostitute's freedom?
Even if there were a hundred of you,
you still wouldn't be able to earn enough.
Back when I got married, even my parents
were happy that I was marrying into money.
But my husband had a gambling problem,
and he amassed a mountain of debt.
The next thing I knew, the young wife of the
textiles merchant had become the town whore.
Please, just let it go.
I appreciate the sentiment, really.
But talk like that is just a pipe dream.
Begging your pardon, sir.
Kohana, you have a visitor.
I'll be right there.
Fairy tale time is over. Please, go home.
C'mon, Shino, I'm begging you. Spot me a little.
You don't expect me to have any money, do you?
Aw, don't be like that, baby...
Customers slip you a little
under the table, right?
Why don't you give up gambling
and earn an honest living?
What did you say?!
What, you got a problem with my gambling?
You wanna leave me?
Sorry, baby, but I don't feel
like letting you go just yet.
What do you think you're doing, you bastard?!
I'm her husband!
I can do whatever I want to her!
That's enough! Let him go!
Shit! I'm gonna bleed you dry for
as long as you live, you hear me?!
Remember that!
Where are you going?
Back to see that Kohana lady?
Why? It's not like I don't understand
why you'd feel sorry for her, but--
It isn't out of pity.
You aren't seriously telling me
that you're in love with her, are you?
Jin, you aren't gonna run
away with her, are you?
If I don't come back...
...I want the two of you to continue
your journey without me.
You can't be serious...
You promised me that you'd help me look
for the sunflower samurai, didn't you?
If you leave, we're through
as friends, you hear?!
You promised me!
We've traveled together all this time!
Forgive me.
You jerk!
Welcome.
What's the matter?
We're leaving.
Pack what you need.
I can't leave... It's hopeless.
Even if I manage to get away from here,
they'll follow me to the ends of the earth.
There is a divorce temple across the river.
If you ask for shelter there,
they might help you.
I can't do that.
Even if they give me sanctuary,
I'll just be a prisoner again.
I won't be able to leave for three years.
I won't be able to meet you like this, either.
I would rather wait for you here.
That day when I met you on the bridge...
You really were planning
to kill yourself, weren't you?
I was.
If you hadn't happened by
when you did, right now I'd be...
Let's go. Together.
I'm sorry to interrupt your good time,
sir, but your time is up, so you need to--
You're amazing...!
Give me an extension.
Take your time, sir!
I'll go down first and wait for you.
But...
It'll be all right.
Now, sir, about that extension fee...
Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
Come back here, you bitch!
Hurry!
We've got a runner! Catch her!
Come back here!
Listen, you two. In this world,
you don't always get what you want.
I thought you said you two were quits!
Forget what I said, just hurry!
You're pathetic, man.
Jin!
I want my money back!
Hurry!
Shino!
You aren't trying to run away
from me, are you, baby?
I've had enough of living
my life under your thumb.
I'm taking my life back.
That's the price of the woman
who used to be your wife.
There she is! Catch her!
Jin!
Thank you.
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels
Spring is announced when the
wild plants break out in a dance
Summer comes to Uji, and in the fields
are patterns of grass set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
I can still see the too-distant blue sky
when I close my eyes (It was so warm)
As I reminisce, I take your hand
as I pluck flowers and sing
Within the memories that
are now coming back to me
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Spring is announced when the
mountain leaves break out in dance
Summer comes to Uji, and textiles with
plains grass patterns are set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels