Save Mugen! Please, save Mugen!
What do you mean by that?
So, it's a trap.
Mukuro, you son of a bitch!
You played me, didn't you?!
Oh, crap!
Damn you, you bastard!
Mukuro!
The pirate ship!
What? Which one is it?
Mugen's on it!
Mugen!
" Misguided Miscreants, Part 2
(A Dark Night's Passing, Part 2)"
Mugen...
I can't believe it, he's dead...!
That would never happen.
Mugen would never die that easily!
--Calm yourself!
--But we have to...
Calm yourself.
In search of new lands
I build a new house
I thatch the house with reed stalks
Gathered neatly in bundles
With reeds gathered neatly in bundles
I thatch the house with reed stalks
Gathered neatly in bundles
At the stone wall
Let us celebrate the golden house
That was built by a hundred black kites
It's not right... It's not right
that they' re so beautiful.
Not when we're this sad down here.
They can't see anything up there.
Looking down from up there, we wouldn't
look any bigger than grains of sand.
I never... I never knew who my father was.
And my mother, she died a long time ago.
Mukuro killed her.
I want to escape from this place.
I want out of this hell.
The eighth month is fast approaching
And yet I've nothing to wear
I want to dress gaily
So brother, will you lend me just one sleeve?
Whoa, wait just a damn a minute...!
I wish to dress my children and loved ones
In the one kimono that I own
As for me, I will wear vines
That I plucked deep in the mountains
If you're gonna try to start some shit
with me, I'll pay you back with interest!
How about it? Why not team up with me?
Say what?
You and me, we're two of a kind.
Both of us are loved by this hell we live in.
I don't work with anybody.
The light of the full moon shines down
Illuminating the world with its divine light
When my lover sneaks in to visit me
I wish that the clouds would
hide that light just a little
What're you afraid of?
I ain't afraid of nothin'.
Then why won't you team up with me?
Because I hate your freakin' guts, that's why.
Listen, the three of us were
born and raised in this hellhole.
We're at the bottom,
so we can't fall any lower than this.
We don't have anything else to lose.
Isn't that right?
Come with me.
That's one of Satsuma's ships.
It's carrying raw sugar.
We're gonna steal that ship.
We'll steal it and its cargo,
and we'll get off this island.
Change in plans! Let's get out of here!
But what about Mugen?!
Do you have any last words?
Hurry up and get it over with.
Going to Hell don't bother me none.
Life here is pretty much a living Hell, anyway.
But the thought of bein' killed by
you bastards rubs me the wrong way.
I lived my life without any help from anybody.
And if I'm gonna die, I'm gonna send
myself to Hell without any help from you.
Son of a...! Shoot! Shoot him!
The same thing happened back then, too.
Mugen was executed by
the Satsuma domain officials
for the assault on the raw sugar transport.
But that was a trap set for him by Mukuro.
And so was this time...
Mugen's been killed by him
twice now. I want to avenge him.
Please, kill Mukuro.
I take it you know where he is?
Mugen...
T-There's a--
--What's wrong?
--A-A dead body!
Mugen!
Mugen... You can't be...
Why?
Why'd you have to die?
No way, he's still alive?
Mugen...!
Hey! Mugen!
Got it? You and me are the only ones
who know where this hiding place is.
We'll leave the gold here
until the heat dies down.
--What about Koza?
--I didn't tell her, either.
I'm trusting you on this. Don't go blabbing
to Koza just because you have a thing for her.
Sounds like you think it was
Koza that won me over.
What, it wasn't?
The reason I signed on was for the money.
So all my little plots were for nothing, huh?
Oh, I wouldn't go that far.
Hey, you people there.
May we help you?
You know that a government transport ship
was attacked here last night, right?
Yes.
We're looking for leads on the attackers.
Did you see or hear anything?
Those are strange clothes.
Are you from this village?
Get over here! We found the ship!
What?!
Is anybody on board?
Is the money safe?!
The hold is empty!
Where the heck did Jin and Koza go?
Mugen's back, but they aren't here...
What?
I'm starving...
Hang on, I'll go scrounge something up.
Finally here, huh?
Shiren's waiting on pins
and needles for you inside.
You! How did you know about this place?
She wouldn't...
I was supposed to be the one who killed him.
Draw your weapon!
I was such a fool...
I was completely fooled...
I was, and so were you...
Mugen? He couldn't have--
Where the heck did he go?! Geez!
You're--
What, you thought I was
gonna die before I killed you?
I'm gonna go put an end to this.
I killed him.
What did you say?
Mukuro is dead. I killed him.
You son of a...
--I was gonna...
--I was played.
We were played for fools.
As was he.
This is one opponent
that I will be unable to kill.
Do you think we did the right thing?
Of course we did. You wanted
to be free of Mukuro, didn't you?
And now we have money to burn.
Once the heat dies down,
I'll show you where it's hidden.
You're having second thoughts?
There's no other way for me to get by in life.
My whole life, this is how I've had to live.
Don't abandon me, okay? Don't leave me.
Kill me...
Please, kill me!
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels
Spring is announced when the
wild plants break out in a dance
Summer comes to Uji, and in the fields
are patterns of grass set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
I can still see the too-distant blue sky
when I close my eyes (It was so warm)
As I reminisce, I take your hand
as I pluck flowers and sing
Within the memories that
are now coming back to me
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Spring is announced when the
mountain leaves break out in dance
Summer comes to Uji, and textiles with
plains grass patterns are set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels