" U ra-Edo "
When one reflects on the past,
regardless of culture,
it is during periods of idleness
that fashion is cultivated and born.
Yes, even the threadbare casual style
was born here during the Edo Era.
And designs resembling street fashion
had already arrived on the scene.
"Aki Province "
"War of the Words (Master of Pen and Sword)"
I think I'll try cod roe
and mochi cheese in mine.
Coming right up!
" Hiroshima-yaki "
"Ju-ju "
So, what are you guys getting?
Seafood style. With oysters.
You got it. And you, buddy?
Gimme what this guy's having.
Coming right up.
You keep ordering the same thing as Jin or me.
You can eat whatever you want, you know?
I don't got much choice.
But everything's written there
on the menu, plain as day.
That's my point. I can't understand it, okay?
Are you telling me that you can't read?
This one here is " no. "
So's this one. And this one, too.
See, I can read just fine.
What's this one, then?
--" No, " I guess.
--It's " me. "
You little bitch, that was a trick question!
Are you telling me that you
can only read one letter?
Being able to read one is
more than enough, you know?
Now that you mention it,
I've never seen you read anything before.
I can get by just fine
without being able to read.
Isn't it amazing that in all the time
we've been traveling together,
we've never noticed that he can't read?
Hey, you just laughed, didn't you?!
Listen up, you don't need to
be able to read to kill people.
What's that crap you're spoutin', boy?!
It's okay for a fool to stay a fool, huh?
Don't give me that pathetic garbage!
Listen good!
Every word has a soul in it!
If you don't know the letters that convey
that soul, you're the one who loses out.
When you're illiterate, you're
automatically branded as an idiot!
Don't that piss you off, boy?!
Well?! Don't it?!
Are you okay with bein' an idiot?!
Are you?!
He passed out...
Let's see... How much do we owe?
D'oh! We're short!
Put it on this old dude's tab, okay?
--Sure thing!
--What? But...
Don't sweat it. Call it a nuisance fee.
Let's go.
Sorry, mister!
Mister? C'mon, wake up. Time to settle up.
All together, it comes to 1 3 shu.
What the hell is this?!
We keep painting it over
and over... It's a vicious circle.
They're getting awfully cocky.
Um, pardon me, ladies.
Do you know who painted this?
Of course we don't! If we did,
we would've had 'em arrested ages ago!
I-I see...
I'm sorry, but there is someone over
in Mihara to whom I am indebted,
so I would like to stop by and pay my respects.
Mihara's pretty far away from here.
Who would you be willing to go that far to see?
An old girlfriend?
To anyone who aspires to
mastery of the martial arts,
Mihara is a town that cannot be passed by.
Among all the town's dojos, the best one in
which to study general weapons mastery...
is Gojuu Hall.
Under the tutelage of
Master Junosuke Niwa, I once--
Fine, go have fun!
And make sure you ask him if he knows
anything about the sunflower samurai, okay?
Hey, deep down, you really want
to learn how to read, don't you?
Just drop it.
I'll teach you.
Look, that's "sa, " and " n, " and " jou. "
That means "was here. " Got it?
That's the bastard who stiffed me yesterday...
What the heck does 4-6-4-9 mean?
Oh, it's "yoroshiku"!
" Nice to meet you "! Get it?
Huh?
"Gojuu Hall "
Who the hell are you?
What do you think you're doing here?
Sorry, pal, but this is our team's turf.
Listen up, pops. I think we're gonna
collect a little relaxation fee from you.
He's telling you to hand over your money!
--S-Stay away!
This is a place where those who strive
to master the martial arts gather together.
This is no place for the likes
of you to be loitering around.
Sorry, mister. But the thing is,
this is our hideout.
Where might I find Master Niwa?
Master Niwa?
Oh, if you mean the bosses,
they're in town right now.
What?
Darn that Mugen... He's always
disappearing into thin air.
--I'm the boss!
--No way! I'm the boss!
Is that how you show your
respect towards your elder brother?!
You were only born one stinkin' minute
before me, so don't pull that big brother crap!
You think that a guy who can't keep
junior and senior rankings straight
is cut out to be the boss?!
What do you think this is,
some procession of feudal lords?
That way of thinking is so behind the times!
Just looking at that face
of yours pisses me off.
You took the words right outta my mouth.
What're they talking about?
Their faces are identical.
--Who talked just now?!
--Pretty...
Stop copying me!
You' re the one who's copying me, you dick!
Those big brown eyes are so cute!
You're wrong!
The way her mouth is a
little coy is seriously sexy!
Goodness.
And that voice like a bell is so sweet!
No way!
The way her little nose is turned up
just a little bit is so honey-bunny!
Hey, you two!
--She's mine.
It's been a long time.
Tatsunoshin. Kazunosuke.
--It can't be!
--Big bro Jin...!
You know these two?
That hurt!
Just who the hell are you?!
My name is Bundai.
" Private School Bundai Hall "
This here is a private school.
And under this roof,
you will address me as Sensei!
You're a teacher?
You can keep trying to solve all your
problems by force the way you're doing now,
but that won't stop the world from turning.
You can't build a castle if
all you've got is carpenters.
What you need is a wood plane.
And even if you've got wood planes,
you'll get hurt if they aren't
kept good and sharp at all times.
First, you sharpen your plane.
" Better to burn out than fade away"
" Let's get outta this town "
I'm about to teach you how to read.
" Drills"
Doesn't it piss you off?!
To have your companions mock you like that?!
Are you kidding me?! You can't read?!
" No "
All right, damn it, you're on!
Why do you quarrel with one another?
As brothers, should you
not be helping one another
and mastering the path that
your father handed down to you?
What do you expect?
Nobody takes over as heads of families or
follows in their father's footsteps these days.
Hell, when somebody offs themselves,
they're only screwing over
the ones they're leaving behind.
Besides, the way this guy dresses scares people.
Come back and try saying that again after
you've washed that filthy mug of yours!
Say what?!
You want some, pinhead?
Enough of this.
If this is the case, settle the matter with
swords like true heirs of Gojuu Hall.
--We're no good with those.
In that case, what could act as a
substitute for a sword for the two of you?
--That'd be...
--Yeah, definitely that.
Your graffiti?
That's not quite right, bro.
It might look like ordinary graffiti to you, but
it's something that we've devoted our lives to.
So in that sense, it's no different from
the way Pop devoted himself to the sword.
It's called tagging, and it's like
it proves that we're alive.
That ain't right.
We try to tag the most dangerous places.
" Police"
Places that nobody else
has ever tagged before.
" Live in the Moment"
It's like the only time we're really alive
is when we're experiencing that thrill.
They're both saying pretty
much the same thing, huh?
Okay, then. You should duel each
other using this tagging of yours.
--How do we do that?
You could say that the winner will be the one
who tags the most dangerous place, right?
--In that case...
--The prize has to be...
Oh, goodness... Whatever shall I do?
--Bro, please act as the judge!
What's this one?
It's "re. "
" Be a woman! "
This one with the swoop
on the end, that one's " re"!
How many times do I gotta explain it?!
This is so damn confusing!
What's the matter, my good first grade pupil?
Are you crying uncle? Are you?
Are you gonna turn tail?
The way all these letters look
so much alike pisses me off!
If you've got complaints to make, I'll listen
to 'em after you've passed these drills!
This is awfully unusual for you, isn't it?
Acting as a mediator all of a sudden...
I mean, this is just a simple
brawl between brothers, right?
Their father, the man I am indebted to,
once asked something of me.
There is now nothing more that I can teach you.
Return to your master and walk
our path with your head held high.
Yes, sir.
I have a favor to ask of you.
If anything should ever happen to me,
I ask that you look after my sons.
--C'mon, Kazu!
--Wait up, Tatsu!
Tag!
" Niwa Family"
This is a surprise... Do you remember me?
It has been a long time, sir.
--I see you've grown into a fine young man.
--Not at all.
My, what fine flowers you've placed there...
They're just wild chrysanthemums
that I found over there.
No, it is the thought that counts.
I'm sure that Master Niwa
is smiling beyond the grave.
What was it that happened?
Of all the earthly emotions of men,
jealousy may be the most powerful.
There was no dojo in the area
that surpassed Gojuu Hall.
The masters of the other dojos
curried favor with the local lord
and made false accusations against Master Niwa.
He was ordered to either close his doors
and take down his sign or cut off his own arm.
And so, in order to leave the dojo to
his sons, he committed ritual suicide.
But his young sons were unable to
appreciate their father's strength
and learn from his example.
With the way those two are behaving,
his memory will never be respected.
" Re "! " Ne "! " No "! " Me"!
"A"! " O "!
All questions answered correctly!
Damn straight. What else did you expect?
And now, use the letters you've
learned to write your own story!
Write it bigger than anybody else!
--Got it?!
--Hell, yeah!
Hey, where the heck have you been?!
Oh, around...
Geez, we've got a serious situation here!
Two men who are vying for my attention
are fighting each other at this very minute.
Sounds rough, all right.
Um... I think they called it
jogging or something.
It's a life-or-death struggle using letters!
Letters, you say?
Stop! Police!
--Police!
--Stop in the name of the law!
What the hell is this?
This is terrible! Somebody, help!
The reds... The blues... How lovely.
I got you beat!
You wish!
No, you wish!
The duel will never be settled at this rate.
Well, is there anywhere that
you haven't put graffiti on yet?
Well...
Yeah, there's one.
--Hiroshima Castle!
Hold it!
Come along peacefully!
"Okonomiyaki "
They're getting revenge in their own way.
The revenge against the lord that
their father was unable to get himself.
It's wrong! They should be ashamed!
I know what you mean.
Kids these days don't have any respect.
You're writing it wrong!
Magnificent...! This is
what I've been looking for!
Who the hell is that?!
Come back here!
I'm number one!
So, who won the duel?
Neither one of us. Somebody beat us to it.
We got beat by some mystery man.
It's a big world. There's always
somebody better than you.
What is important is that you
have learned that lesson.
Then I guess nobody wins me, either.
--Let us cop a quick feel before you go!
Huh? Hey, now!
She's so cute!
Awesome! Just look at those round eyes!
--She's so soft!
--What's up with that?
I recognize your talent for what it is!
You must be the tagging team
that has this town all abuzz.
What if we are?
Who are you people?
How delightfully cool!
Boys, I will make you famous!
You boys have it in you to become designers
who will breathe fresh air
into this stagnant industry!
I just know it!
So, who are you?
The textile merchant who
is known to all in Ura-Edo.
I am Uhori from the Ando Store.
A pleasure, I'm sure.
Nothing doing.
Before that, you do have
something else to see to!
You've been writing everything wrong!
--Aw, Teach!
You're gonna hit the books first! Got it?!
Are you serious?!
Come back!
What's the matter?
This one! And this one, too!
"Sandal "
" Fuu's"
What's going on here?!
"Animal "
Hey, you jerk!
What's the meaning of this?
You gotta write your name
on your stuff, you know?
That symbol--
" Mugen, " it means " infinite. " I made it myself.
Wait, don't tell me that
the man last night was--
" Ura-Edo "
Later, when the two young men traveled to Edo,
they blew a breath of fresh
air into the fashion world,
and their designs spread from
Ura-Edo Avenue to all across the country.
" Niwa "
And people came to call these
two men "The Embodiment of Graffiti. "
To be continued!
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels
Spring is announced when the
wild plants break out in a dance
Summer comes to Uji, and in the fields
are patterns of grass set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
I can still see the too-distant blue sky
when I close my eyes (It was so warm)
As I reminisce, I take your hand
as I pluck flowers and sing
Within the memories that
are now coming back to me
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Spring is announced when the
mountain leaves break out in dance
Summer comes to Uji, and textiles with
plains grass patterns are set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels