What the heck are you two doing?
What about your promise not to kill each other?
This just means that no matter
how hard we try to split up...
...it was always meant to turn out like this!
" Hellhounds for Hire (Part 2)
(Tacit Understanding)"
Wait a minute! Hey!
Hey!
O-Suzu! Let's get out of here!
Hurry! O-Suzu!
I...
I'm sorry.
How dare you do this to O-Suzu?!
Think you can do something about it?
Damn it...!
That's enough!
I knew that you two would come.
What the hell are you
guys doing?! Stay outta this!
I'm the one who's gonna kill him!
Outta my way!
H-He's one of ours! Are you crazy?!
Hey!
Restrain yourself for now.
If you lay down your life now, the person
you're trying to save will be lost, too.
Damn it!
Come back here, you bastard!
You should get rid of that
lunatic right away, Boss.
That man even cuts down his own allies...
I think it's for the best, actually.
It was a fine opportunity to let our
own men see what he's capable of.
B-But... But, boss!
If you truly want to rescue her, your only
option is to crush the Nagatomi Gang.
Their loyalty is bought with money.
I don't think that any of them would
willingly risk his life for their boss.
Take their boss' head, and the
organization will most likely crumble.
Learning that fact alone makes
our infiltration worthwhile.
I swear, we did terrible business today!
You girls had better start
pulling in some money tomorrow!
Let's come up with a way to escape, okay?
It's no use.
I can't run away.
Why not?
If I ran away from here,
my father would be killed.
But... you don't want to do this, right?
Anyway, how come a daughter
has to shoulder her father's debts?
Well, because we're family.
You have a family, too, don't you?
I'm sorry. Did I say something wrong?
No...
Families sure can be a pain, huh?
What's the big idea?!
You don't have to draw your sword anymore.
Your presence alone will be sufficient.
Say what?! Why the hell
did you ask me here, then?
Wasn't it because you wanted to win your fights?
Listen. There are only two
kinds of people in the world.
The rulers and the ruled.
Just by having your strength under my control,
the ruled won't dare rise up against me.
That's what they call efficient ruling.
So, this power you keep talking about
is the power to control other people?
That's right. What's your point?
I ain't the least bit interested in that crap.
I don't wanna rule or be ruled, either one.
Where are you going?!
Stay with me, and you can do anything you want!
Are you seriously going to walk away from that?
For me, I don't believe in
anything but my own skills.
See you around.
Are you turning on me?! Do you
think you can just walk away?!
If you're gonna send somebody after me,
do me a favor and make sure they're damn tough!
What's with you? You want some?
I didn't believe in anything
but my own skills, either.
When I left Boss Kawara's gang,
I thought to myself,
I'm gonna use these skills of mine
to grab something better for myself.
That's all I need.
But the world doesn't work
that way. It's not that simple.
There are times when you gotta agree to
something even when you think it's wrong.
What a load of crap.
What?
Don't spend your life
making excuses to yourself.
You're the one who
decides how to live your life.
C'mon, act sexier, damn it!
My, what fine legs you have!
What's your problem?!
You better stop actin' all high and mighty!
You two are whores, got it?!
Come on, come closer
and attract some customers!
--Hey, you!
--Shut up!
If you're gonna hate somebody,
hate your old man.
--Don't!
--Ooh, I'm gettin' hot, I'm gettin' hot!
Y'know, maybe I'll buy you myself...
W-What the hell do you think you're doing?
B-Blood! It's blood!
I-It's a raid!
Sousuke?!
Sousuke!
Ishimatsu, you bastard!
You've got some nerve,
showing your face around here again!
You always think you can do whatever you want!
Ishimatsu...
I have news about your successor...
He stabbed one of our youngsters.
We were just doing business.
We never had any intention to
spill even a single drop of blood.
How do you intend to make amends for this?
An arm or two won't be nearly enough.
I'll take responsibility for this myself.
--Boss!
--We'll go with you!
Boss!
I'll be fine by myself.
Boss...
Sousuke, what have you done...?
I take full responsibility for his actions.
In that case, I have a proposal to make.
I want to resolve this
situation without bloodshed.
With that in mind, don't you think
we yakuza should behave like yakuza
and settle the matter through gambling?
If you win, I'll return your son to you.
In exchange, I'll take
control of your territory.
It's better than me taking his life, isn't it?
Very well.
And if I win, you will spare my son.
If I lose, I will have him atone
with his life for what he has done.
However...
What?
In the interest of fairness,
my gang will provide the dice roller.
Your gang will provide the dice.
Are you sure?
He knows what it means to be an outlaw.
He should be prepared to
pay the price at any time.
I look forward to our game, then.
What the heck are you two doing?
What about your promise not to kill each other?!
That little bitch!
What a dumb bastard. This will
let me take his territory legally.
What do you mean?
All I need to do is lose.
I'll deliberately lose, give his son
back to him, and take his territory.
But he said that they're going
to provide the dice roller...
Not to worry. Their dice roller
will never show up.
What are you saying, boss?!
We'll be at a disadvantage either way!
Either way, atonement must be made.
But if you lose, Sousuke's life will be--
--Boss!
A big wager?
Right. I overheard some
people talking a while ago.
They say the Nagatomis and Kawaras are
putting their gangs on the line in this match.
So, what will happen if the Kawara Gang wins?
What, do you think that we'll be set free
or something? Don't be so naive.
You mean there's going to be a gang war?
Of course there is!
Old man, this is for yesterday.
You don't want to catch cold, do you?
Thank you.
Where do you think you're going?
In yakuza fights over the years,
I've taken the lives
of countless people that I
harbored no ill will towards.
And the price I've paid is that I've
lost precious friends and family.
I've seen more than enough blood in my time.
It was because of them that I kept this gang
running in spite of that. For our youngsters.
In the end, we're outlaws. Humans who
can't get by in respectable society.
There will always be a handful
of such people in the world.
I thought to myself, someone
has to look after such people.
But when Ishimatsu left and and went to
the Nagatomis, something occurred to me.
I thought to myself, maybe it's
about time for me to step down.
I'll admit that with skills like yours,
you might be able to kill Rikiei.
But that would just cause
a new round of reprisals.
So leave this matter to me, all right?
Give this to Sousuke.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
Instead of catching the customers'
eyes, I'm scaring them away.
If we don't get any customers, we'll be fired,
and we'll be able to leave here, right?
Oh...
Don't give me that " Oh " stuff! You do it, too!
Great! What a terrific face!
You're the one for me!
I've always wanted to have a girl
scold me with that look on her face!
Y-You're kidding, right?
Yes, yes! That's the look!
You're great! You're my kind of girl!
Ow! That hurts!
Let go, you little-- Ow!
A vase...
Take this!
Sir, are you--
She ran away!
Excuse me! Where's the gambling house?
Hop in, hop in!
My name is O-Ryuu, and I will
act as your witness today.
It is an honor to serve you.
Where is your bodyguard?
He walked out on us. I doubt
that he's still in this town.
Both parties, please present your wagers.
"Signed Memorandum "
There will be one throw,
and I ask that there be no delays.
Where's the girl?
Um... She escaped.
Escaped?! That little moron!
I approve.
Now, Boss Kawara. Your dice roller?
It doesn't look like he's arrived yet.
He sure is late... I wonder what's keeping him?
He sure is late...
Damn it, I wonder what's keeping him?
So... Is this the gambling house?
--She's here!
Hurry, hurry!
This way, this way!
--We're counting on you!
Come on, get changed! Get changed!
What in the--
If your roller isn't going to show up,
I suppose we'll have to provide one.
Wait a minute. Just a while longer.
Boss, the dice roller has arrived!
He what?!
What're you--
A little vase...
Let's play.
What will you do?
All I can do is place my fate
in the hands of the heavens.
Boss...
Very well, begin!
Are both parties ready? You are, then?
In they go!
Now, place your bets, place your bets!
Odd!
Even!
Play!
Two-five, odd!
We recognize the Nagatomi Gang
as the winner in this match.
I concede defeat.
As an outlaw, I will see to it that
this matter is seen through properly.
At any rate, I never wanted
to win in the first place.
Wha--?
I don't intend to make my dear
adopted children suffer under you.
What I'm saying is that I've no intention
to surrender my territory to you.
What are you playing at?
As we agreed, I will give
you a life in atonement.
I will atone with my own.
Dad! Dad!
This is pathetic. Talk about
an anachronistic farce...
Damn it, this won't make me one red cent.
You're wrong!
My father stayed true to his code as
an honorable outlaw right up to the end!
You aren't outlaws! You're nothing!
You're honorless thugs!
Being a thug suits me fine. I'll just
take your territory by force, that's all.
You fool. You threw your life away for nothing.
Careful, now!
Hold it right there, bodyguard.
What are you--
Why did you come here?
Nobody was comin' after me...
...so I figured I'd come after you guys instead!
Hold it! Don't you care what happens to--
Go ahead, see if I care!
Damn!
Ishimatsu, what are you doing?!
Get back there and kill those guys!
You never trusted me because
I used to be with the Kawaras.
It's not just me. You never
trusted the other guys, either.
The only thing you ever had faith in was money.
Ishimatsu...
I finally came to my senses.
This was my father's--
He said that he wanted me to give it to you.
Ishimatsu. Will you come back to us?
Sousuke...
I'm sure it's what my father would have done.
Thank you for offering. But I'm an outlaw, too.
I don't want to turn into the sort
of thug that you were talking about.
Once I've paid for what I've done,
I'll gladly take you up on your offer.
I want to settle things.
Thank you for all you've done.
I'm really happy for you, O-Suzu. Bye!
Bodyguard!
Come back someday, you hear?!
Sure.
Once we find the sunflower samurai, okay?
Sorry, pal, but I don't know
the meaning of the word restraint.
I don't doubt it.
Spring is announced when the
wild plants break out in a dance
Summer comes to Uji, and in the fields
are patterns of grass set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
I can still see the too-distant blue sky
when I close my eyes (It was so warm)
As I reminisce, I take your hand
as I pluck flowers and sing
Within the memories that
are now coming back to me
I'm setting out to find my way back to you
Spring is announced when the
mountain leaves break out in dance
Summer comes to Uji, and textiles with
plains grass patterns are set out to dry
The autumn moon rises,
let's celebrate its fullness
Winter passes by, and I count off
the days and months again
Dawn comes, and we part ways once again
My dreams becoming distant apparitions
I turn to the warm wind for help,
the wind I felt every time you held me
As I was bathed in the light
that followed on your heels