Are you sure it's okay?
Is what okay?
Is it okay if we keep staying on?
No, if we continue to stay on, there won't be any progress.
Besides, I don't like having to stay put... having to observe from the dark.
Agnes is so impatient.
Using a bright smile to hide it...
I want to rely on my two feet and find my Maitresse.
I'm not without clues.
Maitresse is also looking for the same thing, isn't she?
Yeah. Artifact, right?
Yes.
It may be without basis, but I feel that I'll understand some things when I reach Ert'Aria.
Is it that intuition of yours again?
The world's number one puppeteer's intuition.
Oh dear...
terekusai hodo chikazuite
When I get close enough to become shy,
照れくさいほど近ずいで
kikoetai koe ga aru
there is a voice that I heard
聞に声がある
wagamama muri iitai houdai
Saying something is impossible like a spoiled child,
ワカママ-ムリ言いたい放題
kikasete yo ai no shoutai
tell me the identity of love
聞かせてよアイの正体
muzukashii kara nigechatta
Ran away, because it was too difficult,
む坂しいから逃げちゃった
kanashikute mae wo mite
was sad so looked forward
悲しくて前を見て
futatabi tatsu daichi yonde
Call upon the earth once more,
再び発つ大地呼んで
ase nigiru ookina mangetsu
The breathtaking giant moon
汗握るおおきな満月
kakkou ii to kakkou warui doushite kyokutan nanda
Cool, or uncool, Why is it so extreme?
格好イイ格好ワルイ　どうして極端なだ
daisuki de daikirai na koto shika wakaranai kedo
Love it and hate it,I know nothing else, but
大スキで大っキライな事しからないけど
hajimatta
it has started
始まった
Land star isshu no bouken
Run! Start! A unique adventure,
Ｌａｎｄ　Ｓｔａｒ一種の冒険
hitori ja nai tte te wo tsunagu
Take this hand because we are not alone
ひとりじゃないって手を繋ぐ
might star me wo tojite
Boy! Start! Closing your eyes
Might Star　目を閉じて
watashi to motto iki wo sutte
Moving through the times together,
わたしともっと息を吸って
mirai ga kirei na hou he to ugoku you ni
for a beautiful future We will move towards it!
ミライがキレイな方へと動くように
Within the Darkness
Come!
The World's number one puppeteer Agnes Boulange's street acrobatics shall end here.
Thank you.
You were also amazing today.
Thank you, madam.
Oh right, I was about to pay a visit to Oasis.
Then you want to submit a quest?
Are we crossing that hill?
That's right.
It came from that mine up ahead.
Let's go, Agnes.
Do you know that elderly woman?
The hotspring crystal supply is running low, so she wanted us to go and bring some back.
She frequently attends Agnes' street performance.
She's a special customer to me.
Special?
Yes.
I heard she's a die hard fan of Agnes.
Die hard fan is a little...
But she's very nice to me.
It sure feels nice with the sunlight peering through the gaps between the leaves.
The scenery, style, and waters here are the complete antithesis of Ert'Aria.
It's a rabbit.
It's cold.
But it's pure and refreshing.
Feels like everyone is here for a picnic.
A picnic?
It's probably because the quest is slightly more relaxed this time, so it gives off a mood like this.
Well if a crystal monster appears, just leave it to me.
When that happens, we'll be counting on you.
So reliable.
It's about time we start moving.
Sure.
To the hotspring crystal, let's go!
Alright!
Hotspring crystal?
They must be getting excited, preparing to soak in the hotsprings together for a while.
A mixed bath with Leicester?
Yes, a mixed bath.
A mixed bath...
We have to catch up with them.
Onwards we go!
Go!
We must catch up with them this time, Ritos.
Again?
Nee-san, there's a cliff ahead.
Looks like I said it too late.
Tell me earlier!
The forest is full of danger, isn't it, Nee-san?
It seems so worn out.
It's a closed mine, that's why.
How should we go about digging?
First, we find a suitable place to dig.
Alright, it should be around here.
Notice how it produced a white powder.
Just like this.
It's beautiful.
I can feel some weak Ale.
Yeah.
This is a hotspring crystal.
This stuff will slowly melt in hot water, filling Ale into it.
But this one's considered very small.
It's difficult making out, isn't it?
I have an idea.
Let's have lunch here.
Yay! Lunch lunch!
I approve.
Me too.
I'm so full.
It's delicious.
Agnes?
I'm going to take a look in front.
Well then, let me accompany you.
The Agnes today is much more hardworking than usual.
Really?
After all, it's for a special customer.
You also mentioned it just now.
That elderly woman was the first customer I met upon arriving in Ert'Aria.
She always frequents my performances.
I feel that if she claps for me, I'll be able to energize.
That's why you're so full of vigor.
What's wrong?
That.
According to the map, it should be this route.
Amazing!
Let's count meteors together everyone...
Even though it feels strange in my heart.
You noticed my fast beating heart.
Will I become stronger if I am together with a gentle person like you?
These are high grade stuff.
Alright! Let's start collecting.
Knocking the door with the rhythm of the heart...
What's wrong?
Which side will the door open on?
Look.  Even though it is sealed beautifully, there are traces of being dug before.
That's a whole new encounter.
Strange, my heart is beating so fast.
Adding to memories is so enjoyable.
It's actually so well hidden.
I'm excited to see what's inside.
Wearing a smile everyday is the best.
I feel some kind of aura inside.
Let's hope our dreams will be realized at this moment.
It's light and floating... it feels great.
Power keeps on coming.
Sorry for the wait.
Thank you.
Let's resume from just now.
Initially, it was thought that the victims sent the SOS.
There were some who said it was a prank.
But it didn't seem that way.
I don't know who it is and what his motives are...
Regardless, it's an unbelievable mysterious light.
Mysterious light?
It came from that mine up ahead.
One, two, GO!
What is this... place?
When you look at that, you kind of feel energized.
It feels really good.
That can't be...
What exactly is this thing?
I don't know what it is, but the probability of it being dangerous is very low.
Do you know anything, Monte?
Explaining situation; I can feel a strange flow of Ale.
A strange flow of Ale?
Danger!
There's a fault in the upper strata, materialization:  confirmed.
No~
Oh Nee-san, are you making a sexy pose?
I'm not! Hurry and save me!
To make use of the situation to increase your popularity... that's cunning.
Like I said, I'm not!
Are you alright, Nee-san?
Ouch...
An... earthquake?
The vibration is rather strong.
This is bad! Let's get out of here.
Where's Agnes?
Agnes!
Leicester.
Leicester!
Hurry up, Papa!
Is everyone alright?
Yes.
I'm fine.
Papa, I'm so scared!
Watch out, Minette-san!
Are you alright?
No need to worry. What about the others?
Carina-san! Minette! Chelsea-san! Nick!
Tango!
Everyone is okay over here!
Don't worry, Agnes.
Tango.
We're also okay.
That's a relief.
What should we do now?
We can only escape from the way we got in, and then ask for help.
Let's go, Miss.
B-But... Leicester and Annie-chan are trapped inside.
Carina-san...
We can't leave them here.
What if there's another earthquake...
Carina-san, we'll search for a way out on our own.
But Leicester...
You can't be like this, Carina-sama.
Please be calm, Leicester and I will be fine.
Annie-chan...
It's not a wise choice to stay here.
There might be another wave of earthquakes.
Since it's impossible to meet up quickly, the best bet is for us to each find a way out.
I understand.
Chel-san.
Let's make a bet.  Will it be Papa who will get out first or us?
Minette. We won't lose.
See you later.
Tango, I'll leave everyone to you.
Roger.
Luckily we have you around.
It's nothing.
You won't gain anything from praising me, you know.
Speaking of which, it really is troubling, isn't it?
Agnes?
We have to hurry.
It's alright!
Like I said, it's alright.
It'll be alright.
It's alright, Agnes.
Leicester.
Let's go.
What's the matter?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
Agnes, you did a great job.
You too.
I've seen something like this before.
It's just like today... I was trapped.
I searched everywhere for an exit.
I managed to get out at the end.
Agnes...
There was also a rainbow in the sky back then.
Thank you very much for earlier.
Subconsciously, I feel that it's okay if you see through me.
You knew I was afraid.
So I think it will be all right to hug you and cry in difficult situations.
I totally didn't think you'd feel that way.
If there's a reliable person beside me, it gives me added courage.
That's why I have to thank you, Leicester.
You're welcome.
That's right, we have to look for the others.
Leicester? Annie-chan?
Papa!
Everyone!
That's great, everyone is okay.
Just a question... where did we go?
Yes, Nee-san?
Picnic...
You're so intelligent today... that's rare.
Nee-san, are you okay?
I'm... really... not all right.
That's it, Agnes.
Of course, that's just what I thought.
Here.
Oh, those are hotspring crystals.
You're giving this to us?
We collected quite a few, so we're splitting some with you.
Your kindness has really touched me.
I see, this is Leicester's hint that he wants to bathe with me.
Me too!
You can't!
Quest complete. You did well.
Leicester, the bath is empty.
Isn't it more appropriate to let Carina-san and the rest use it first?
Being the first person to bathe is not good for a girl's skin.
There you go, use it.
Then I'll use it first.
That elderly woman was really happy. This is great.
It's about time I got out.
Agnes...
Shelley-san told me to get in first.
She's up to her pranks again.
She got me, that mischievious prankster.
Yay, bath, bath.
I'm so excited.
Oh, Annie-chan isn't here?
Yeah, where did she go?
Let's get in first.
Yes!
Is something wrong?
No, I thought I sensed an aura.
Could it be a peeping tom?
Please don't find out.
Leicester's heart is beating very fast.
It's not just me.
Looks like I'm too sensitive.
Well then, I shall go in first.
Yes, baths.
It seems I don't need to hide after all.
When you say that, it's indeed the case...
I didn't think we'd have to stick together after I got undressed.
Agnes...
It's embarrassing, but it's alright...
It's not like I hate it or anything.
Hurry and get out of here.
Sorry for the wait.
Annie-chan, where'd you go?
Mom!
Thrilling isn't it?
I see, the aura came from you just now.
I wanted to secretly admire everyone nude.
No way...
You didn't have to peep.
Then I shall not hold back.
I'll savor your three nude bodies!
I want to savor too!
You can't do that.
Annie-chan, Minette-chan..
My chest isn't big. There's actually nothing to see.
Here!
Chelsea is so smooth.
Impressive, that's Carina-sama for you.
No, Annie-chan, don't...
It's so soft.
So slippery, so smooth.
It's awesome!
mijika ni ite mo yoku shiranai
I don't really know when you are close,
身近にいてもよく知らない
tameiki shinpai o nosete
A sigh, showing worries
ため息　心配を乗せて
kono machi o nukeru ashita o omou
Thinking about the tomorrow
この街を抜ける　明日(あした)を思う
nanika itte yo
that this town will go through
なにか言ってよ
nanika onegai
Say something,
なにか…おねがい
yume o mita kedo oboetenai no
I dreamt, but can't remember
「夢を見たけど憶えてないの」
wasureta furi ga heta da to oshienaide
Don't tell me that, acting that I forgot is weird
忘れたふりが下手だと教えないで
massugu na kimochi ga mae o miteru
The straightforward feelings that look ahead.
まっすぐなキモチガ前を見てる
yorokobi o miteru
Looking at the joy,
喜びを見てる
mayoikeshite RIDE ON RIDE ON RISE
Erasing the worries, Ride, Ride, Rise!
迷い消して Ride on, Ride on RISE
massugu ni kaze ga egaku kaikisen
The straight tropical line drawn by the wind
まっすぐに風がえがく回帰線
ki ga tsuitara
When you realize,
気がついたら
Ah tokimeki nemuru mae ni hayaku hayaku
Ah! The excitement Before sleeping, Hurry, hurry!
Ah,ときめき眠る前に早く…早く…
Preview
Wow, why did you come out on your own?
This is bad! We have to tell them.
Clan Oasis, holiday.
The drama is approaching a turning point.
This is a quest that I accepted.
An Oasis Holiday
I want to complete it on my own.