Within that warm dream...
I sleep sweetly.
From then on, I thought everything would be fine even if I kept sleeping like this.
But...
Listen carefully, Minette.
There are many people living in this world filled with light.
Many people?
The day will also come when you open your eyes.
You'll definitely bring happiness to those people.
I can... make them happy?
Of course you can.
Because, that's the reason you were born.
The great person who created me, said those words.
If they're true, then it'll be a very very wonderful thing.
So, I've been thinking; the day has arrived for me to open my eyes.
If there's someone next to me...
I must first let that person be happy, and become part of their family.
I made a vow to those words in my heart.
The Night of the Meteor Shower
The trading city situated on the northern-most islets of the Nostrum district; Ert'Aria.
There are people from various countries in this city,
gathering goods from different parts of the world.
Hence, this city is called The World's Treasury.
Right now, the entire city is busy preparing for the Harvest Festival.
This year's festival coincides with the Meteor Shower, which happens once every seven years.
As a result, the number of tourists in the city is as high as ever.
On the other side of this buzzing city sits our Guild house, Oasis.
Oasis Clan Caretaker
Nina Lindberg
Good morning, Leicester-san.
Items Engineer
Leicester Maycraft
Good morning, Nina-san.
Did you stay up all night working again?
Yeah, the automatic dishwasher that I invented is almost complete.
You shouldn't push yourself too hard.
Besides, today is the meteor shower, which happens only once every seven years.
I bet Carina-san is looking forward to it, too.
I'm back!
The Jewel of Ert'Aria
Carina Verritti
Is Leicester still asleep?
Good morning, Carina-san.
You're finally awake...
Yeah, I just got up.
I poked your sleeping face first.
Then, I pinched your nose.
The Leicester who woke up due to breathing difficulties is looking at me with a warm smile.
Good morning Carina-san.
Good morning, Leicester.
Your sleeping face is so dashing.
If that's the case, to me, Carina-san is...
Seriously, Leicester.
I'm only telling the truth.
Leicester.
Carina-san.
Welcome back, Carina-san.
What a sour yet sweet kiss.
Good morning, milady.
Morning.
Hey Nina, have you greeted Leicester?
Y-Yeah, just now...
I really wanted to be the first person to greet Leicester.
It's alright.
Look, this makes you the first person to hold my hand today.
Carina-san?
Milady.
Are you alright?
Huff~
My heart is still beating non-stop.
What's the matter, Carina-san?
No, it's nothing.
But, it sure is crowded around here.
Everybody is looking forward to tonight's meteor shower.
Yeah, we'll have to prepare properly for tonight's party.
Leicester.
Look, it's so cute.
A doll? The craftsmanship is really complex.
How was it made?
Seriously Leicester, you're always so mesmerized when you see things like this.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize...
It's over at the town square. It's incredible.
I heard the puppets are moving.
Really?
It seems to be over there.
Oh, Carina-sama.
Hey, it's Carina-sama.
The lady from the Verritti family?
Everyone, how do you do?
I see, the Leis boy is with you.
Both of you are close as ever.
Leicester, thanks for the clock you fixed.
No problem. If you need any help, feel free to call me.
That's enough already. Come over, you two.
Thank you.
Thanks everyone.
Both of you,Please look closely.
Agnes Boulange.
Self-proclaimed Best
Puppeteer in the World
Agnes Boulange
The world's number one street performer.
Wow, it's a street performance.
Well then...
Here!
Incredible.
It's as if they are alive.
Automatic puppets, Automata?
Automata?
That?
And, using this lively atmosphere; Tango!
That's the cat we saw earlier...
Say hi to everyone, Tango.
I'm Tango the white cat, at your service.
The cat spoke?!
Impressive, this is the first time I've seen a talking automaton.
You have great sight, Onii-san.
Well then...
For today's special guest, we're inviting the "Jewel of Ert'Aria", Carina-sama!
Yes?
The best puppeteer in the world, Agnes's street acrobatics...
...will now reach the climax.
Clap, clap, clap...
Leicester, I...
I'm looking forward to your performance, Carina-san.
It's showtime!
Since it's come down to this, bring it on!
Puppet dance fest.
Everyone's sure getting into it.
May I?
Yes!
Are you alright?
I failed.
Then, why don't we do it slowly?
Well, this concludes the performance of the best puppeteer in the world.
Thank you, thank you.
It's all thanks to you two. You lit up the atmosphere.
I didn't expect to have the help of the legendary Carina-sama.
No no, it's nothing like that.
We also enjoyed ourselves.
Tango-san seems to be asleep.
The more intricate the automaton, the more Ale it consumes.
[Ale: The energy source of this world]
But, I think he'll wake up later.
Speaking of which, we have quite the feast here.
This amount of food is normal for people like us from Print'brise.
My, Agnes-san is from Print'brise?
Yeah, I'm in the middle of a journey for personal reasons.
I plan to stay here temporarily before the Harvest Festival ends.
Right! I have to find a place here to stay quickly.
Why don't you come to our Guild house, Oasis?
There are still some vacant rooms.
Can I?
Of course you can.
Right, Leicester?
You're the Clan Master and since you've decided...
I have no reason to object.
I'm so lucky!
Thank you very much, Carina-sama.
Don't worry about it.
You should join us for the meteor shower tonight.
I'm so looking forward to it.
What's that?
It's the Knights Templar's parade.
Knights Templar... Followers of Rangubasu?
Yeah.
They are escorting the hidden treasure, Artifact, which is going to be displayed at the Harvest Festival.
Artifact...
You can see clearly from here.
Look Carina-sama, she is so beautiful.
Yeah, really. She looks very majestic.
She's looking this way!
Isn't staring at others considered rude?
Did you hear that, Ritos?
I did, Nee-san.
We can't pretend we didn't hear it.
Yeah, she actually ate so many desserts on her own and said it's normal.
That's not what I'm referring to!
The meteor shower, meteor shower!
Yeah, yeah...
What's with that "I don't care" face...
It's not like that...
Yes, let's chase after them.
Yeah, that's right.
We can't stand here doing nothing.
Let's go, Ritos.
Nee-san?
What?
Give me a sexy pose.
That hurt...
Nee-san, it's very slippery there. You must be careful.
You should've said that earlier!
I'm home.
Welcome back! Leicester!
You sure are late, Leicester.
Aunt Shelley...
It's scary for other people if you hug me suddenly like this, Mom.
Mother?
Capricious Mother
Shelley Maycraft
Oh? So, it's fine if no one else is watching?
She's actually Leicester's mother.
She's so young; it gave me a huge shock.
Oh my, why thank you.
Agnes-chan is also very cute.
Hello nice to meet you!
How do you know my name?
There's still some time before the party.
Yeah, actually there's someone I wanted to introduce to everyone.
Though I did tell her to come here...
Is she not here yet?
This is bad, it must be her old habit kicking in.
Shelley-sama.
Yes?
There's actually someone strolling back and forth outside the window.
That's her!
Go ahead, Chelsea.
Yes!
Knights Templar
Chelsea Arcot
I'm Chelsea Arcot from the Knights Templar.
Welcome to the Oasis Clan House.
I'm Carina Verritti.
I'm really sorry to bother you all.
Chelsea has always had a horrible sense of direction.
How embarrassing...
Hey, isn't she the one...
I see, so you're my Mom's friend.
Ah, yes.
We've known each other for quite a long time.
Coincidences really do happen.
Since she doesn't come to Ert'Aria often, I asked her to join us for tonight's party.
We're honored to have you.
It may be a bit early, but, shall we head to the party location?
Everything's prepared.
That's Nina-chan for you.
Well then, let's go!
Say, where will the party be held?
Over there.
I managed to get my Dad to let us use the roof of the cathedral.
It's the highest point in the city.
We'll be able to see the meteor shower clearly from there.
Awesome! That's the daughter of the Verritti family for you.
Oh, isn't that Carina-sama?
Carina-sama, where are you going?
Good evening, everyone.
The meteor shower is so exciting, isn't it?
Sure is.
The acrobatic girl from earlier is with them.
I really enjoyed it!
Thanks!
Look look, she's from the Knights Templar.
Yeah, she's gorgeous.
Thank you very much.
It must be hard to be surrounded by so many people.
Yeah, I'm really honored.
Seriously, Leicester.
That woman's a beauty.
The guy next to her is also very cool.
They make such a great couple.
Oh dear, how embarrassing.
I'm filled with envy.
Don't be deceived, everyone!
Good evening.
What? He greeted me so naturally.
We overheard that everyone in the Oasis Clan House will be watching the meteor shower in secret.
So, my sister stalked you guys.
Hey! You were the one who said I should follow them!
Why do you pretend you don't care?
You girls are still the same.
Who are these funny people?
They are from Tortilla Co. in front of our Clan House.
Younger of the Tortilla sisters
Ritos Tortilla
Older of the Tortilla sisters
Salsa Tortilla
Salsa-san and Ritos-san.
Putting aside my sister,
to say that I'm funny... I can't accept it.
I didn't say anything funny either.
Sure, sure.
I've been ignored.
Let me introduce them.
This girl is Agnes-chan.
I'm the best puppeteer in the wold.
Oh dear...
You actually dare to claim you're the best in the world in front of my sister.
How presumptuous.
Huh? Salsa is also a puppeteer?
No, I'm not!
Don't go about advertising me with things you just made up!
My sister's caused trouble for everyone.
I'm sorry.
Since when?!
Interesting people.
Finally, she's Chelsea-san from the Knights Templar.
Nice to meet you.
What were you two saying about not being deceived?
That's right.
Everyone, don't be deceived!
This person isn't Leicester's girlfriend, but his mother!
Right, it'll be bad if this doesn't get sorted out.
Oh? Why is that?
That's because...
Well, it means...
I see, so that's why.
It means, I am the person whom Leicester-san is going to marry.
No, what do you mean by "marry"?!
No way.
How dare you disregard me and go on talking about getting married?
Hey that's not fair! I want to marry him, too.
Like I said, what's with the marrying thing?!
OK then, just let him marry me.
No way!
You sure are popular, Leicester.
Milady, chatting may be a good thing but time is of the essence.
We should get going.
Is that so?
Strange? I thought you guys were viewing the Meteor Shower from here?
No, not really.
We are having a party on the roof of the cathedral.
I understand now.
You intend to let the people worship you from the ground.
That's too much.
Would you two like to come along?
Really?
Thanks for the offer, but we are viewing it from an even higher place.
T-That's right.
We'll go somewhere that's much, much higher than the cathedral.
Is there such a place in this city?
See ya, Leicester.
We'll take our leave.
Carina-san.
Yes?
Here, grab on.
I'm sorry.
We've been Walking the entire day.
It would be nice if these stairs continued endlessly.
We're almost at the top.
The city's view is incredible.
It's actually quite beautiful.
It has a "Welcome to Ert'Aria" sort of feel.
It's beautiful.
Quick, look!
Chelsea's skin is so soft.
Shelley, it tickles.
Shelley-sama, please don't get too carried away.
Fine!
There's plenty this year.
It's mysterious, don't you think?
Why would there be such a phenomenon every seven years?
Oh?
What's wrong?
No... that meteor seems to be getting larger.
Yeah, it's true. It feels like our sense of distance is messed up.
It seems to be headed in this direction.
Hey, is it really headed in this direction?
It's going to hit us.
Don't worry.
That meteor is just a cluster of Ale.
It has no mass.
Besides, the meteor is not headed in this direction...
Leicester!
My my, things are going to get quite interesting.
Shelley-sama, do you know if there's anything there?
That, you'll have to see for yourself.
mijika ni ite mo yoku shiranai
I don't really know when you are close,
身近にいてもよく知らない
tameiki shinpai o nosete
A sigh, showing worries
ため息　心配を乗せて
kono machi o nukeru ashita o omou
Thinking about the tomorrow
この街を抜ける　明日(あした)を思う
nanika itte yo
that this town will go through
なにか言ってよ
nanika onegai
Say something,
なにか…おねがい
yume o mita kedo oboetenai no
I dreamt, but can't remember
「夢を見たけど憶えてないの」
wasureta furi ga heta da to oshienaide
Don't tell me that, acting that I forgot is weird
忘れたふりが下手だと教えないで
massugu na kimochi ga mae o miteru
The straightforward feelings that look ahead.
まっすぐなキモチガ前を見てる
yorokobi o miteru
Looking at the joy,
喜びを見てる
mayoikeshite RIDE ON RIDE ON RISE
Erasing the worries, Ride, Ride, Rise!
迷い消して Ride on, Ride on RISE
massugu ni kaze ga egaku kaikisen
The straight tropical line drawn by the wind
まっすぐに風がえがく回帰線
ki ga tsuitara
When you realize,
気がついたら
Ah tokimeki nemuru mae ni hayaku hayaku
Ah! The excitement Before sleeping, Hurry, hurry!
Ah,ときめき眠る前に早く…早く…
Papa!
Preview
Nice to meet you, I'm Minette.
I have a favor to ask.
I'll protect you for sure if anything happens.
Leicester!
Everyone! Please!
A promise...
Yes, a promise.
Dragon's World