I'm taking my sister home.
I was planning to send her back when she regains consciousness.
Aber-nii, I got frightened.
Are you referring to the fact that I turned Miriam into an automaton?
You should know this.
She won't live long.
That's why we need Minette's core.
Nii-san.
Miriam-sama.
Miriam.
Minette-san.
You said you're preparing a new core for me, is that right?
Yeah.
Is that Minette-san's core?
Nii-san, answer me.
It's all for the sake of your health.
No way... it can't be...
This is to allow you to continue living.
There isn't any other way.
I don't want it.
I don't want to take away the life of my important friend so as to continue living.
So Nii-san, please stop it.
We're leaving, Avril.
But Minette's core, the Anima Pearl...
Our priority now should be taking Miriam home.
Yes. Let's go back, Miriam-sama.
Wait, Nii-san, Avril.
Miriam.
See you again.
Okay, see you soon Minette-san.
Let's go.
Kosobayui kedo mimikashite
It's ticklish but lend me your ear
こそばゆいけど耳かして
Sasayaita honki da yo
I'll whisper the truth.
囁いた本気だよ
Nazokake-hora-engine hashin
Riddle, here, engine start!
メンカク-ホラエンジン発進
Ima kimeta ai ni nare
Now become the love we've decided on.
いま決めたアイになれ
Tomaranai yo ne, demo saikou
It won't stop, you see. But it's the best.
とまらないよね　でも最高
Narihibike shouri no bell
The bell of echoing triumph.
鳴い響く勝利のべル
Heiwa ni sae yuuki hitsuyou
Even for peace you need courage
平和にさえ勇気ひつよう
Mezasu no wa michi no kuuro
We head for the unknown airlane.
目指すのは未和の空路
Choushi ii ne hyoushinuke
Letting down feels good
調子イイね拍子扳け
Kotae ga zannen datte
Even if the answer is disappointing
答えが残念だって
Daisuki ni nacchau yo
I'll really fall for you
大スキになっちゃうよ
Kuyashiku kokoro sawaida
My vexing heart clamored.
悔しくココロ騒いだ
Akogare no
The faraway
憧れの
Moon Light
Tookute bouzen
I admire it in amazement.
猿くて茫然
Shiawase datte mado koeru
Happiness comes through the window.
シアワセだって窓越える
High Light
Dokomademo
Going anywhere
どこまでも
Ochitsukanai koi no hate
To the end of the love that won't settle down.
落ち着かない恋の果て
Shiren wa karen ni pasu shite
Pitifully passing the test,
試練は可憐にバスして
Mou daijoubu
It's alright now.
もうだいじょう
Minette's Choice
It's a nice fragrant, Scented tea?
Yes, it's Orange Pecco.
Looks like it's going to take a while over there.
The enemy seems to be desperate.
Yeah, so we've to protect Minette-san properly.
That's right.
Papa...
I'll go and look up information about the core.
I'll ask the Knights Templar to search for Aberdeen.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Meanwhile, I'll find a way to allow both Miriam-san and Minette to be happy.
I heard Leicester-san likes grazing so I came.
So Leicester likes grazing?!
Salsa and Ritos.
Hello, Leicester-san.
I've already make sense of the situation.
From where do you understand?
From the point where the mysterious cool guy barged in.
Just say you understand from the start!
Yes, we thought of making an appearance when everyone was in a pinch to look heroic.
But the situation was so tense that we didn't know what to do.
I'm really sorry my sister is a stalker.
You were there as well!
You can leave the abnormal behaviour of the Ale to us.
That'll be a great help.
Is this alright, everyone?
Sure.
Then we'll protect Minette, the Ale matters will be left to you guys.
So that's what they decided...
I'll stay here and guard.
It's clearing up.
Minette-chan, can I ask you a favour?
Can you do the laundry?
Sure thing.
All done.
Thanks for the help.
What a nice weather.
The laundry will dry in no time if that's the case.
The wind feels good.
Yeah.
Since the weather is so good, why not have lunch here?
It's almost time for lunch?
Feel free to eat more.
I made this Pizza together with Minette.
How is it?
Yes, it's delicious.
Nick... eat slowly will you.
My bad, because it's too delicious I can't stop eating.
Seriously, you can't be helped.
Tea is next.
Thanks, Nina.
You should also join us.
Minette.
Why don't we go play at beach after this?
Alright!
I already requested the Knights Templar to search for Aberdeen.
I also managed to contact my Dad.
He's helping us by gathering information from all the clans.
Both of you did well.
Minette-chan seems to be enjoying herself.
She's unexpectedly happy, which relieves me.
Well, we'll be there for her if anything happens.
All of you are so reliable.
Well then, I should be going back-
My hair is all wet.
Come, let's go in.
It's nice to have such long hair like yours.
Your short hair is also pretty.
It's convenient when you comb or wash it.
That's right.
Is something wrong?
No.. it's nothing...
I was thinking I'm giving you, Leicester and the rest lots of trouble.
I can understand Aber-nii's feelings.
For him to be doing such things only means it isn't something minor.
But...
Are you sad?
Sad?
Aberdeen and Miriam are like a close family to you.
It's more of feeling lonely rather than feeling sad.
You're still concerned about me... Even now...
You're really kind-hearted.
You're also very kind
It tickles
Papa, you're incredible.
Initially, I could only extract a little even when I tried my best.
Really?
Papa.
I'm thinking... of letting Miriam join Oasis when she recovers.
Aberdeen and Avril too.
That's a great idea.
Clan Oasis will be invincible if that happens.
Yes it will!
Miriam...
Minette-san is a really important friend to me, so...
Miriam-sama, you should be resting right now.
Nii-san, Avril, please...
Miriam-sama...
We're almost there.
Yeah.
There are unprecedented sightings of abnormal Ale behavior, southwest of Sangula City.
Unprecedented?
According to the sightings, the Ale seems to be flowing in the reverse direction.
The occurance of a reverse Ale flow is really unimaginable given it's temperament.
The Wesico mine is the mine we visited before, isn't it?
You only realised it now?
It's the place of the service shot where you were hanged upside down.
That wasn't on purpose!
What?
W-What's that?
Hey, this doesn't look good.
We're going to be fine. Right, Ritos?
Hey, Ritos?
Papa, good night.
Good night, Minette.
You should sleep earlier too, Papa.
Sure, thank you.
Good evening, Minette-chan.
The stars are so pretty tonight.
Y-Yeah...
Do you like the sky with stars?
I love it.
What about Ert'Aria?
I really really love it.
Do you also like everyone?
I love them all.
Even Leicester?
Definitely!
Shelley-mama, you're here because you know what I plan to do?
Do you wish for me to know?
What do you want me to do?
I could persuade you to stay, or I could support your decision.
I'm not the kind of person who will stop people from doing something they want to.
Is that true?
Going all out for what you want to do.
That's a very wonderful thing.
Yes.
Have you really thought about things from all perspectives.
I did.
My son, that will panic when he wakes up and realizes that you're no longer around.
Have you thought about that?
How about everyone in Oasis who are really worried about you?
I... only thought about myself.
Well, almost everyone thinks about themselves.
Really?
Yeah.
Leicester who wants to help you and Miriam-chan.
But he didn't consider how troubled and miserable you'd be.
Aberdeen-kun also didn't spare a thought for Miriam-chan.
Same thing applies to Miriam-chan as well.
Does she understand her brother and Avril-chan's real feelings?
It's the same for anyone.
They only make an excuse for what they feel like doing.
Not caring about what others will feel.
That's because people are not linked to one another, so you can't see their feelings.
So, what are you going to do?
Mise... Altoise told you to bring happiness  to everyone.
You're wrong!
Miriam was turned into an automaton because she was sick...
Yet she still can't be cured.
But I'm the only person who can cure her.
At this moment, Miriam is still....
I experienced many happiness from Papa and the rest.
So it's now Miriam's turn to obtain happiness.
That's how I feel!
Aren't you going to discuss this with Leicester?
Because I...
really love Papa.
I don't want to be separated from him, I want to be together with him.
It's the same for Miriam and everyone, I don't want to leave them!
But... but...
Yes.
I also don't want to be separated from you.
You're a good child, you really thought over it seriously.
You've to do your best and not regret it.
I will.
Thank you very much, Shelley-mama.
I love you.
I love you too, Minette-chan.
Minette!
Leicester?
Leicester-san?
Something wrong?
Minette-san!
This bell is...
Don't tell me Minette...
No way...
Leicester!
What's wrong?
Hey! What's going on, Leicester!?
You always wish upon stars.
Minette...
I don't know what you're longing for.
Minette!
Because everything that I need is here by my side.
It makes sense stars I don't reach.
Minette!
MINETTE!
Listen to the wind sound.
We will kiss but we don't want his words for us.
Will you be my love?
Something, I got what you been looking for.
It's here in this small town you don't like.
Something says the words I never said to anyone else.
Make me smile, make me cry, make me feel.
I can't lie.
Soon you'll want me like I wanted you to say.
On your side even when you are wrong.
Gonna be your hero, save you from everything.
That I want you.
Preview
For the sake of my daughter, I will do anything.
What can you do!
You can be more stubborn...
Their Respective Feelings