Chelsea Arcot, reporting.
You came at the right time, Chelsea.
A calamity will strike Ert'Aria again.
Yes.
Your mission is to find the reason behind it,
to prevent the situation from getting worse.
Understood.
I was born for this purpose.
Right here, I have a good precognition.
Do you wish to listen?
A good precognition?
Yes. Chelsea, you'll find your happiness in Ert'Aria.
terekusai hodo chikazuite
When I get close enough to become shy,
照れくさいほど近ずいで
kikoetai koe ga aru
there is a voice that I heard
聞に声がある
wagamama muri iitai houdai
Saying something is impossible like a spoiled child,
ワカママ-ムリ言いたい放題
kikasete yo ai no shoutai
tell me the identity of love
聞かせてよアイの正体
muzukashii kara nigechatta
Ran away, because it was too difficult,
む坂しいから逃げちゃった
kanashikute mae wo mite
was sad so looked forward
悲しくて前を見て
futatabi tatsu daichi yonde
Call upon the earth once more,
再び発つ大地呼んで
ase nigiru ookina mangetsu
The breathtaking giant moon
汗握るおおきな満月
kakkou ii to kakkou warui doushite kyokutan nanda
Cool, or uncool, Why is it so extreme?
格好イイ格好ワルイ　どうして極端なだ
daisuki de daikirai na koto shika wakaranai kedo
Love it and hate it,I know nothing else, but
大スキで大っキライな事しからないけど
hajimatta
it has started
始まった
Land star isshu no bouken
Run! Start! A unique adventure,
Ｌａｎｄ　Ｓｔａｒ一種の冒険
hitori ja nai tte te wo tsunagu
Take this hand because we are not alone
ひとりじゃないって手を繋ぐ
might star me wo tojite
Boy! Start! Closing your eyes
Might Star　目を閉じて
watashi to motto iki wo sutte
Moving through the times together,
わたしともっと息を吸って
mirai ga kirei na hou he to ugoku you ni
for a beautiful future We will move towards it!
ミライがキレイな方へと動くように
Night of the Party
This is great.
I can even reach the branches in high places.
Besides the extension function that you wanted, I also reduced the weight by 20%.
Your skills are still as sharp as ever, Leicester.
Thank you very much.
Papa is awesome.
By the way, press that blue button on the handle.
Button?
This one?
I also installed a beam emission device.
R-Really?
Thanks a lot...
I-I lost.
That's Lord Arcot for you.
That strike was like a flow of water, a work of art.
No, it's not like that.
Chelsea!
Minette-san, and Leicester-san as well.
I see...
You came to return the repaired item.
That's right.
I didn't expect to see the Knights Templar in training.
What an added bonus!
Wait a minute, is that guy the rumoured boyfriend?
Yeah, Lord Arcot frequently mentions him in her conversations.
What exactly is their relationship?
Right?
The Knights are surprisingly approachable.
Well, yeah...
Hi Leicester-kun. So this is where you were.
Carina, Uncle.
Minette-chan!
You're also very lovely today.
Verritti-san is also here?
No, I went over to Oasis and heard you came here.
Chel-san is also here. That's good.
You're also looking for me?
Reward party for the Knights Templar?
Yeah, I want to organize a grand one at my place tonight.
Is it a party?
Yes, it's a small token of appreciation from us to the Knights.
It's an honour to be invited, but we have the mission to guard the Artifact.
Yeah, about that...
Leicester-kun, I want you guys to take over the Knights during the party.
The reward party starts at dusk and ends at midnight, so it won't be very long.
You only have to patrol the Sacred Temple and its surroundings.
If that's the case and you're fine with it, leave it to us.
I'm counting on you then.
Yes.
The guarding of the Sacred Temple is officially an accepted quest.
Thanks, Nina.
But... I'm really sorry about it, because of us Knights Templar...
Why are you being so formal?
That's right. Haven't you guys always been working hard for our city?
I'll do my best, too!
Minette-chan and Annie-chan will have something else to do.
Me too?
There are many fans of Minette-chan within the Knights Templar.
They've requested that you must be there for the party.
I bet it'll be fun.
You should go, Minette.
I got it.
Wow! A party!
Hey so, does it mean I also have fans?
Yeah. Everyone said they want to watch your acrobatics properly for once.
It's a pleasure. Okay, I accept.
What's with that?
That means only Leicester and I are patrolling?
Seems that way.
Chelsea-san, you should forget about your job tonight.
Have an enjoyable time at the party.
Thank you very much.
Now that everything is decided, let's start the preparations!
Yeah.
It's a special party; you have to dress up properly.
Nina, are the dresses ready?
Yes, all kinds of designs are prepared in your room.
Well then everyone, let's go and try them on.
Yes!
Here here, this way.
Everyone...
It's a perfect fit.
It's a bit hard to move around with this, but I'll bear with it since it's cute.
Yeah, both of you look gorgeous.
I'm not used to such clothes...
Well, well...
Don't worry!
We'll teach you how to wear it step-by-step!
What's wrong with all of you?
Minette, hold down Chel-san.
Alright!
S-Stop...
Is this the place where they store the Artifact?
Yeah, it is to be displayed at the upcoming Harvest Festival.
All the Artifacts from around the world will be gathered here.
That's...
The Sacred Celestine.
It's the most valuable amongst all the Artifacts.
It's the treasure of all treasures.
Just by looking at the surface, you can already tell it's made with exceptional skill.
You must be attracted to it.
As an items engineer, I'm particularly interested in it.
The people from the ancient past... Just what kind of feelings and emotions do they put into making it?
That's right.
Chelsea!
Leave this place to us.
You should be getting ready to go.
Is it time already?
You should enjoy yourself for a while, Chelsea-san.
Yes, thank you very much.
I shall leave the rest to you.
We should take turns patrolling the interior and exterior.
Fine.
Everyone from the Knights Templar, welcome!
Please make sure you forget about your usual chores and enjoy yourselves to the fullest.
May the Goddess bless Ert'Aria and Rangubasu.
Cheers!
Everyone, look here!
The acrobatics of the best puppeteer in the world, Agnes-san, is about to start.
I have been waiting.
Look over there. It's Tango-chan.
Everyone, thanks for your support.
Minette-san, try this sweet.
Please, also try this fruit.
Wow, thanks.
So adorable!
Must be nice...
I also want to wear a beautiful dress and attend the party.
What foolish words are you blabbering, Nee-san?
Our quest this time is to guard the entire party venue.
I know that...
I'm envious of Minette and the others.
They must be having a feast inside.
We're standing guard here so that the people inside can enjoy themselves.
Have more pride in your job.
Ritos...
That's right! I have to do my best.
Work is more important than having a feast.
That's just like Nee-san, what a respectable work attitude.
Wha-? What are you eating?
Food from the party. I got it when I walked past the entrance just now.
Why did you eat it on your own?
But Nee-san, didn't you mention work is more important than food?
I got scammed!
Yes, it sure is magnificent.
It was indeed the right decision to invite Oasis over.
Dad, Mum.
My, it's Carina.
Are the preparations complete?
Yes.
Quick, over here, Chel-san. Come in.
Y-Yes!
This is fabulous!
Please allow me to escort... May I?
Sure.
What elegance.
The usual Lord Arcot is beautiful, but she's particularly beautiful tonight.
Carina-san.
I still think it's better not to...
What are you talking about?
It suits you very well.
Chelsea, you're so pretty.
D-Don't stare at me like that...
Go to Chel-san...
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
Miss.
May I have a dance...
May I have a dance?
It's my pleasure.
I'm so hungry...
Here Nee-san, I left a share for you.
Really?
Sandwich...
...skins that were left over from the making process.
My younger sister is getting harsher with every word.
Ritos, did you hear something just now?
Yeah, I sensed something's aura.
Be alert, Golem.
Golem!
Hi, Chelsea.
Shelley, Nagan-dono.
Both of you are also here.
Sorry about that, I had my job so we're late.
How could I miss Chelsea's dressing up?
Stop joking about me.
Yes, your expression is not bad.
I'm relieved to see you so happy.
Yes.
Are you alright?
Sorry, it seems I drank too much.
My, what's wrong?
Chelsea?
This aura is...
Everyone, on your guard!
What's that!
Crystal monster?
How did it appear inside the city?
Everyone, attack!
Okay, Agnes!
Monte!
Activation start.
Now entering assault mode.
Mum, Dad, get away from here.
Yes.
Be careful, Carina.
Both of you, escort the Archduke and everyone to a safe place.
But, Lord Arcot...
I'll stay behind with everyone from Oasis to stop the Crystal monster.
It's too dangerous.
You don't even have your sword.
Don't worry about me.
They are with me.
Garnet, come out quick!
What's happening...
Hey, what's this supposed to mean?
It's a Crystal monster.
That thing is...
You know that thing, Garnet?
Yeah, its name is Glade Viper GX.
It's a Crystal monster that's able to hide its form and moves at high speed.
Sounds very strong.
What an exaggerated name.
No need to explain. One look and you'll know.
Over there, Annie-chan!
What a frightening creature...
Garnet, please call Papa here.
What?
Papa is at the Sacred Temple.
He'll surely think of something!
I got it. The Sacred Temple, right?
I'm counting on you.
Watch out, Minette-san!
That was close...
We're here to help.
That's impressive.
What do we do?
We won't be able to attack if we can't see it.
Nee-san, since it's come to this, it's time to use the secret weapon.
Secret weapon?
We have something like that?
Because it's a secret.
At least tell me about it!
Alright.
Press the red button on the back of Golem's head.
You sure like to order people around.
Back of the head... Back of the head...
Nekomini earmuffs
Everyone, please cover your ears and get down.
Found it.
Good! I'm pressing it.
I already predicted something like this would happen,
so I got Leicester-san to install a high frequency device.
It's useful now.
Like I always say, tell me about things like this sooner...
Where's the Crystal monster?
Did the sound frighten it away?
No, I can still feel its aura.
We were too careless.
Yeah, I didn't expect the mansion to be the target instead of the Sacred Temple.
The Crystal monsters actually appeared inside the city...
The time is approaching.
The Goddess's premonition?
It'll be fine.
We have that bunch of reliable children.
Right?
Nee-san, what are we doing now?
We're standing by to prevent the monster from escaping outside.
You're really useless, Nee-san.
Just leave it to me and Golem.
I'm counting on you, guys!
Seriously, we're at our limit just by dodging and defending.
If we could at least know the opponent's position...
If you know its position, can you think of something?
Yes.
No matter how fast it is, I'll definitely hit it...
Leicester-san?
Papa.
Leicester.
Sorry for the wait, you guys.
What do you think, Leicester?
Have you found a method to defeat that Glade Viper FX?
What?
Didn't you say GX earlier?
She told me it was EX.
It has many other nicknames!
Yes yes, let's just leave it at that.
What should we do, Papa?
That Crystal monster seems to have the tendency to attack objects emitting light.
I see, it's true.
Then...
It will surely attack if we emit a strong light.
Wait, Leicester!
It's dangerous, come back!
Come!
Max power!
Papa!
Chelsea-san! Now!
Leicester-san, that was too reckless.
Sorry. I didn't have time to explain.
Papa, thank goodness you're alright.
Speaking of which, what's that?
It's a Crystal powered lamp.
I thought I could use it for patrol purposes at night.
So I created it and it managed to be useful.
Don't make others worry like that.
Yes!
But... It's great..
Chel-san, wait!
Leicester-san, you're alright...
Chelsea-san.
Are you alright?
Hang in there, Chelsea-san!
I'm envious.
She must be exhausted.
It's still pretty messy over at the Knights Templar.
Let's have her stay at the clan house tonight.
I'll inform the two of them.
That's right, do so. I got it.
Chelsea really enjoyed it.
Yeah, she did.
She can't handle alcohol well but she drank a lot.
She even interacted with others on her own.
She wasn't used to it, but she still enjoyed herself.
I see.
I'm sure it's because someone told her to have fun.
I'm putting you down, Chelsea-san.
Yeah...
Your clothes, I-I'm leaving them here.
Sorry...
I-I think you should change later.
I got it... Nyuu...
Nyuu...?
I'll leave now.
Chelsea-san?
Leicester-san, I really enjoyed myself...
I... really...
Goodnight, Chelsea-san.
mijika ni ite mo yoku shiranai
I don't really know when you are close,
身近にいてもよく知らない
tameiki shinpai o nosete
A sigh, showing worries
ため息　心配を乗せて
kono machi o nukeru ashita o omou
Thinking about the tomorrow
この街を抜ける　明日(あした)を思う
nanika itte yo
that this town will go through
なにか言ってよ
nanika onegai
Say something,
なにか…おねがい
yume o mita kedo oboetenai no
I dreamt, but can't remember
「夢を見たけど憶えてないの」
wasureta furi ga heta da to oshienaide
Don't tell me that, acting that I forgot is weird
忘れたふりが下手だと教えないで
massugu na kimochi ga mae o miteru
The straightforward feelings that look ahead.
まっすぐなキモチガ前を見てる
yorokobi o miteru
Looking at the joy,
喜びを見てる
mayoikeshite RIDE ON RIDE ON RISE
Erasing the worries, Ride, Ride, Rise!
迷い消して Ride on, Ride on RISE
massugu ni kaze ga egaku kaikisen
The straight tropical line drawn by the wind
まっすぐに風がえがく回帰線
ki ga tsuitara
When you realize,
気がついたら
Ah tokimeki nemuru mae ni hayaku hayaku
Ah! The excitement Before sleeping, Hurry, hurry!
Ah,ときめき眠る前に早く…早く…
Preview
Papa praised me.
You actually used sleep medicine. You're so capable Nee-san.
Minette-chan was born here.
Even this kind of timing...!
Yes, I found it.
I was always looking for it.
The Puppet Forest
Finally...