We're in a time of peace
Shows power like this
are just going to give off the wrong impression
You honestly believe your children can win a war?
I hope they never have to
I don't understand how everyone can be so calm
You're still thinking about Torchwick?
Torchwick, the White Fang, all of it
Something big is happening and no one is doing anything about it
We're not ready
And we may never be ready
Our enemies aren't just gonna sit around and wait for graduation day
They're out there somewhere, planning their next move
And none of us know what it is, but it's coming
Have a little faith
You'll know what you need when you need to know
Our second semester's going to be great
But classes start back up tomorrow
Which is why I've taken the time to schedule a series wonderful events for us today
This ought to be good
They're supposed to be the defenders of the world
And they will be
But right now they're still children
So why not let them play the part
It isn't the role they'll have forever
BRB
This SUB is presented by Baidu RWBY Bar
Creator: sbz_kid