The world of Remnant is a dangerous place
Particularly for man
In the countless years that humanity has roamed the planet, civilizations have grown and fallen
But four have withstood the test of time
Atlas
Mistral
Vacuo
Vale
These four kingdoms with the help of natural barriers and human tenacity, have proven that they have the will to survive
Each kingdom has a governing council to represent the people and their needs
Next, comes the military
While most kingdoms only call on its citizens to serve when needed
others find it important to be..prepared
There are still those who choose to venture outside the walls of the kingdoms
Roaming nomads and small villages are not uncommon
Yet neither is their tendency to..disappear, overnight
Lastly, the Huntsmen academies
These institutions' soul purpose is to train the next generation of huntsmen
The next generation of defenders that will live and die to protect the lifestyle that they've become so accustomed to
Yes, the world of Remnant is indeed a dangerous place
But the four kingdoms stand as beacons of hope
As safe havens from the darkness that surrounds them
They are the key to mankind's survival
as long as they stand united..
BRB
This SUB is presented by Baidu RWBY Bar
Creator: sbz_kid