Dust
By definition it is a naturally occurring energy propellant
that can be triggered by the Aura of Humans and Faunus
But in reality, it is much much more
Found in four basic forms, Dust can be combined both artificially and naturally to form new stronger types
Each with unique properties
Since its discovery
Men has concocted on multitude of ways
in which to harness the power of this mysterious crystals
From airships to androids
Dust has made its way into practically every facet of technology
Some prefer to use Dust in its raw form
Elegant, yet destructive
Those who choose to wield Dust in this state must possess a certain level of discipline
to ensure that their resulting powers do not break free from their control
Dust ammunition serves as a more practical application in today's modern society
With the technological advancements in weapon design
Warriors need simply choose the right cartridge for the job, and pull the trigger
Well, this is become the standard method of use
It is not uncommon to find individuals still practising more archaic forms of Dust manipulation
Such as weaving it into clothing
or even fusing it directly with their own bodies
Despite working, fighting, and even turning a profit with it
Humanity has still yet to understand how Dust came to be
And more importantly
How their involvement with Dust, will ultimately change the world of Remnant
BRB
This SUB is presented by Baidu RWBY Bar
Creator: sbz_kid